<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--以下特殊字符不可使用：-->
<!--&rsquo;全局替换为'-->
<!--<br/>换行符全局替换为\n-->
<blogs>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>1</id>
        <date>November 27, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Difficult Customer</title>
        <description>
            A: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I’ll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order? B: No, I’m still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What’s good here?
        </description>
        <cover>images/waitress.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0001pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Difficult Customer **\nA: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I'll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order?\nB: No, I'm still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What's good here?\nA: For you sir, I would recommend spaghetti and meatballs.\nB: Does it come with coke and fries?\nA: It comes with either soup or salad and a complimentary glass of wine, Sir.\nB: I'll go with the spaghetti and meatballs, salad and the wine.\nA: Excellent choice, your order will be ready soon.\nB: How soon is soon?\nA: Twenty minutes?\nB: You know what? I'll just go grab a burger across the street.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**still working on** : not yet completed, need more time\n**would recommend** : suggest\n**complimentary**: free\n**go with**: to choose, pick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>2</id>
        <date>November 28, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Calling In Sick</title>
        <description>
            A: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you? B: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.
        </description>
        <cover>images/calling.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0002pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Calling In Sick**\nA: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you?\nB: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.\nA: Hi, Julie, how are you?\nB: Actually, I'm feeling quite ill today.\nA: I'm sorry to hear that. What's wrong?\nB: I think I'm coming down with the flu. I have a headache, a sore throat a runny nose and I'm feeling slightly feverish.\nA: I see... so you're calling in sick?\nB: Yes, I was hoping to take the day off to recover.\nA: OK, then. Try and get some rest.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**was hoping** :to kindly expect\n**calling in sick**: report that you will not go to work because you are sick\n**coming down:**getting, acquiring\n**quite ill**: very sick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>3</id>
        <date>November 29, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Hotel Upgrade</title>
        <description>
            A: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?
        </description>
        <cover>images/hotel.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0003pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Hotel Upgrade **\nA: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?\nB: I'd like to check in please. I have a reservation under the name Anthony Roberts.\nA: All right R.O.B.E.R.T.S... Oh, Mr. Roberts we'vebeen expecting you&amp; and here is your keycard to the presidential suite.\nB: But there must be some mistake; my reservationwas for a standard room.\nA: Are you sure? Let me double check .\nB: Yeah&amp;Here, this is my confirmation number.\nA: You're right Mr. Roberts, there seems to be a mixup,unfortunately we're overbooked at the moment.\nB: So..\nA: Not to worry. We're pleased to offer you a complimentaryupgrade.\nB: Presidential suite baby!\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**check in** :register at a hotel or airport\n**under the name:** name used for the reservation</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>4</id>
        <date>November 30, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - I need an assistant</title>
        <description>
            A: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fist-bumps.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0004pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Office - I need an assistant!**\nA: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.\nB: I understand that, but the fact is we're understaffed.\nA: The timing is just not right. The economy is bad,and it's too risky to take on new staff.\nB: Yeah, I guess you're right.... here's an idea, what if we hire an intern? She would take some of the weight off my shoulders.\nA: She?\nB: Yeah, you know, a recent graduate. She could give me a hand with some of these projects and we could keep our costs down.\nA: That sounds reasonable... let me see what I can do.\nA: Tony, I'd like to introduce you to your new assistant.\nB: OK, great! Let's meet her!\nC: Hi, I'm Adam.\nB: Oh... hi... I'm Tony...\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**resources** : money\n**understaffed** : not enough people to do the job\n**the timing is just not right** : it is not a good time now\n**weight off my shoulders** : remove pressure or stress</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="markdown_tools.html">
        <id>5</id>
        <date>November 30, 2018</date>
        <title>Tool - Markdown实时预览及Html互转</title>
        <description>
            Markdown 是一种简单的、轻量级的标记语法。用户可以使用诸如 * # 等简单的标记符号以最小的输入代价生成极富表现力的文档。
        </description>
        <cover>images/markdown.jpg</cover>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>6</id>
        <date>December 1, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Cut In Line</title>
        <description>
            A: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.
        </description>
        <cover>images/queue.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0005pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Cut In Line**\nA: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.\nB: Yeah, but just relax honey, we're here and we're going on vacation. In a few hours we'll be in Hawaii, and you'll be on the golf course.\nA: Oh no! Look at that line! It must be a mile long!There's no way I'm waiting for another two hours.\nB: Honey... don't...\nC: Hey man, the end of the line is over there.\nA: Yeah...\nC: No seriously, I was here first, and you can't cut in line like this.\nA: Says who?\nC: I do!\nA: So sue me!\nC: Alright...that's it....\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**There's no way** : impossible\n**cut in line** : jump the queue (in British English)</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>7</id>
        <date>December 2, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Road Trip</title>
        <description>
            A: So, are we all ready to go? B: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.
        </description>
        <cover>images/roadtrip.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0006pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Weekend - Road Trip**\nA: So, are we all ready to go?\nB: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.\nA: Did you get the camera?\nB: Got it! Did you fill up the tank?\nA: Yup, it's all set.\nB: You're sure we're not forgetting anything?\nA: I'm sure... we've got all our bases covered.\nB: Well&amp; let's get going then! I love road trips!\nB: Um... do you think we can make a pit stop?\nA: But we've only been on the road for ten minutes.\nB: I know, but I forgot to go to the bathroom before we left.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**all ready to go**:prepared, ready to leave\n**packed**:full, everything is inside\n**fill up the tank**:put gas in the car\n**all set**:ready</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>8</id>
        <date>December 3, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Computer Virus</title>
        <description>
            A: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.
        </description>
        <cover>images/computer-stethoscope.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0007pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>"**The Office - Computer Virus! **\nA: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.\nB: Just give me a second; I'll be right up.\nB: I ran a virus scan on your computer, and it turns out that you have a lot of infected files!\nA: But I'm quite careful when I'm browsing the internet, I have no idea how I could have picked up a virus.\nB: Well, you have to make sure that your anti-virus software is updated regularly; yours wasn't up to date, that's probably what was causing your problems.\nA: Ok. Anything else?\nB: Yeah, try not to kick or hit the computer!\nA: Um yeah; Sorry about that."</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>9</id>
        <date>December 4, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - G20 Summit is Holding in Buenos Aires</title>
        <description>
            World leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine.
        </description>
        <cover>images/G20.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181203_0014852xLB.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nWorld leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine. James Landale is at the summit. President Putin is likely to face tough questions over Russia seizure of Ukrainian vessels. President Trump said he wouldn't meet the Russian leader until the confrontation was resolved. And Mohammad bin Salman the Saudi Crown Prince is also in town looking to repair his reputation after the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi. But for all these tensions, European leaders said it was important for the G20 to come together to tackle the world's problems.\nBefore the summit formally got underway, the United States, Canada and Mexico signed a new trade deal. This is seen as a victory for Mr. Trump who opposed the previous agreement. Andrew Walker reports. Many barriers to commerce between the US, Canada and Mexico were removed or reduced by the North American Free Trade Agreement, which came into force a quarter of a century ago. But President Trump called it the worst trade deal ever. Now, the three leaders have signed a replacement which keeps much of the original agreement. But it includes additional provisions that will, for example, make it more expensive for car makers to use parts from outside the region and will mean more opportunities for US dairy farmers to sell their milk products in Canada. It has been a contentious negotiation and there were reports that late disputes about the dairy issue might have held up the signing ceremony.\nInternational Olympic Committee says it's freezing all planning for the boxing tournament at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics because of concerns about the sport's governing body. It's launching an inquiry into the International Boxing Association AIBA over its governance, ethics and financial management. Our sports correspondent Alex Capstick reports. The IOC halted preparations for the Olympic boxing tournament in Tokyo, including the qualifying process following talks among the organization's leading officials in the Japanese capital. For several months, serious concerns have been expressed over the way the sport's governing body has been run. It came to a head earlier this month when Gafur Rahimov was elected as president of AIBA, despite allegations that he's part of an international criminal network, something he's always denied. But whatever is ultimately decided regarding the future of AIBA, the IOC still wants boxing to be part of the Tokyo Games.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181204.jpg](images/bbc-20181204.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n世界各国领导人现正在布宜诺斯艾利斯参加G20峰会，峰会已表现出了紧张和分歧，许多是因为特朗普总统在贸易和气候变化上的好斗态度引发。俄罗斯对乌克兰采取的军事行动又进一步加重了大会的紧张氛围。以下是詹姆斯·兰德尔的报道。普京很有可能会因俄罗斯扣押乌克兰船只而面临尖锐的提问。特朗普表示在对峙解决之前他不会与普京见面。沙特王储穆罕默德·本·萨尔曼也来到了这里，试图挽回一下因沙特记者贾马尔·哈苏及被杀事件而受损的名声。虽然本次大会充满了紧张气氛，欧洲领导人表示最重要的是各国能聚在一起解决世界问题。\n在峰会正式开始之前，美国、加拿大和墨西哥签署了一份新的贸易协议。这被认为是特朗普的胜利，因为他反对之前的协议。以下是安德鲁·沃克的报道。北美自由贸易协定消除或降低了很多美国、加拿大和墨西哥之间的贸易壁垒，该协议在25年之前正式生效，但是特朗普称这是有史以来最差的贸易协议。现在这三名领导人已经签署了一个替代协议，保留了很多之前的协议内容。但是也新增了一些附加条款，比如汽车生产商使用该区域之外零件将会更加昂贵，另外也会更有利于美国奶农向加拿大销售奶制品。协商的过程很激烈，有报道称近期的乳制品问题争端或延长签字仪式。\n国际奥组委称正在冻结2020年东京奥运会的拳击比赛筹备工作，原因其管理机构存在问题。它正在对国际拳击联盟AIBA的管理情况、道德和金融状况进行调查。以下是本台体育通讯员亚历克斯·卡普斯蒂克的报道。国际奥组委停止了东京奥运会拳击比赛的筹备工作，包括资格赛，此前奥组委主要官员在日本首都举行了会谈。几个月以来，国际奥组委一直都在担心该体育机构的运作方式。本月初，加弗尔·拉西莫夫成功当选 AIBA主席，事情也达到了非做不可的地步，拉西莫夫被指是国际犯罪网络成员，但他本人否认。无论AIBA的前景如何，国际奥组委仍然希望拳击项目出现在东京奥运会上。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>10</id>
        <date>December 5, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Yellow Vest Movement in Paris</title>
        <description>
            The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances.
        </description>
        <cover>images/yellow-vest-movement.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181204_3542471yYn.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello. The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances. He was speaking after the latest protest saw the demonstrators attack police and spray graffiti on the Arch of Triumph. This report from Hugh Schofield. Demonstrators, some of them clearly agitators rather than bona fide yellow vests have fought running battles with police. They have torn up cobblestones to serve as projectiles and set fire to cars and even buildings. Police responded with tear gas and anti-riot grenades. What's been happening today takes the "yellow vest" movement to a new level. The scenes unforgettably vivid are of destruction. President Macron who's in Argentina at the G20 needs urgently to find a way out of this confrontation.\nMexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has promised to scrap the neoliberal economic policies of the past twenty five years. Speaking at his inauguration ceremony and Congress, Mr. Lopez Obrador said neoliberalism had led to poverty, crime and mass migration in Mexico and promised a new start. Starting from now, a peaceful and orderly transformation has begun that at the same time will be profound and radical, because we will end the corruption and impunity that impede Mexico's rebirth. The left-wing leader also announced the creation of a free trade zone in a vast area next to the border with the United States, where taxes will be lower and the minimum wage higher.\nThe African Union says it's worried about the lack of progress of peace talks for Burundi and has urged all sides to refrain from taking any judicial action that could cause further rifts. The warning comes a day after the Burundian government issued an international arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya and sixteen high ranking officials. Will Ross reports. The warning from the African Union appears to be aimed at the government of Burundi. Peace talks with the opposition have stalled and some feared the government has risked opening old ethnic wounds by issuing the arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya. The move is an awkward one for the African Union because Mr. Buyoya is now working for the AU as its special representative in Mali. The 1993 assassination of President Melchior Ndadaye, the country's first Hutu leader triggered the civil war in which three hundred thousand people were killed. That was Will Ross. This is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181205.jpg](images/bbc-20181205.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。法国总统马克龙谴责了巴黎反政府游行暴力事件，称这根本不是表达不满的合法方式。在最近的示威活动中，游行人群袭击了警察，还在凯旋门上涂鸦，之后法国总统做了这番讲话。以下是休·斯科菲尔德的报道。许多游行者很明显是鼓动者而不是真正的“黄马甲”抗议人士，他们与警察打起了游击战。他们将鹅卵石当作投掷物，点燃汽车甚至是建筑物。警察用催泪弹和防爆手雷进行了反击。今天发生的事情让“黄马甲”运动再次升级。这里到处都是毁灭的景象，让人历历在目。总统马克龙正在阿根廷参加G20峰会，他正迫切地想解决冲突的方法。\n墨西哥新总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔承诺将会取消施行25年的新自由经济政策。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔在就职仪式和国会上表示新自由经济政策导致了贫穷、犯罪和大规模移民，他承诺墨西哥将会有一个新的开始。现在，一个和平有序的变革已经开始，同时它也是深刻彻底的，因为我们会根除阻碍墨西哥重生的贪污和法外逃脱。这名左翼领导人还宣布将会在与美国接壤的广阔区域开创一个自由贸易区，这里的税率将会更低，最低工资也会更高。\n非洲联盟称他们对布隆迪和平谈判没有进展感到担心，并且敦促各方避免采取可能导致分歧加深的任何司法行动。在非盟发出警告的前一天，布隆迪政府发布了对前总统皮埃尔·布约亚和16名高级官员的国际逮捕令。以下是威尔·罗斯的报道。非盟的警告很明显是针对布隆迪政府的。布隆迪政府与反对党的和平谈判已经陷于僵局，一些人担心政府将会通过发布前总统皮埃尔·布约亚的逮捕令重新揭开之前的民族伤疤。此举让非盟处于一个尴尬的境地，因为布约亚现正为非盟工作，在马里任特派代表。1993年，该国首个胡图族领袖，总统梅尔基奥尔·恩达达耶被刺杀，这引发了国内战争，导致30万人被杀。以上是威尔·罗斯的报道。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>11</id>
        <date>December 6, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Mexico's new President start investigating the disappearance of 43 students</title>
        <description>
            On his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago.
        </description>
        <cover>images/安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1205_2603183KA2.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nOn his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago. The incident sparked weeks of protests. Will Grant reports.\nThe whole government is going to help with this plan. President Lopez Obrador told the victims' families who had gathered for the event, "and I can assure you that there will be no impunity either in this sad and painful case or in any other." It has been more than four years since the group of 43 young men and women were disappeared allegedly by State Security Forces. The lack of meaningful action or any prosecution of those involved was a stain on the previous administration, and human rights groups have long called for a new investigation.\nOne of Afghanistan's top sports officials has admitted for the first time that players in the women's national football squad and in other sports have been sexually abused and the problem must be addressed. The allegations of years of rape, sexual harassment and sexual coercion have been voiced publicly by a former captain of the women's football team. Jill McGivering reports.\nThe comments by Hafizullah Rahimithe, the head of Afghanistan's National Olympic Committee are the first official acknowledgment that the allegations of abuse made by some Afghan women footballers may be credible. Khalida Popal, a former team captain has been trying for years to highlight sexual assault, harassment and bullying by coaches and officials, which she claims to have witnessed and had reported to her. Officials in the Afghanistan Football Federation say the claims are untrue. Women involved in other sports have also spoken to the BBC,but are frightened of being identified.\nAn eighty-year-old woman has become the latest casualty of anti-government protests in France. She died in hospital in the southern city of Marseille after being hit in the face by a tear gas canister as she drew the shutters of her fourth floor apartment during rioting on Saturday. Three other deaths have been blamed on the protests.\nTwo jailed Catalan separatist leaders have announced that they're going on hunger strike from Tuesday, joining two colleagues who stopped eating at the weekend. Joaquim Forn and Josep Rull, said they were protesting against the Constitutional Court's refusal to let them appeal to European Courts against pretrial detention. The trials of nine Catalan separatists who have been held in jail for up to fourteen months are due to begin in January. Uruguay has rejected an asylum request by the former President of Peru Alan Garcia, who's under investigation for corruption. He entered Uruguay's embassy in Lima two weeks ago after a court banned him from leaving the country for the next eighteen months. Mr. Garcia says the allegations are politically motivated. The Uruguayan government praised Peru's legal system.\nThis is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181206.jpg](images/bbc-20181206.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n在墨西哥新任总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔就职的第一天，他签署了一项法令启动一个真相调查委员会，调查4年前43名学生失踪一案。该事件也引发了数周的抗议活动。以下是威尔·格兰特的报道。\n政府将全力协助实施该计划。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔总统对集结的受害者家属表示，“我能向你们保证，在该起沉重悲痛的案中或是在任何其他的案件中，凶手都逃脱不了惩罚。”当时据国家安全部队称有43名年轻男女失踪，此时距此已过去四年多的时间了。上一届政府没有实质性作为，也没有对涉案人员提起诉讼，这已经成为他们的一个污点，另外，人权组织在很久之前就要求对此展开新的调查。\n一名阿富汗体育部门高官首次承认国家女子足球队以及其他体育队的运动员受到性侵害，并称该问题必须要得到解决。女子足球队的前队长公开发声，称她们受到多年的强奸、性骚扰和性胁迫。以下是吉尔·麦吉弗林的报道。\n阿富汗国家奥委会主席哈飞祖拉·拉西梅斯所做出的评论是官方首次承认，阿富汗女足队员提出的性侵指控或许是可信的。哈莉达·博帕尔是一名前队长，多年来她一直试图曝光球队教练和官员的性侵、性骚扰和霸凌行为，她声称曾亲眼目睹也向主席报告过这些行为。阿富汗足协官员表示这些指控并非事实。其他项目的女队员也向BBC说了这件事，但她们害怕被认出来。\n一名80岁的女性成为法国反政府游行活动的又一位遇难者。她在法国南部城市马赛市的医院中去世，死因是在周六暴乱中，她在四楼房间里拉百叶窗时被一枚催泪弹击中面部。还有其他三名遇难者死于抗议活动中。\n两名被监禁的加泰罗尼亚分裂主义领导人宣布他们将从周二开始绝食抗议，他们的两名同事早在上周就开始了绝食。乔吉姆·弗恩和约瑟夫·罗尔表示，他们是在抗议宪法法庭拒绝让他们就审前羁押向欧洲法庭提起上诉，狱中的九名加泰罗尼亚分裂主义分子被判监禁14个月之久，并将从一月份开始服刑。乌拉圭拒绝了秘鲁前总统阿兰·加西亚的庇护请求，现在他正在接受腐败调查。两周之前，法院判定他在未来18个月内不得出国，之后他来到乌拉圭驻利马大使馆。加西亚表示这些指控都带有政治动机的，而乌拉圭则称赞了秘鲁的法律体系。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="music/index.html">
        <id>12</id>
        <date>December 6, 2018</date>
        <title>Music - 告白气球（周杰伦）</title>
        <description>
            Music - 告白气球（周杰伦）
        </description>
        <cover>images/balloon.jpg</cover>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>13</id>
        <date>December 7, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit</title>
        <description>
            The British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit by warning Parliament that the choice is between her deal, no deal and no Brexit.
        </description>
        <cover>images/brexit.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181206_2216387HVk.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello.\nThe British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit by warning Parliament that the choice is between her deal, no deal and no Brexit.\nDon't let anyone here think that there's a better deal to be won by shouting louder. Don't imagine that if we vote this down, a different deal is going to miraculously appear. The alternative is uncertainty and risk. So I promise you today, this is the very best deal for the British people. I ask you to back it in the best interests of our constituents and our country.\nDuring the debate, Mrs. May said the EU had neither the time nor the inclination to reopen negotiations before Britain leaves next March.\nThe US Special Counsel Robert Mueller says Donald Trump's former National Security Advisor Michael Flynn should face little or no prison time for giving what he called substantial assistance to the Russian election meddling probe. Mr. Mueller is leading an investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 US presidential election. In court documents filed on Tuesday, Robert Mueller said Mr. Flynn has given first-hand details of contacts between Mr. Trump's transition team and Russian government officials.\nUS stocks have fallen sharply on fears of an economic slowdown. The Dow Jones Industrial Average had its worst day in nearly three months. All of the major US indexes ended the trading day down by more than three percent.\nWe've seen all of the major indexes down more than three percent. You've got bank stocks leading the way, but it wasn't just bank stocks, it was transportation stocks, industrial stocks, Caterpillar, General Electric. A lot of this has to do with concerns or warning signals flashing from the bond market, suggesting that there's perhaps worries about economic growth lying in the future. The likelihood of a recession is much higher and that's why market watchers are paying so much attention to this and getting spooked today.\nThat was Michelle Fleury and markets in Asia also opened sharply lower.\nA group of US Congress members have called on the Rwandan government to drop charges against Diane Rwigara, a government critic who's facing up to 22 years in prison on charges of incitement and fraud. She's due to be sentenced in Rwanda later today. Supporters say the charges are politically motivated and arose from Ms Rwigara's bid to run against President Paul Kagame in last year's elections.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/TheresaMay.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻，大家好。\n英国首相特蕾莎·梅开启了一场为期五天的重要脱欧辩论，以此警告议会要么接受她的协议，要么无协议脱欧，要么不脱欧。\n不要让在座的人认为通过大喊大叫就能赢得一项更好的协议。不要幻想着否决了这份协议，就会有一份不同的协议奇迹般地出现。替代方案充满了不确定性和风险。所以今天我向你们保证，这是一份对英国民众来说最好的协议。 为了我们的人民和国家的最大利益，我请求你们支持这份协议。\n在辩论中，特蕾莎·梅表示欧盟没有时间也没有意愿在英国明年三月脱欧之前再次开启协商。\n美国特别顾问罗伯特·米勒表示特朗普的前国家安全顾问迈克尔·弗林为俄罗斯干预美国大选的调查提供了实质性的帮助，因此他将面临短期刑期或零刑期。米勒正在带头调查俄罗斯干涉美国2016年总统大选一案。在周六的一份法庭文件中，罗伯特·米勒表示弗林提供了关于特朗普过渡团队和俄罗斯政府官员联系的一手资料。\n出于对经济衰退的担忧，美国股市暴跌。道琼斯工业平均指数达到了近三个月以来的最低点。所有的主要美国指数在交易日结束时都下降了3个百分点以上。\n我们看到所有的主要工业指数都下降了超过3个百分点。银行股票首当其冲，但是不仅仅是银行股票，运输业股票、工业股票、卡特彼勒和通用电气的股票都受到了影响。很多都和债券市场传递出的担忧和警告信号有关，这也暗示了人们对于未来经济增长的担忧。出现经济衰退的可能性变得更高，这也是为什么市场观察者今天如此关注该事件并感到惊慌的原因。\n以上是马歇尔·弗勒里的报道。亚洲市场开盘同样大幅下跌。\n美国国会议员呼吁卢旺达政府撤销对政府批判人士黛安·瑞嘉的指控，因煽动和诈骗指控，她将面临22年之久的刑期。今天晚些时候将在卢旺达进行宣判。支持者表示这些指控带有政治动机，且是由于瑞嘉去年与保罗·卡加梅竞选总统引起的。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>14</id>
        <date>December 8, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in Washington</title>
        <description>
            There have been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the National Cathedral in Washington.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fly-a-flag-at-half-mast.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181207_3945526LE6.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News. The French government is abandoning plans to increase fuel taxes that prompted weeks of sometimes violent demonstrations. Four people died and hundreds were injured. After suspending the measure temporarily earlier this week, the Prime Minister Edouard Philippe has announced that it'll be dropped altogether from legislation on next year's budget. He said the government had to maintain peace. If the state is to remain strong and firm, it is first of all, the guarantor of public peace. To set the course and hold it is necessary in order to govern France. And as I said yesterday, no tax is worth putting the unity of the nation in danger.\nSerbia says it's considering military intervention as a possible response if its former province of Kosovo goes ahead with a plan to create its own army. President Aleksandar Vucic said the proposal was aimed at driving out Serbs still living in Kosovo.\nThe Liberian state energy company says about sixty percent of all electricity generated in the country is stolen. The theft is causing estimated losses of about thirty five million dollars a year as Warren Bull now reports. The Liberia energy corporation says large numbers of people are making illegal connections to their homes and businesses. Speaking to state radio, a spokesman said the theft was diverting cash that would have been used to improve power supplies to the west African country. Liberia is trying to rebuild an energy sector destroyed during a civil war which lasted from 1989 to 2003. The United States is giving financial and technical aid to increase connectivity as part of the Power Africa Initiative launched by the former US President Barrack Obama.\nBut the country still has one of the lowest access rates to energy in the world, only one in eight Liberians have electricity. There have been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the National Cathedral in Washington. Gary O'Donoghue was following the ceremony. With full pomp and ceremony, America paid tribute to its 41st President, a man who spent a lifetime in public service. George W. Bush, eldest son and 43rd President delivered the warmest of eulogies. But in America he leaves behind a country much changed since he controlled the levers of power, a country divided in ways that would have been anathema to his brand of politics. This is the latest world news from the BBC.\n![](images/bush-funeral.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。法国政府将放弃上涨燃油税的计划，该计划也激起了数周暴力时发的游行活动。已有四人死亡，数百人受伤。本周初该计划暂时中止之后，总理爱德华·菲利浦宣布上涨燃油税将从明年的预算法案中移除。他表示政府需要保持和平状态。如果法国要保持强大和稳固的话，首先它要保证治安。在治理法国方面，制定方向和稳固这一方向是必要的。正如我昨天所说的，没有一项税法可以不顾国家的统一。\n塞尔维亚称或考虑武力介入，如果原省份科索沃实施创建军队的计划。总统亚历山大·武契奇表示他们的计划是驱逐仍生活在科索沃的塞尔维亚人。\n利比里亚国家能源公司表示大约60%的国家电力被盗。偷电行为造成了大约每年3500万美元的损失，以下是沃伦·布尔的报道。利比里亚能源公司表示大量民众正在为其家庭和企业非法连接电网。一名发言人对国家广播说，偷电行为所转化的钱本应该用于为这个西非国家改善电力供应。利比里亚正在重建毁于1989年到2003年内战期间的电力部门。美国正在为利比里亚提升电网连接提供财力和技术支持，这也是由美国前总统巴拉克·奥巴马发起的非洲电力计划的一部分。\n但是该国仍然是世界上电网连通率最低的国家之一，只有八分之一的利比里亚人通上了电。美国前总统老布什的国葬在华盛顿的国家大教堂举行，人们向他表达了真挚的悼念。盖里·奥德诺霍正在对葬礼进行报道。在隆重的葬礼上，美国民众向第41任总统致以敬意，他将一生的时间都用在了公共事业上。他的大儿子，美国第43任总统小布什发表了最温暖的悼词。自从他掌控权利杠杆以来，他离开后的美国发生了很大变化，国家的分裂现状也正是他的执政理念所深恶痛绝的。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>15</id>
        <date>December 9, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Russia will respond in kind if US pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles</title>
        <description>
            President Putin of Russia says his country will respond in kind if the United States pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles.
        </description>
        <cover>images/nuclear-missile.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1209_3508560Wg5.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Neil Nunes.\nA new global climate study says carbon dioxide emissions will reach a record high this year, much of it caused by the burning of coal in China and the increasing use of cars. The research says worldwide CO2 output is projected to rise by 2.7% this year, compared to 2017.\nA series of confidential emails between senior figures at Facebook reveal the social media giant gives some companies preferential access to users’ data. That meant the firms could see information about users’ friends. Netflix and Airbnb were among the firms given privileged access.\nThe Liberian state energy company says about 60% of all electricity generated in the country is stolen. Officials from the Liberian electricity corporation told state radio that large numbers of people are making illegal connections to their homes and businesses. They said the theft caused annual loss of $35 million.\nPresident Putin of Russia says his country will respond in kind if the United States pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles. It follows a 60-day ultimatum to Moscow to comply with the treaty.\nScientists in Britain have completed the world’s largest gene sequencing project in health care, which is hoped will revolutionize medical treatment for people with cancer and rare diseases. The researchers have mapped 100,000 human genomes. Each one contains a person’s DNA and errors that then can trigger a vast range of disorders.\nThere’ve been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the national Cathedral in Washington. Mr. Bush’s biographer Jon Meacham called George H. W. Bush the last great soldier-statesmen.\nBBC news.\n![](images/Putin.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n尼尔·努内斯为您播报BBC新闻。\n一项最新的全球气候研究指出，二氧化碳排放量今年将达到历史新高。其中很大一部分是由全球汽车使用量升高以及中国的燃煤造成的。该研究指出，全球二氧化碳的排放量今年或同比上升2.7%。\n脸书上两位高层人士的机密一系列机密邮件表明，脸书这家社交媒体授予一些公司特权，让它们可以获取用户数据。也就是说，这些公司可以看到用户朋友是谁等信息。包括网飞公司和爱彼迎在内的一些公司都获得了这样的特权\n利比里亚国家能源公司称，该国近60%的发电量都被窃取了。该公司工作人员在接受国家电台采访时表示，很多人都会非法连接家和企业的电网。他们称，这种窃取行为导致3500万美元的年损失额。\n俄罗斯总统普京表示，如果美国退出冷战时期的核武器控制协议，那么俄罗斯会以牙还牙，并会研制新型导弹。俄罗斯此举是在美国给其下了60天合规的最后通牒后做出的。\n英国科学家完成了世界上最大的卫生保健领域的基因序列测定项目。有人希望这个项目能为癌症和稀有疾病患者带来变革性的医学治疗。研究人员绘制了10万个人类基因组。每个都包含一个人的DNA以及会导致大量失调的误差。\n人们在华盛顿国家大教堂为美国前总统乔治·布什举行了国葬，热切缅怀这位领袖。布什传纪作者乔恩·米彻姆称布什是最后一位伟大的战士及政治家。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>16</id>
        <date>December 10, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines</title>
        <description>
            North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines and improvised explosives after almost a decade of conflict in the region.
        </description>
        <cover>images/mines.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc181209_5909215h4F.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines and improvised explosives after almost a decade of conflict in the region. The Islamist group Boko Haram continues to attack towns and villages and to kidnap hundreds of school girls, most notoriously from the town of Chibok in 2014. The number of people being killed and injured by mines and explosives in Nigeria has greatly increased according to research by the Mines Advisory Group (MAG). Over 160 killed in the past two years, with hundreds more injured. It's had a devastating impact on the region and prevents large areas of land from being farmed, and it's a familiar pattern across the globe.\nSo how many landmines are there around the world? Minefields are often the deadly remnants of war left behind long after the combatants have gone. Under international law when mines are laid they must be mapped so they can be removed safely at a later date. All too often they're not mapped or maps are lost and process of de-mining can be a slow and dangerous one. In 2016, post-conflict clearance operations undertaken by charities such as the Halo Trust destroyed over 200,000 anti-personnel and 20,000 anti-vehicle mines around the world. But this hardly scratches the surface of the problem. There are still an estimated 110 million anti-personnel mines still in the ground with more being laid every year in active conflict areas. In a single year as many as 8,000 people are killed or seriously injured many of them children. That's almost one person killed or injured every hour of every day. That figure has risen as a result of the widespread use of improvised explosive devices by non-government forces.\nBBC news.\n![](images/landmines.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n在尼日利亚东北部地区冲突停止几乎10年后，其地下仍然埋着上千的地雷和简易爆炸装置。而布下这些地雷和爆炸装置的伊斯兰组织“博科圣地”现在仍然在袭击城镇和乡村，并且因在2014年绑架了奇博克上百名学校女生而臭名远扬。根据地雷顾问团的调查，在尼日利亚，因为地雷和爆炸丧命和受伤的人数有了大幅的增长。在过去两年，尼日利亚超过160人因为地雷丧命，还有上百人因此受伤。地雷给尼日利亚东北部地区带来了灾难性的冲击，大面积地区受此影响不能耕种，全世界其他地区也都是类似的模式。\n那么在全世界地下埋着多少地雷？布雷区在参战方离开很久后，经常还是致命的战争遗留物。根据国际法，地雷在被布下后，必须在地图上标注，这样它们过后可以被安全移除。但是经常是，它们没有被标注或者地图遗失了，因此排雷的过程变得非常缓慢和危险。在2016年，像哈洛信托这样的慈善组织在后冲突地区进行了排雷行动，共摧毁全世界范围内的超过20万杀伤人员地雷和2万反载具地雷。但是这几乎没有解决问题。据估计，全世界的地下仍然埋着1.1亿杀伤人员地雷，并且在活跃的冲突地区每年还会布放新的地雷。单单一年，就有8000人因为地雷丧命或严重受伤，很多是儿童。这几乎相当于每天每小时就有一人因为地雷丧命或者受伤。这个数字还在增长，因为非政府武装力量现在广泛使用简易爆炸装置。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>17</id>
        <date>December 10, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei</title>
        <description>
            There's been a renewed selloff on Wall Street with traders alarmed about the arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei.
        </description>
        <cover>images/court-sketch.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1209_0119272DVx.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Jonathan Izard.\nThere's been a renewed selloff on Wall Street with traders alarmed about the arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei. The US national security adviser John Bolton admitted that he had known the arrest in advance. He said Huawei was one company Washington suspected was being used as an arm of the Chinese government.\nRwanda's high court has acquitted the political activist Diane Rwigara and her mother of charges of forgery and inciting insurrection. Miss Rwigara served more than a year in prison after being disqualified from running in presidential elections. She said the charges were politically motivated.\nThe Hungarian National Association of Journalists says it will challenge the government in the constitutional court for establishing a pro-government media conglomerate, and for exempting it from scrutiny. The Central European Press and Media Foundation was established last month by the authorities who said it was in the national interest.\nThe Eiffel Tower and a number of Paris museums and markets will be shut on Saturday amid fears of further street violence involving the “yellow vest” protest movement. The demonstrations began in protest of fueled tax rises, but have broadened amid anger about rising living costs.\nThe Netherlands has ordered an investigation into illegal adoptions by Dutch couples of foreign children. It will focus first on the adoption of children from Brazil, but will also of the cases from Columbia, Indonesia, Sri Lanka and Bangladesh over the 3 decades of the late 1990s.\nA leading human rights group says it has received credible reports that a 4th Saudi women’s rights activist has been tortured while in detention. Saudi Arabia denied earlier reports that 3 leading women activists detained this year have been assaulted and sexually harassed.\nProtests have been taken place in Bolivia in 8 of the country's 9 regional departmental capitals after the court ruled both the President Evo Morales and vice president would be allowed stand for office in primaries in January.\n![](images/MS_Meng.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n乔纳森·伊泽德为您播报BBC新闻。\n华尔街再次出现抛空现象，因为投资者受到警示——中国科技公司华为某高管在加拿大被捕会对股市造成影响。美国国家安全顾问约翰·博尔顿承认在逮捕之前，他已得知此事。他表示，美国政府怀疑华为是中国政府的左膀右臂。\n卢旺达高等法院无罪释放了政治活动家戴安娜及其母亲，赦免了她们的伪造罪和煽动暴动罪。戴安娜曾服刑1年多，此前她欲参加总统竞选但却被认定不符合资格。她表示，这些罪名都是有政治意图的。\n匈牙利全国新闻工作者协会称其会在宪法法院与政府对簿公堂，内容有关政府成立了一个支持政府的传媒集团，并免除该集团审查的事宜。中欧新闻和媒体基金会于上个月由当局成立，当局说这是符合国家利益的。\n埃菲尔铁塔和一些巴黎博物馆和市场将于周六关闭，因为有人担心与黄背心运动有关的街头暴力会愈演愈烈。抗议示威起于赋税的上涨，因民众对生活成本升高恼火而加剧。\n荷兰要求调查本国夫妇非法收养外国儿童。调查将首先关注巴西儿童的收养，但也会考虑哥伦比亚、印尼、斯里兰卡、孟加拉国等国在上世纪90年代末期至今30年间的收养案例。\n某知名人权组织称自己收到了可信报告，报告指出第4位沙特女权活动家在拘留期间受到虐待。沙特否认了此前的报告，而此前报告指出，今年已经有3位知名女性活动家在拘留期间遭到强暴和性骚扰。\n玻利维亚已发生多次抗议事件。全国的9个大城市里有8个发生了抗议事件。原因是法院判决总统埃沃·莫拉莱斯和副总统都可以参加1月的初选。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>18</id>
        <date>December 11, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A pivotal moment in Donald Trump's presidency</title>
        <description>
            Court documents filed ahead of the sentencing of President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen have revealed new details about his contacts with Russia before the 2016 election.
        </description>
        <cover>images/Donald-Trump.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181210_5936360QGP.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is the BBC News with Fiona Macdonald. Court documents filed ahead of the sentencing of President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen have revealed new details about his contacts with Russia before the 2016 election. The memo from the Special Counsel Robert Mueller says Mr. Cohen met a trusted person in the Russian Federation. A separate document filed by federal prosecutors directly implicate President Trump in Michael Cohen's illegal payments to two women. Jon Sopel reports. These two filings could turn out to be a pivotal moment in Donald Trump's presidency. For the first time in a document from federal prosecutors, there's an accusation that in effect, Donald Trump broke the law during the presidential election campaign in buying the silence of two women who claimed to have had affairs with him. Michael Cohen has pleaded guilty to paying off the former porn star Stormy Daniels and a Playboy Model Karen McDougal in breach of Campaign Finance Laws. But the prosecutors say that he acted in coordination with and at the direction of Individual-1. Individual-1 in these court papers is the president.\nNearly 90,000 police are being deployed across France to counter a fourth weekend of protests by the "yellow vest" movement. Shops and metro stations have been closed in Paris. Lucy Williamson reports. Eight thousand security forces will be deployed in the capital, almost double that of last weekend. Another eighty thousand will be spread throughout France. They are expected to be more mobile than before and more proactive in tackling any threat. The government has said it expects extreme violence and that today's protesters include people who are coming explicitly to smash and it says to kill. The Interior Minister described the movement as a monster that was escaping its creators' control.\nA stampede at a nightclub in central Italy has killed at least six people. About a thousand people were in the venue in Corinaldo near Ancona, one of Italy's best-known rapper Sfera Ebbasta was performing at the club. Here's Caroline Rigby. What we're hearing is that people smelt a strong odor that they think might have been something like pepper spray. They fear that that might have been sprayed that caused people to panic inside, try and flee, trampling over each other according to officials and that caused a number of them to be crushed. We're hearing around a hundred have been injured, about ten of them seriously that they've been taken we understand to two nearby hospitals where the injured are being treated. You're listening to the world news from the BBC.\n![](images/nightclub.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，欢迎收听BBC新闻，我是菲奥娜·麦克唐纳德。在特朗普前律师迈克尔·科恩宣判之前，法庭公布的文件透露了他在2016年大选时与俄罗斯联系的新细节。特别顾问罗伯特·米勒的备忘录称科恩曾与一个“受信任”的俄罗斯联邦人士见过面。由联邦检察官发布的一份独立文件直接表明，特朗普与迈克尔·科恩向两名女性非法付款有关。以下是乔恩·苏博尔的报道。因这两个文件的发布，特朗普的总统生涯将会迎来一个关键节点。这是第一次在联邦检察官的文件中有对特朗普的指控，称他在总统竞选活动中花钱让两名女性保持沉默，这两名女性都声称与特朗普有染。迈克尔·科恩承认花钱买通前成人影星斯托米·丹尼尔斯和花花公子模特凯伦·麦克道戈，这违反了竞选金融法。但是检察官称他的行为是协同、并在“一号人物”的命令下实施的，法庭文件的一号人物指的是总统本人。\n法国部署了将近九万名警察，来对抗“黄马甲”运动人士第四周的抗议活动。巴黎的商店和地铁站都已关闭。以下是露西·威廉姆森的报道。八千名安全部队将会被部署在首都，几乎是上周人数的两倍，另外八万名警察将会分布在法国各地。预计他们在处理公共威胁方面将会更具机动性和主动性。政府表示将会迎来极度的暴力事件，今天的抗议人群中就有人明确表示是来破坏的，更有人称将会杀人。内政部长将这场运动称为洪水猛兽，现已脱离了其组织者的控制。\n意大利中部的一家夜店发生了一起踩踏事件，导致至少6人死亡。大约1000人聚集在安科纳市附近的科里纳尔多的一家场馆中，当时意大利一名非常出名饶舌歌手斯菲拉·伊博斯塔正在这家夜店表演。以下是卡罗兰·里戈比的报道。我们当时听到的是人们闻到了刺激的气味，他们认为应该是胡椒喷雾之类的东西。根据官方的消息，他们担心有人喷洒胡椒喷雾，造成了场馆内部人员的恐慌，人们仓皇失措四散逃离，造成了踩踏事件，并造成多人被踩伤。我们收到消息称现有100多人受伤，10人伤势严重，据我们所知伤者已被送往附近的两所医院接受治疗。您正在收听的是BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>19</id>
        <date>December 12, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - UNCCC in Poland failed in keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5℃</title>
        <description>
            Delegates at a UN climate change conference in Poland have expressed dismay over the failure to welcome an international report on keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5 degrees Celsius.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pollution.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181211_0704496Gbq.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Julie Candler with the BBC news. President Trump says his Chief of Staff John Kelly will leave his post at the end of the month. He told reporters he would decide on General Kelly's replacement within the next few days. A former Marine General with deep government know-how, John Kelly first served Mr. Trump as Homeland Security Secretary. As Chief of Staff, he was widely seen as bringing discipline to the White House. Here is Dan Johnson in Washington. The job of Chief of Staff is talked of as an important insider role, someone who can go into the Oval Office and tell the President the hard truth. So people are looking with interest for who Donald Trump will replace John Kelly with because he apparently was prepared to tell the President how it was. That's why their relationship has been fraught over the last eighteen months, why there have been occasions where apparently John Kelly was close to resigning.\nDelegates at a UN climate change conference in Poland have expressed dismay over the failure to welcome an international report on keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5 degrees Celsius. Our environment correspondent Matt McGrath is at the conference. Here in Poland, efforts to welcome the report and recognize its significance quickly run into difficulties. Saudi Arabia, the US and Russia merely wanted to take note of the report. This dispute over words masks a deep row between countries that want rapid political action on cutting carbon and those who do not. As no acceptable compromise could be found, the text had to be dropped under UN rules. Many delegates were outraged by what they saw as a blatant attempt to weaken the science on climate change.\nSeveral women have come forward in Brazil to accuse an internationally known self-proclaimed spiritual healer of sexually abusing them. Joao Teixeira de Faria better known as Joao of God, has followers all over the world. Our America's editor Candace Piette has more details. On Brazil's Globo TV network, a Dutch woman Zahira Leeneke Maus accused Mr. Faria of manipulating her to perform sex acts and then raping her. Nine other Brazilian women who remained anonymous gave similar accounts. They say the abuse happened at Mr. Faria's spiritual clinic near Brasilia where he said to treat ten thousand people a month, many of them foreigners. In a statement to Globo TV, Mr. Faria's office strongly denied the allegations.\nThe government of Angola says it wants to begin discussions about the ownership and possible return of artifacts that were taken from the country before its independence from Portugal in 1975. The Culture Minister says so far no list of relevant objects has been put together, but that officials had identified several Angolan pieces of art in a museum in Lisbon. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/UNCCC.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是朱莉·钱德勒，欢迎收听BBC新闻。特朗普称白宫幕僚长约翰·凯利将会在月底卸任。他告诉记者称将会在几天内决定凯利将军的替代者。作为一名深谙政事的前海军将军，约翰·凯利最初任特朗普的国土安全部长。作为白宫幕僚长，他因为白宫肃整纪律而被广为所知。以下是丹·约翰逊在华盛顿的报道。幕僚长被认为是一个非常重要的内部角色，因为他可以直接走进总统办公室，向总统谏忠言，所以人们都很关心特朗普将会选谁作为约翰·凯利的替代者，因为很明显他准备告诉总统事情的来龙去脉，这也是为什么二人在过去18个月里关系令人担忧的原因。这也是为什么约翰·凯利多次几近辞职的原因。\n在波兰举行的联合国气候变化大会上，代表们感到十分失望，因为没有在全球控温1.5摄氏度这一国际报告上达成一致。以下是本台环境通讯员马特·麦格拉斯的在会议现场的报道。在波兰，这份报告的推广以及重要性认同方面很快遇到了困难。沙特阿拉伯、美国和俄罗斯仅仅表示会关注该报告。此次争论也隐藏了深层次的争吵，那就是想要立即采取政治措施减排和不想减排国家之间的争论。由于没有能接受的折中方案，这份报告只能按照联合国规定搁置。许多代表因一些国家公然无视气候变化的科学性而感到愤怒。\n在巴西，多名女性提出性侵指控，被指控人享誉国际，且自称是一名心灵治愈师。乔安·特谢拉·德·法里亚被熟知为“上帝的乔安”，他的追随者遍布全世界。以下是本台美洲编辑坎迪斯·皮尔特的报道。在巴西的环球电视台上，荷兰女性扎希拉·里尼卡·摩斯指控法里亚操纵她进行性行为，然后强奸了她。9名匿名的巴西女性也给予了类似的描述。她们称性侵就发生在法里亚在巴西利亚附近的精神诊所中，他称这里每月接待一万名病人，大部分都是外国人。在一份递交给环球电台的声明中，法里亚办公室强烈否认了这些指控。\n安哥拉政府表示希望与葡萄牙讨论1975年安哥拉独立前被抢走的艺术品的所有权并希望葡萄牙归还。葡萄牙文化部长表示目前为止没有相关的文物列表，但是其官员在里斯本的一家博物馆里认出了一些安哥拉艺术品。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>20</id>
        <date>December 13, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The former Nissan Chairman has been officially charged with underreporting his income</title>
        <description>
            The former Nissan Chairman Carlos Ghosn has been officially charged by Japanese prosecutors with underreporting his income by about 44 million dollars over a five-year period.
        </description>
        <cover>images/nissan-symbol.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1212_2312850BRX.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is the BBC News with Fiona Macdonald.\nThe former Nissan Chairman Carlos Ghosn has been officially charged by Japanese prosecutors with underreporting his income by about 44 million dollars over a five-year period. He denies the allegation. Mr. Ghosn was one of the most high-profile car company bosses in the world. From Tokyo, Rupert Wingfield-Hayes reports.\nProsecutors have finally indicted Mr. Ghosn, accusing him of making misstatement on Nissan's annual securities reports. The indictment has come 22 days after Mr. Ghosn's arrest at Tokyo airport, and on the last day prosecutors could hold him without charge. In addition, this morning, the Japanese Securities and Exchange Commission asked prosecutors to indict Mr. Ghosn for suspected violations of financial rules. It's not clear whether this is a new and separate allegation.\nArmenia's acting Prime Minister Nikol Pashinyan has consolidated his authority with a landslide victory in a snap parliamentary election. He came to power in a peaceful revolution earlier this year and has promised to tackle corruption and reform Armenia's economy. Rayhan Demytrie reports.\nNikol Pashinyan's My Step coalition has received around 70% of total votes cast by Armenians in snap parliamentary elections. Two other parties passed the threshold and will be apportioned seats in parliament. But the former governing Republican Party is out. Early results suggest it picked up less than five percent of the vote, a stunning defeat after ruling Armenia for almost two decades. Mr. Pashinian will now have to begin the task of carrying out ambitious reforms to improve his country's economy and raise standards of living for ordinary Armenians.\nExit polls from the Peruvian referendum suggest the country is back the anti-corruption reforms of President Martin Vizcarra. Local media reporting that people have voted in favor of judicial reform, changes to campaign finance laws, and restrictions on the number of consecutive terms able to be served.\nThe French President Emmanuel Macron is due to meet trade unionists and business leaders following another weekend of violent anti-government protests in Paris and other cities. Mr. Macron has remained largely silent over the unrest. He scheduled to make an address to the nation later on Monday.\nThe European Court of Justice is to rule in the next few hours on whether the UK can unilaterally pull out of the process governing its withdrawal from the EU. Last week, a chief legal advisor to the court said Britain could do so without permission from other member states, as long as the decision followed a parliamentary vote, a general election or a referendum.\nBBC news.\n![](images/nissan-chairman.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，欢迎收听BBC新闻，我是菲奥娜·迈克唐纳德。\n日产汽车前会长卡洛斯·戈恩现已被日本检察官正式提起公诉，罪名是在5年期间内未如实上报其收入约四千四百万美元。他本人否认了这项指控。戈恩曾是世界最知名汽车公司的老板之一。以下是鲁珀特·温菲尔德-海耶斯的报道。\n检察官最终向戈恩提起了诉讼，指控他在日产的年度证券报告中造假。戈恩在东京机场被捕22天后检方对他提起了诉讼，那也是检方可以在不起诉他的情况下扣押他的最后一天。另外，今晨日本证券交易委员会要求检察官以涉嫌违反金融法规的罪名起诉戈恩。现尚不明确这是否是一个新的不同的指控。\n亚美尼亚代理总理尼科尔·帕希尼扬以压倒性优势取得了议会提前选举的胜利，巩固了他的政权。他在今年年初的一次和平革命中上台，承诺将会处理贪污腐败问题并改革亚美尼亚的经济。以下是瑞翰·迪米特里的报道。\n在议会提前选举中，尼科尔·帕希尼扬所在的“我的步伐”联盟获得了约70%的选票。另外两个政党得票通过最低门槛，并将在议会中获得席位。但是前执政党共和党却已出局。早期结果表明该政党的选票不足5%，这也是该党执政亚美尼亚近20年来最大的落败。帕希尼扬现在需要开始实施他宏大的改革计划，以改善本国的经济并提高普通亚美尼亚民众的生活水平。\n秘鲁公投后的民调显示本国民众支持马丁·比斯卡拉总统的反腐改革。当地媒体报道称人们支持司法改革、竞选金融法革新以及对连任次数进行限制。\n法国总统埃马纽埃尔·马克龙将会见工会人士和商界领袖此前巴黎和其他城市周末再次爆发暴力反政府游行。马克龙在骚乱之后基本上都在保持沉默，他计划在周一发表全国演讲。\n欧洲法院将会在接下来的几个小时内裁定英国是否可以单方面退出脱欧进程。上周，欧洲法庭的一名首席法律顾问表示英国可以在不经过其他成员国的许可下退出，只要该决议通过议会投票、普选或是全民公投就行。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>21</id>
        <date>December 14, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The President of the European Commission has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit</title>
        <description>
            The President of the European Commission Jean-Claude Juncker has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit deal that the British Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to salvage.
        </description>
        <cover>images/brexit2.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181213_5721302yF6.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is Charles Carroll with the BBC News. The President of the European Commission Jean-Claude Juncker has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit deal that the British Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to salvage. Mrs. May is on a tour of Europe to ask Mr. Juncker and her Dutch and German counterparts for assurances to try to convince sceptical British MPs to back the agreement. Earlier today, Mr. Juncker addressed the European Parliament. There is room if used intelligently, there is room enough to give further clarifications and further interpretations without opening the Withdrawal Agreement. This will not happen: everyone has to note that the Withdrawal Agreement will not be reopened. Many British MPs fear the country could become permanently stuck in a legally binding backstop plan to avoid re-establishing a hard border in Ireland. Mrs. May canceled a parliamentary vote on her deal due to have taken place today and acknowledged that she would have been defeated.\nThe United Nations has launched a plan to support more than five and a half million refugees from Syria who are being hosted in neighboring countries. The organization is appealing for 5.5 billion dollars to help provide education and other services. Imogen Foulkes reports from Geneva. Since the Syrian conflict began, a million Syrian babies have been born in exile. A trickle of refugees around thirty seven thousand have returned home this year, and that could increase to a quarter of a million next year. But it's just a fraction of the estimated 5.6 million Syrian refugees in neighboring countries. Return is risky. Sporadic fighting continues.\nAt least ten people have been killed in an overnight attack by a rebel group in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo. Local officials say suspected members of the Allied Democratic Forces attacked the town of Oicha in the Beni region where they looted property and animals. The ADF which began as a Ugandan rebel group in the 1990s, has been blamed for hundreds of killings since 2014.\nA Franco-German meeting is underway in Paris to counter the smuggling of illegal firearms from the western Balkans. The French Foreign Minister Jean-Yves Le Drian said that Europol estimated that up to six million firearms were in circulation in the countries of the former Yugoslavia. Forty-four thousand illegal firearms had been destroyed there over the past year, he said, but that was not enough. He stressed the need for tighter checks on the borders of Bosnia-Herzegovina. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/BritishPrimeMay.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是查尔斯·卡罗尔，欢迎收听BBC新闻。欧盟委员会主席让-克洛德·容克表示英国脱欧协议没有重新商讨的余地，英国首相特蕾莎·梅仍在努力挽救该协议。特蕾莎·梅正在欧洲寻访，并希望容克，荷兰和德国领导人能够给予保证，说服持怀疑态度的议员们支持这项协议，今天早些时候，容克在欧洲议会发表了讲话。如果明智的话，我们还有空间来继续阐明，给予更深入的解释，而无需启动脱欧协议。这是不会发生的，所有人都应该知道脱欧协议不会重启。很多英国议员害怕英国将会长期困在受法律约束的后备计划上，以避免爱尔兰再次出现“硬边界”问题。特蕾莎·梅取消了原定于今天举行的脱欧协议议会投票，并承认她有可能会被打败。\n联合国已经启动了一项对超过550万叙利亚难民的支持计划，他们正流落在邻国。该组织正在请求55亿美元的资金向他们提供教育和其他服务。以下是伊莫金·福克斯的报道。自从叙利亚冲突开始之后，有一百万叙利亚婴儿在流亡之路上出生。大约有三万七千人的小股难民已在今年返回故乡，明年这一数字将增加到二十五万人。但这也是逃亡到邻国的五百六十万难民的一小部分。回家之路充满危险，零星冲突还在继续。\n在刚果民主共和国东部，至少有10人在叛军夜袭中死亡。当地官员表示“民主联盟军”成员涉嫌袭击了贝尼地区的奥伊察镇，并抢走了他们的财产和家畜。“民主联盟军”由上世纪九十年代乌干达的一个叛军组织发展而来，因从2014年起杀害了数百人而饱受指责。\n一场法德会议现正在巴黎召开，来应对西巴尔干地区的非法军火走私问题。法国外长让-伊夫·勒德里昂表示欧洲刑警组织预计高达六百万件军火在前南斯拉夫国家流通。他表示，四万四千件非法军火去年在那里被销毁，但是还远远不够。他强调需要加强在波黑边界的检查。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>22</id>
        <date>December 15, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership</title>
        <description>
            The British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership of the governing Conservative Party.
        </description>
        <cover>images/starsbourg-terrorist-shooting.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1214_3534614MX4.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello.\nThe British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership of the governing Conservative Party. The Party's Members of Parliament backed her by 200 votes to 117 in a secret ballot. The BBC's Laura Kuenssberg has this assessment.\nThis was a clear result in favor of the Prime Minister, but also a clear picture of a party in conflicts and a result brokered only by a promise from Theresa May to go, if not just yet. She'll have now what a loyal minister described as a little more time. And yes Tory rules say that she can stay on undisturbed by the same kind of challenge for another twelve months. But while she is temporarily safer, Theresa May has less clout. A Prime Minister with a sell-by date holds less sway.\nPresident Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen has been sentenced to three years in prison for lying to Congress and violating US Election Finance Laws. Nada Tawfik is at the court in New York.\nMichael Cohen hung his head and shook it in disbelief when the sentence was read. He was hoping for no jail time, but the judge ultimately imposed three years in prison. Substantial but still on the lower end of sentencing guidelines. The judge said that Michael Cohen had lost his moral compass and should have known better as a lawyer, and he said that no future cooperation could be taken into consideration in sentencing.\nFrance remains on its highest level of security alert as the search continues for a gunman who shot dead two people near a Christmas market in Strasbourg on Tuesday. The authorities have issued a photo of the suspect. The French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe has announced the deployment of hundreds more soldiers across the country.\nAs of today, five hundred soldiers have been added to the force, and in the coming days, thirteen hundred will join those already mobilized. The objective is to secure sites open to the public, particularly Christmas markets.\nThe United States has warned Turkey against carrying out unilateral military action in northern Syria. The Pentagon said such a move would be of grave concern and could jeopardize US troops helping to fight the Islamic State group. The statement was issued after Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdogan said his forces would begin a military operation against a US-backed Kurdish militia in the region.\nYou're listening to the world news from the BBC News.\n![](images/conservative-party-vote.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n英国首相特蕾莎·梅挺过执政党保守党对她领导能力的不信任投票。在无记名投票中，党内国会议员给她投了200个支持票和117个反对票。以下是我台劳拉·昆斯伯格的观点。\n对于首相来说这明显是一个有利的结果，但是这也清楚地表明了党内存在分歧，而这一结果的促成源于特蕾莎·梅离任的承诺，离去只是时间问题。正如一名拥护她的大臣所说，她现在又多了一些时间。按照保守党的规定，一年内不会对她发起不信任投票。尽管她暂时安全一些了，但是特蕾莎·梅的影响力已不如从前。一个被加上“保质期”的首相，其影响力也会下降。\n特朗普总统的前私人律师迈克尔·科恩因对国会说谎以及违反美国选举财务法被判刑三年。以下是那达·托菲克在纽约法庭的报道。\n当法官宣判时，迈克尔·科恩俯首摇头，不敢相信这样的结果。他本希望不会被判入狱，但是法官最终判了他三年的刑期。虽获刑，但也是按照量刑标准从轻宣判。法官表示迈克尔·科恩丧失了道德准则，身为律师知法犯法，法官还表示宣判结果没有商量的余地。\n法国仍处于最高级别的安全警戒状态，同时也在继续搜寻一名枪手，周二他在斯特拉斯堡的一家圣诞节市场附近枪杀了两人。政府已经发布了嫌犯的照片。法国总理爱德华·菲利普宣布在全国范围内再部署数百名士兵。\n截至今天，已有500名士兵加入武装力量，接下来的几天里还会有1300名士兵加入到队伍中。他们的任务就是保护开放的公共区域，尤其是圣诞节市场。\n美国警告土耳其不要在叙利亚北部发动单方面军事行动。五角大楼表示这样的举动将会引起严重关切，也会危害帮助与伊斯兰国组织战斗的美国的士兵的安全。在此声明发布之前，土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安曾表示他的军队将会对该区域内美国支持的库尔德民兵组织发动军事行动。\n您正在收听的是BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>23</id>
        <date>December 16, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A Syria refugee living in British Villa as Green Fingers</title>
        <description>
            I have been so lucky to be living here for the last year. My parents, my brothers and sisters, I've sent them so many pictures and they don't believe it because for me this house is a place where I used to see in a movie, in an old English movie.
        </description>
        <cover>images/horticulture.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc181216_1238273D7T.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I have been so lucky to be living here for the last year. My parents, my brothers and sisters, I've sent them so many pictures and they don't believe it because for me this house is a place where I used to see in a movie, in an old English movie. The only reason that I left Syria and my brother who's two years older than me left was the government army, which we didn't want to join. We didn't want to hurt people, we didn't want to kill people.\nThat's not us. This is not what our religion taught us. I was hoping to come back in six months time. So, I was like: 'Mum I'm going to see you in six months time.' But here I am after seven years and I didn't see her. I started my journey through Turkey, Greece, the boat. Complete horror and just, just pure fear. We ended up in the Calais Jungle. The most horrendous place I've ever been in Europe. I've got to the UK, applied for asylum. I met this really nice lady who helped me when I was having trouble with accommodation and I met with the Chair and Trustee of this house, of Southside House. I have always felt lucky in this place. So mostly I work in the garden. I think they say I have green fingers. Green fingers? Is that right? I grew up in a very beautiful farm house with my parents, with animals. And I used to help my mum in the garden. My mum grew vegetables.\n![](images/english-house.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我过去一年都住在这里，感觉自己太幸运了。我给我的父母还有兄弟姐妹发了很多照片，他们不相信我住在这，因为对我来说，这样的房子只存在于我过去常常看的电影里，英国老电影里。我离开了叙利亚，比我大两岁的哥哥也离开了，我们离开的唯一原因是因为政府军，我们不想加入政府军。我们不想伤害人，我们不想杀人。\n那不是我们想做的事。这不是我们的宗教教我们做的事。我当时希望六个月后就可以回去。所以当时想说：妈妈，我六个月后去看你。但是我在这里七年了，我没有去看她。我是从土耳其和希腊开始我的旅程的，做船。充满了恐怖，纯粹的恐惧。我们在加来丛林结束了旅程。那是我到欧洲后去过的最可怕的地方。我到了英国后，申请了避难。我遇到了这位非常善良的女士，她在我住宿遇到麻烦时帮助了我，我和这个房子——“南侧房”的主席兼受托人见了面。在这个房子里，我总是感觉很幸运。大部分时间我都在这个花园工作。我想他们说我有“绿手指”。绿手指？对吗？我在一个非常漂亮的农舍长大，还有父母和动物陪伴。我过去常常在菜园里帮我妈妈干活。我妈妈种菜。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>24</id>
        <date>December 17, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida has been broken</title>
        <description>
            The UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida that came to effect on Friday has been broken. Fighting erupted on the city's outskirts. Residents said they could hear shelling and gun fire. The Saudi-backed government and the Iranian-backed Houthi rebels had reached the truce after a week of talks in Sweden.
        </description>
        <cover>images/yemen-ruins-children.png</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1216_5431545hMR.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Ally Macue.\nThe UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida that came to effect on Friday has been broken. Fighting erupted on the city's outskirts. Residents said they could hear shelling and gun fire. The Saudi-backed government and the Iranian-backed Houthi rebels had reached the truce after a week of talks in Sweden.\nThe military in Nigeria has accused the United Nation's Children’s Agency of training and deploying spies for Islamist militants, and suspended UNICEF operations in the northeast. The suspension has surprised the agency which told the BBC it would verify the statement.\nPresident Trump's former lawyer says the US leader knew he was wrong toward payments to keep 2 women silent about the alleged affairs with him. Mr. Trump had denied asking Michael Cohen who has been sentence to jail to break the law.\nThe head of the Russian Orthodox Church has accused Ukraine of persecuting believers. These comments come ahead of a meeting to create an independent Ukrainian church, a plan that has infuriated President Putin.\nThe United Nations has launched an emergency appeal to help house and feed around 3.5 million Venezuelan refugees who fled their country's severe economic crisis. The UN says it's the first plan of its kind in the Americas.\nProsecutors in Spain have accused the Columbian pop star Shakira of tax evasion, alleging that she owes more than 16 million dollars. They argued she was living in Spain for 2 years while listing her official residence elsewhere. Shakira denies evading tax.\nThe college campus in the Indian city of Madras has set up separate entrances and wash basins for students eating vegetarian and non-vegetarian food in the canteen. Some students have reportedly called the move untouchability.\nAnd the BBC's African Footballer of the Year award has gone to Liverpool's Egyptian striker Mohamed Salah. It's the second year in the row that he's won.\nBBC news.\n![](images/trump-deny-silence-affair.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nAlly Macue为您播报BBC新闻。\n联合国在也门的重要港市荷台达就停火进行了调解，而调解本来于周五生效，但现在又被打破了。荷台达郊区爆发了冲突。市民称他们听到了枪炮声。由沙特支持的政府军和伊朗支持的胡塞叛军在瑞典进行了一周的会谈后本来达成了停火协议。\n尼日利亚军方控诉联合国儿童基金会为伊斯兰激进分子培训并部署间谍，并终止了自己在东北部的行动。终止行动一举让联合国儿童基金会大为震惊。后者在接受BBC采访时表示会确认该说法的真实性。\n特朗普总统前律师称，特朗普知道自己不应该给2名女子封口费，让她们对与自己的风流韵事保持缄默。特朗普否认曾要求目前已入狱的迈克尔·科恩做违反法律的事情。\n俄罗斯东正教会领袖指责乌克兰迫害信徒。在此番言论之后将召开一场会议，这次会议将创建一个独立的乌克兰教会，而这个计划激怒了普京总统。\n联合国发起了应急呼吁，以帮助收留350万名委内瑞拉难民，并为他们提供食物。这些难民都是为了逃离本国严重的经济危机而来的。联合国表示，这是第一次在美洲发起这样的计划。\n西班牙检察官指控哥伦比亚流行歌手夏奇拉存在逃税行为，并称夏奇拉已逃税1600多万美元。检察官称，夏奇拉在西班牙生活了2年，但却将官方住处登记在其他地方。而夏奇拉本人否认逃税。\n印度马德拉斯市的大学校园在食堂设立了分开的入口和洗手池给素食主义者和非素食主义者。据报道，一些学生称此举完全是贱民制的表现。\n我台非洲足球先生的奖项颁发给了利物浦的埃及中锋穆罕默德·萨拉赫。这是穆罕默德·萨拉赫连续第二年获得该奖项。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>25</id>
        <date>December 17, 2018</date>
        <title>iOS - Refactoring Code</title>
        <description>
            iOS代码重构 : Refactoring - 改善既有代码的设计
        </description>
        <cover>../refactoring/1.png</cover>
        <markdown-content>![](../refactoring/2.png)![](../refactoring/3.png)![](../refactoring/4.png)![](../refactoring/5.png)![](../refactoring/6.png)![](../refactoring/7.png)![](../refactoring/8.png)![](../refactoring/9.png)![](../refactoring/10.png)![](../refactoring/11.png)![](../refactoring/12.png)![](../refactoring/13.png)![](../refactoring/14.png)![](../refactoring/15.png)![](../refactoring/16.png)![](../refactoring/17.png)![](../refactoring/18.png)![](../refactoring/19.png)![](../refactoring/20.png)![](../refactoring/21.png)![](../refactoring/22.png)![](../refactoring/23.png)![](../refactoring/24.png)![](../refactoring/25.png)![](../refactoring/26.png)![](../refactoring/27.png)![](../refactoring/28.png)![](../refactoring/29.png)![](../refactoring/30.png)![](../refactoring/31.png)![](../refactoring/32.png)![](../refactoring/33.png)![](../refactoring/34.png)
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>26</id>
        <date>December 18, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Australia now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel</title>
        <description>
            The Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison has said his country now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. But in a speech in Sydney, Mr. Morrison said the Australian embassy would not be relocated from Tel Aviv until the final status of Jerusalem was resolved.
        </description>
        <cover>images/sri-lanka.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181217_0244391RFT.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news. I'm John Shea. Tens of thousands of police have been deployed across France in preparation for the latest protests by the "yellow vests" movement. Paris has been shaken by some of the most serious rioting in decades over the last two weekends. Indications so far are that fewer people will join the demonstrations this week. Here's Hugh Schofield. After President Microns offered to open up the state's coffers on Monday, some in the "yellow vests" movement have acknowledged that that was a major step forward and they are calling for a pause. Others fear that the violence at the last two Saturday protests, much of it actually caused by young opportunists rather than bona fide protestors, is damaging the cause. But there are still "yellow vests" surround the country who feel that now is not the time to ease up the pressure. They feel that if Macron has given once he can give again.\nThe UN climate conference in Poland has been extended to allow negotiators more time to finalize a deal on cutting greenhouse gas emissions. The talks continued through the night on contentious issues, including how poor countries should be compensated for the damage caused by global warming.\nMahinda Rajapaksa has announced his resignation as Sri Lanka's prime minister. In a statement, he said he had no intention of continuing in the post without a general election being held. With the details here's Anbarasan Ethirajan. Mahinda Rajapaksa who strongly believes in astrology, signed his resignation letter in an auspicious time during a religious ceremony held at his home in Colombo. He was controversially appointed two months ago by President Maithripala Sirisena to replace Ranil Wickremesinghe, triggering a political crisis in Sri Lanka. But he failed to command a majority in Parliament and a court also restrained him from acting as Prime Minister. In a statement, Mr. Rajapaksa said his resignation would make way for the president to form a new government. There are suggestions that Mr. Rajapaksa's resignation could lead to Mr. Wickremasinghe returning to power on Sunday.\nThe Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison has said his country now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. But in a speech in Sydney, Mr. Morrison said the Australian embassy would not be relocated from Tel Aviv until the final status of Jerusalem was resolved. He said the decision took him to account the interests of both sides. Australia now recognizes West Jerusalem, being the seat of the Knesset and many of the institutions of government, is the capital of Israel. Furthermore, recognizing our commitment to a two-state solution, the Australian government is also resolved to acknowledge the aspirations of the Palestinian people for a future state with its capital in East Jerusalem. This is the latest world news from the BBC.\n![](images/west-jerusalem.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，我是约翰·席亚。法国各地部署了数万名警察，为近期的“黄马甲”抗议活动做准备。在过去的两周内，巴黎受到了数十年来最严重的骚乱活动。到目前为止，有迹象表明本周参加游行的人在减少，以下是休·斯科菲尔德的报道。总统马克龙周一提出将会打开国库，一些“黄马甲”活动人士承认这是重要一步，并且呼吁暂停游行活动。一些人担心最近两个周六的抗议活动是由年轻的机会主义者引起的，而不是真正的游行人员，这将会给游行活动带来不好的影响。但是现在仍有“黄马甲”人士在法国境内游行，他们称现在还不能松懈对政府的压力。他们认为马克龙能让步一次就能让步第二次。\n在波兰举行的联合国气候大会现已延期，目的是给与谈判者更多的时间达成关于削减温室气体排放的协议。会议连夜讨论了争议问题，包括欠发达国家如何弥补气候变暖造成的损失。\n马欣达·拉贾帕克萨宣布将辞去斯里兰卡总理职务。在一份声明中，他表示如果不进行大选，他将没有继续任职的意愿。以下是安巴拉森·安提拉的报道。马欣达·拉贾帕克萨本人深信占星术，他在家乡科伦坡的宗教活动期间选了一个黄道吉日签署了辞职信。两个月之前，他在争议之中被总统迈特里帕拉·西里塞纳任命为总理，代替了拉尼尔·拉贾帕克萨，这也引起了斯里兰卡的政治危机。但是他未能让该党在国会中占据多数席位，法庭同样也限制了他总理的实权。在声明中，拉贾帕克萨表示他的辞职将会给总统组建新的政府扫清道路。有迹象表明，拉贾帕克萨的辞职将会导致拉贾帕克萨在周六重新就职总理。\n澳大利亚总理斯科特·莫里森表示澳大利亚现在承认西耶路撒冷为以色列首都。但是在悉尼的讲话中，莫里森表示，在耶路撒冷首都身份被最终确认之前，澳大利亚大使馆将不会从特拉维夫迁出。他表示考虑了双方利益之后做了这个决定。澳大利亚现在承认西耶路撒冷为以色列首都，这里是国会以及许多政府机构所在地。另外，为了贯彻我们的两国方针，澳大利亚同样决定承认巴基斯坦人民对于东耶路撒冷作为其首都的渴望。以上为最新的BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>27</id>
        <date>December 19, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Pakistani has approved death sentences for fifteen terrorists</title>
        <description>
            The head of the Pakistani Army has approved death sentences for fifteen people convicted by military courts of involvement in Islamic attacks.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pakistani-terrorists.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181218_59273296tg.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News. I'm John Shea. Environmental groups and some countries have criticized Saturday's agreement at the UN climate conference in Poland as lacking in ambition. The deal sought to lay down the rules to implement the 2015 Paris accord. David Shookman has this assessment. Applause and relief in Katowice mask some difficult questions about this latest deal. Under the new rules, countries are expected to publish their plans for cutting their emissions of greenhouse gases. But the Paris Agreement is voluntary, so no government is under any obligation. And even if every country takes the steps that they've promised to, the world will still be on course for what scientists consider dangerous levels of warming. But critics point to the most recent assessment by the UN climate panel, which concluded that emissions must start falling in the next twelve years.\nSri Lanka's ousted Prime Minister Ranil Wickremasinghe has been sworn back into office nearly two months after he was sacked by President Maithripala Sirisena. The move plunged Sri Lanka into a political crisis which saw Mr. Wickremasinghe replaced by the former President Mahinda Rajapaksa, but he's faced political and legal setbacks as Charles Haviland reports. Mr. Wickremasinghe's return to office is likely to end seven weeks of constitutional chaos. In October, his uneasy political ally President Sirisena tried to boot him out and replace him with Mahinda Rajapaksa, the hard-line nationalist ex-president. Mr. Sirisena also tried to dissolve Parliament, but on Thursday the Supreme Court deemed that action illegal. The crisis has rocked a country still grappling with an ugly pattern of human rights abuses during its long ethnic war.\nThe head of the Pakistani Army has approved death sentences for fifteen people convicted by military courts of involvement in Islamic attacks. Twenty other militants were given prison sentences. This report from Charish Haney. The confirmation of the death sentences comes as Pakistan marks the fourth anniversary of an attack on an army-run school in Peshawar in which more than a hundred and fifty people were killed. The attack prompted Pakistan to lift a six-year moratorium on executions, and hundreds are reported to have been put to death since then. The fifteen who had their death sentences confirmed could appeal. Rights groups say military trials are unfair, but the authorities insist they have no choice in a country ravaged by militancy. BBC News.\n![](images/ranil-wickremasinghe.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，我是约翰·席亚。环境保护组织和一些国家批评了波兰联合国气候大会达成的协议，称其缺乏“雄心壮志”。该协议旨在制定规定来落实2015年的《巴黎协定》，以下是大卫·舒克曼的报道。在卡兹委托会议的掌声和欣慰的掩盖之下，这项最新的协议还有很多棘手的问题。在新的规定之下，各国应该公开削减温室气体排放的计划。但是《巴黎协定》是自愿性质的，所以谈不上义务。即使每个国家都按照承诺采取了措施，世界还是会继续升温到科学家所认为的危险水平。但批评人士指向了联合国气候小组近期的评估，该评估称碳排放必须在接下来的12年内开始下降。\n斯里兰卡被罢黜的总理拉尼尔·维克勒马辛哈重新宣誓就职，近两个月之前，他被总统迈特里帕拉·西里塞纳解雇。维克勒马辛哈被前总统拉贾帕克萨替代时，还引起了斯里兰卡的一次政治危机，但是后者遇到了政治和法律上挫折。以下是查尔斯·哈维兰的报道。维克勒马辛哈重新上任有可能会结束七周的宪法危机。然而在十月份，他的政治盟友，总统西里塞纳曾解雇他，并让强硬派民族主义者，前总统马欣达·拉贾帕克萨就职。西里塞纳同样想解散国会，但是周二最高法院认为此举不合法。该危机震动了斯里兰卡，然而这个国家还没有摆脱其漫长民族战争中丑陋的侵犯人权问题。\n巴基斯坦军领导人批准了15人死刑判决，军事法庭判处他们有罪，他们参与了伊斯兰袭击。另外20名武装分子被判服刑，以下是查理士·汉尼的报道。死刑判决确认的同时正值四周年纪念，白沙瓦一所军营学校四年前遭袭，当时有150多人被杀。该袭击促使巴基斯坦取消了6年死刑缓刑制度，据报道已有数百人被执行死刑。被确认死刑判决的这15人可以上诉。人权组织表示军事宣判是不公平的，但是政府表示在一个武装分子肆虐的国家这也是不得已的选择。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>28</id>
        <date>December 20, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch Bambi</title>
        <description>
            A judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch repeat screenings of the Walt Disney film Bambi as part of his sentence.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fawn-bambi.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1219_4329637Vdw.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News.\nFighting has erupted again around the Yemeni port of Hodeida after a United Nations-brokered ceasefire failed to take hold. Houthi rebels and the Saudi-backed government had agreed to halt the violence at talks in Sweden last week, but government officials accused the Iranian-backed Houthis of shelling government troops east of Hodeidah just minutes after the truce came into force.\nA court in El Salvador has freed a woman who spent a year and seven months in jail accused of trying to abort her baby. The 20-year-old woman Imelda Cortez said that she became pregnant by her stepfather who sexually abused her for many years. Leonardo Rocha has more details.\nImelda Cortez said that she began being sexually abused by her stepfather when she was 12 and in April last year she gave birth to a baby. She says the baby is from her stepfather who's now in his seventies. Doctors in El Salvador, they accuse her of trying to terminate the pregnancy, which in El Salvador amounts to a charge of attempted murder.\nThe family of a dying two-year-old boy in California say his Yemeni mother is being prevented from visiting him by the Trump administration's travel ban on visitors from seven mainly Muslim countries. Doctors say Abdullah Hassan is terminally ill with a brain disease. The boy's father, whose was born in California, brought him to the US. Saad Sweilem is from the Council on American-Islamic Relations.\nThey've been actually waiting for over a year to try to get her to be able to come here. Just a few months ago, they finally realized, you know we can't wait much longer. So the father went ahead and brought Abdullah here to the US in hopes that he'd get medical treatment and in the meantime, his wife would be able to get her visa situation ratified and become joined them. But instead it's taken a turn for the worst and now we find her son Abdullah here and his mother unable to come be by his side.\nA judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch repeat screenings of the Walt Disney film Bambi as part of his sentence. Generations of children and adults have been reduced to tears by the carton film of Bambi released in 1942 in which the young fawn's mother is killed by a hunter. Here's Anthony Zahra.\nA judge in Missouri has sentenced David Berry Jr. to watch the film once a month during a year-long jail sentence. Berry has been convicted of illegally killing hundreds of deer and taking their heads for trophies. Officials said it was one of their largest-ever poaching investigations.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/salvador.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n联合国斡旋下的停火协议未能实现，也门港口城市荷台达再起战火，上周瑞典会谈时，胡塞武装和沙特支持的政府军同意停止暴力，但是政府官员指责伊朗支持的胡塞叛军在荷台达东部向政府军开炮，而此时距离停火协议生效仅几分钟。\n萨尔瓦多的一家法庭释放了一名因意图堕胎而入狱一年零七个月的女性。这名20岁的女性名为伊美黛·科特兹，她表示自己被其继父性侵多年，最终导致怀孕。以下是莱昂纳多·罗查的详细报道。\n伊美黛·科特兹表示她从12岁开始被其继父性侵，并在去年4月生下一名婴儿。她表示孩子是她继父的，而他现已70多岁。萨尔瓦多医生指控她意图终止妊娠，而这在萨尔瓦多被认为是谋杀未遂。\n在美国加州，一名生命垂危的两岁男孩的家人称他在也门的妈妈因特朗普政府对7个主要穆斯林国家的旅行禁令而不能来到他的身边。医生表示阿卜杜拉·哈桑患脑疾且生命垂危。男孩的父亲出生在加州，他将男孩带到了美国。以下是美国伊斯兰关系理事会的萨德·斯韦勒姆的讲话。\n实际上他们已经等了一年多想让孩子的母亲来到美国。几个月之前，他们最终意识到已经不能再等了。于是父亲先带着阿卜杜拉来到了美国，希望他能得到治疗，同时也希望妻子的签证获批从而和他们团聚。但现在男孩的病情恶化，我们看到病床上的阿卜杜拉而他的母亲却无法来到他的身边。\n美国密苏里州的一名法官下令一名小鹿偷猎者反复观看迪士尼影片《小鹿斑比》，并将此作为他判刑的一部分。几代人，不论大人还是小孩都被这部1942年上映动画片《小鹿斑比》感动地流下了眼泪，影片中小鹿的妈妈被猎人猎杀。以下是安东尼·扎赫拉的报道。\n密苏里州的一名法官判处小大卫·贝里有期徒刑一年，并在此期间内每月观看这部影片一次。贝里因非法猎杀数百头鹿并取下鹿头作为战利品而被判刑。相关官员表示这是该州有史以来调查的最大偷猎案件之一。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>29</id>
        <date>December 21, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - New York's Attorney General closed the charity established in President Trump's name</title>
        <description>
            New York's Attorney General has held the closure of the charity established in President Trump's name as a victory for the rule of law.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-charity.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181220_0417129WMe.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm David Harper with the BBC News. New York's Attorney General has held the closure of the charity established in President Trump's name as a victory for the rule of law. Barbara Underwood, who is a Democrat, accused the Trump Foundation of engaging in a shocking pattern of illegality. Our north American editor Jon Sopel has more details on the charity. Far from this being a vehicle for giving and philanthropy, the New York Attorney General has described in the most scathing terms how the Trumps were using this for their own purposes. There was a shocking pattern of illegality, including unlawful coordination with the Trump presidential campaign. Repeated and willful self-dealing, this amounted to the Trump Foundation functioning as little more than a checkbook to serve Mr. Trump's business and political interests. Trump's attorneys said those accusations were inaccurate and politicized.\nA judge in the United States has delayed the sentencing of President Trump's former national security advisor Michael Flynn to give more time for him to cooperate with prosecutors. The judge was fiercely critical of Mr. Flynn, saying it could be argued that he sold out his country. Mr. Flynn pleaded guilty last year to lying to the FBI about his contacts with the Russian ambassador to the US. At a briefing, the White House spokesperson Sarah Sanders expressed the administration's support for Mr. Flynn. The delay is something between General Flynn and the courts, and that's something for them to determine what timeline looks like. In the meantime, we wish General Flynn well, and we'll continue to focus on doing what we do here every single day.\nThe Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has offered his resignation following the withdrawal earlier this month of one of the partners in his governing coalition. Kevin Connolly reports from Brussels. Charles Michel, a French-speaking liberal, has been in government with the conservative movement of Flemish-speaking nationalists, the NVA. When that coalition collapsed last week cause of NVA's rejections to Mr. Michel's decision to agree to the new UN declaration on migration, it left Mr. Michel out on a limb. His resignation is now held in suspension, leaving him as a kind of caretaker Prime Minister. Somehow, Mr. Michel now has to find a way to pass a federal budget. If he can't, the country will edge closer to political crisis. Kevin Connolly reporting from Brussels.\nHuman Rights Watch has called on the authorities in Mali to prosecute militia members and their leaders, saying attacks in the center of the country are spiraling out of control. Earlier this month, an ethnic Dogon militia killed 34 people from the Fulani ethnic group. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/belgian-prime-minister-charles-michel.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是的大卫·哈珀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。纽约总检察长宣布关闭特朗普名下的基金会，并将此视作法制的胜利。芭芭拉·安德伍德是一名民主党人士，她表示特朗普基金会的违法行为令人震惊。以下是本台北美编辑乔恩·苏博尔的详细报道。该基金会不仅不是一个捐赠和慈善的工具，相反纽约总检察长言辞尖刻地描述了特朗普家族是如何用它为自己谋利的。它的违法模式令人震惊，包括与特朗普总统竞选活动的非法合作。通过连续的蓄意自利交易，特朗普基金会只不过是特朗普商业和政治利益的支票簿。特朗普的律师称这些指控不正确，且是政治化的指控。\n美国一法官推迟了特朗普前国家安全顾问迈克尔·弗林的宣判日期，目的是给他更多的时间和检察官合作。这名法官严厉地批判了弗林，称其行为可以认作是卖国。弗林在去年认罪，承认他在与俄罗斯驻美国大使联系一事中向FBI说谎。白宫发言人萨拉·桑德斯在发布会中表达了政府对弗林的支持。宣判推迟是弗林将军与法庭的事，具体的宣判时间也会由他们决定。同时，我们希望弗林将军身体健康，我们也会在处理白宫日常事务的同时继续关注此事。\n比利时首相夏尔·米歇尔提出辞呈，原因是本月初有执政联盟合作伙伴退出，以下是凯文·康诺利在布鲁塞尔的报道。夏尔·米歇尔是一个说法语的自由党人，他与发动保守运动的民族主义人士，“新弗拉芒联盟党”组成了联合政府。执政联盟上周瓦解，因为“新弗拉芒联盟党”拒绝米歇尔签署联合国关于移民问题的新宣言，而这也让他处于一个孤立无援的境地。他的辞职被暂时搁置，这也让他成为了临时首相。米歇尔现在需要设法通过一项联邦预算，如果失败的话，国家将会进入政治危机的边缘。以上是凯文·康诺利的报道。\n人权观察组织呼吁马里政府起诉民兵组织成员及其领导人，称马里中部的袭击活动正失去控制。本月初，多贡族民兵组织杀害了34名富拉尼族平民。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>30</id>
        <date>December 22, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Japan has decided to withdraw from the IWC in order to resume whaling on a commercial basis</title>
        <description>
            In September, Japan launched a controversial bid to ease the moratorium on commercial whaling imposed by the IWC more than thirty years ago. But its argument that whale stocks has recovered sufficiently to justify the resumption of sustainable hunting was voted down. That seems to have paved the way for this decision. According to the Kyoto News Agency, Tokyo would only allow whaling in the seas around Japan and not stray into Antarctic waters.
        </description>
        <cover>images/japan-whaling.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1221_2206384pgR.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News. Hello, I'm Gareth Barlow.\nSenators in the United States, including high-profile Republicans, have condemned President Trump's announcement that he's withdrawing American forces from Syria. Six senators led by the Republican Lindsey Graham have written to Mr. Trump, accusing him of making a costly mistake that threatened US security.\nEarlier, the chair of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Bob Corker, said the move was completely unexpected. We've got allies around the world that have been with us all this time, have been fighting with us. There's probably fifty or sixty countries that have been involved in some form of fashion. To my knowledge, we didn't even communicate with them that this morning we were gonna make this announcement. It's caught everybody off guard. I know that, I doubt there's anybody in the Republican Caucus in the Senate that just isn't stunned.\nBritain, a major ally of the US has expressed concern and questioned Mr. Trump's assertion that Islamic State militants in Syria had been defeated. The British Defense Minister Tobias Ellwood said that on the contrary, the threat from IS was very much alive.\nJapanese government sources say the country has decided to withdraw from the International Whaling Commission in order to resume whaling on a commercial basis. The BBC's Cat Wiener has more details.\nIn September, Japan launched a controversial bid to ease the moratorium on commercial whaling imposed by the IWC more than thirty years ago. But its argument that whale stocks has recovered sufficiently to justify the resumption of sustainable hunting was voted down. That seems to have paved the way for this decision. According to the Kyoto News Agency, Tokyo would only allow whaling in the seas around Japan and not stray into Antarctic waters.\nMeanwhile, a court in Japan has rejected a request by prosecutors to extend the detention of Carlos Ghosn, the former chairman of Nissan who was sacked for alleged financial misconduct. The ruling means he could soon be released. With the details, Steve Jackson reports.\nCarlos Ghosn was first detained on the nineteenth of November when his private jet landed in Tokyo. The 64-year-old French-Brazilian was one of the world's most powerful auto industry executives, but has spent the past month in prison. During that time, he's been charged with lying about his pay for several years. He's accused of hiding eighty million dollars of income and of misusing company funds. He denies all the allegations. The timing of his release is unclear, but Japanese media say it could happen as soon as Friday. The court also rejected an extension to the detention of Greg Kelly, an aide to Mr. Ghosn.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/withdraw-forces-from-syria.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，大家好，我是加雷斯·巴罗。\n包括知名共和党人在内的美国议员对特朗普宣布从叙利亚撤军进行了谴责。以共和党人林赛·格雷厄姆为首的六名议员致信特朗普，指责他犯了一个代价高昂的错误，威胁到了美国的安全。\n早前，参议院外交关系委员会主席鲍勃·考克尔曾表示此举完全出人意料。一直以来，我们的盟友遍布世界各地。他们一直与我们并肩战斗。美国在全世界大约有50到60个这样的盟国。据我所知，我们甚至没有和他们沟通过，他们不知道今晨我们会做出这样的决定。这让每个人都措手不及，我知道，恐怕参议院共和党核心小组内没人不对此感到震惊。\n作为美国的一个重要盟友，英国也对此表示关切，并质疑了特朗普关于叙利亚境内伊斯兰国军事力量已被击败的声明。英国国防部长托比亚斯·埃尔伍德表示，与特朗普所言相反，伊斯兰国组织的威胁依旧很大。\n日本政府消息称日本已决定退出国际捕鲸协会，以恢复商业捕鲸业。以下是BBC记者卡特·温纳的详细报道。\n九月，日本发起了一项具有争议的恢复商业捕鲸提议，要求解除30多年前IWC强制实行的商业捕鲸禁令。日本辩称鲸鱼的数量现已充分恢复可以重新开始持续捕鲸，但遭到否决。这似乎给日本恢复捕鲸的决定铺平了道路。京都新闻社报道称，日本将只允许在日本周边海域捕鲸，并不进入大西洋海域。\n同时，日本一法庭拒绝了检方要求延长日产前董事长卡洛斯·戈恩羁押期的要求，不久前卡洛斯因所谓的财政不当行为遭解雇。法庭的裁定意味着他可能在不久之后会被释放。以下是史蒂夫·杰克森的详细报道。\n卡洛斯·戈恩首次在11月19日被拘押，当时他的私人飞机落地东京。这名64岁的法裔巴西人曾是世界上最强汽车企业高管之一，但是过去半个月却在狱中度过。在此期间，他被指控在多年的薪资问题上说谎。他被指控隐报了八千万美元的收入并挪用了公司的资金。他否认了所有指控。他的释放日期尚不清楚，但是日本媒体称最早周五就会被释放。该法庭也拒绝延长戈恩助手格蕾格·凯利的羁押期。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
</blogs>
