<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--以下特殊字符不可使用：-->
<!--&rsquo;全局替换为'-->
<!--<br/>换行符全局替换为\n-->
<blogs>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>1</id>
        <date>November 27, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Difficult Customer</title>
        <description>
            A: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I’ll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order? B: No, I’m still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What’s good here?
        </description>
        <cover>images/waitress.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0001pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Difficult Customer **\nA: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I'll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order?\nB: No, I'm still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What's good here?\nA: For you sir, I would recommend spaghetti and meatballs.\nB: Does it come with coke and fries?\nA: It comes with either soup or salad and a complimentary glass of wine, Sir.\nB: I'll go with the spaghetti and meatballs, salad and the wine.\nA: Excellent choice, your order will be ready soon.\nB: How soon is soon?\nA: Twenty minutes?\nB: You know what? I'll just go grab a burger across the street.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**still working on** : not yet completed, need more time\n**would recommend** : suggest\n**complimentary**: free\n**go with**: to choose, pick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>2</id>
        <date>November 28, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Calling In Sick</title>
        <description>
            A: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you? B: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.
        </description>
        <cover>images/calling.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0002pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Calling In Sick**\nA: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you?\nB: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.\nA: Hi, Julie, how are you?\nB: Actually, I'm feeling quite ill today.\nA: I'm sorry to hear that. What's wrong?\nB: I think I'm coming down with the flu. I have a headache, a sore throat a runny nose and I'm feeling slightly feverish.\nA: I see... so you're calling in sick?\nB: Yes, I was hoping to take the day off to recover.\nA: OK, then. Try and get some rest.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**was hoping** :to kindly expect\n**calling in sick**: report that you will not go to work because you are sick\n**coming down:**getting, acquiring\n**quite ill**: very sick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>3</id>
        <date>November 29, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Hotel Upgrade</title>
        <description>
            A: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?
        </description>
        <cover>images/hotel.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0003pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Hotel Upgrade **\nA: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?\nB: I'd like to check in please. I have a reservation under the name Anthony Roberts.\nA: All right R.O.B.E.R.T.S... Oh, Mr. Roberts we'vebeen expecting you&amp; and here is your keycard to the presidential suite.\nB: But there must be some mistake; my reservationwas for a standard room.\nA: Are you sure? Let me double check .\nB: Yeah&amp;Here, this is my confirmation number.\nA: You're right Mr. Roberts, there seems to be a mixup,unfortunately we're overbooked at the moment.\nB: So..\nA: Not to worry. We're pleased to offer you a complimentaryupgrade.\nB: Presidential suite baby!\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**check in** :register at a hotel or airport\n**under the name:** name used for the reservation</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>4</id>
        <date>November 30, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - I need an assistant</title>
        <description>
            A: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fist-bumps.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0004pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Office - I need an assistant!**\nA: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.\nB: I understand that, but the fact is we're understaffed.\nA: The timing is just not right. The economy is bad,and it's too risky to take on new staff.\nB: Yeah, I guess you're right.... here's an idea, what if we hire an intern? She would take some of the weight off my shoulders.\nA: She?\nB: Yeah, you know, a recent graduate. She could give me a hand with some of these projects and we could keep our costs down.\nA: That sounds reasonable... let me see what I can do.\nA: Tony, I'd like to introduce you to your new assistant.\nB: OK, great! Let's meet her!\nC: Hi, I'm Adam.\nB: Oh... hi... I'm Tony...\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**resources** : money\n**understaffed** : not enough people to do the job\n**the timing is just not right** : it is not a good time now\n**weight off my shoulders** : remove pressure or stress</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>5</id>
        <date>December 1, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Cut In Line</title>
        <description>
            A: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.
        </description>
        <cover>images/queue.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0005pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Cut In Line**\nA: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.\nB: Yeah, but just relax honey, we're here and we're going on vacation. In a few hours we'll be in Hawaii, and you'll be on the golf course.\nA: Oh no! Look at that line! It must be a mile long!There's no way I'm waiting for another two hours.\nB: Honey... don't...\nC: Hey man, the end of the line is over there.\nA: Yeah...\nC: No seriously, I was here first, and you can't cut in line like this.\nA: Says who?\nC: I do!\nA: So sue me!\nC: Alright...that's it....\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**There's no way** : impossible\n**cut in line** : jump the queue (in British English)</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>6</id>
        <date>December 2, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Road Trip</title>
        <description>
            A: So, are we all ready to go? B: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.
        </description>
        <cover>images/roadtrip.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0006pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Weekend - Road Trip**\nA: So, are we all ready to go?\nB: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.\nA: Did you get the camera?\nB: Got it! Did you fill up the tank?\nA: Yup, it's all set.\nB: You're sure we're not forgetting anything?\nA: I'm sure... we've got all our bases covered.\nB: Well&amp; let's get going then! I love road trips!\nB: Um... do you think we can make a pit stop?\nA: But we've only been on the road for ten minutes.\nB: I know, but I forgot to go to the bathroom before we left.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**all ready to go**:prepared, ready to leave\n**packed**:full, everything is inside\n**fill up the tank**:put gas in the car\n**all set**:ready</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>7</id>
        <date>December 3, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Computer Virus</title>
        <description>
            A: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.
        </description>
        <cover>images/computer-stethoscope.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0007pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>"**The Office - Computer Virus! **\nA: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.\nB: Just give me a second; I'll be right up.\nB: I ran a virus scan on your computer, and it turns out that you have a lot of infected files!\nA: But I'm quite careful when I'm browsing the internet, I have no idea how I could have picked up a virus.\nB: Well, you have to make sure that your anti-virus software is updated regularly; yours wasn't up to date, that's probably what was causing your problems.\nA: Ok. Anything else?\nB: Yeah, try not to kick or hit the computer!\nA: Um yeah; Sorry about that."</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>8</id>
        <date>December 4, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - G20 Summit is Holding in Buenos Aires</title>
        <description>
            World leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine.
        </description>
        <cover>images/G20.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181203_0014852xLB.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nWorld leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine. James Landale is at the summit. President Putin is likely to face tough questions over Russia seizure of Ukrainian vessels. President Trump said he wouldn't meet the Russian leader until the confrontation was resolved. And Mohammad bin Salman the Saudi Crown Prince is also in town looking to repair his reputation after the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi. But for all these tensions, European leaders said it was important for the G20 to come together to tackle the world's problems.\nBefore the summit formally got underway, the United States, Canada and Mexico signed a new trade deal. This is seen as a victory for Mr. Trump who opposed the previous agreement. Andrew Walker reports. Many barriers to commerce between the US, Canada and Mexico were removed or reduced by the North American Free Trade Agreement, which came into force a quarter of a century ago. But President Trump called it the worst trade deal ever. Now, the three leaders have signed a replacement which keeps much of the original agreement. But it includes additional provisions that will, for example, make it more expensive for car makers to use parts from outside the region and will mean more opportunities for US dairy farmers to sell their milk products in Canada. It has been a contentious negotiation and there were reports that late disputes about the dairy issue might have held up the signing ceremony.\nInternational Olympic Committee says it's freezing all planning for the boxing tournament at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics because of concerns about the sport's governing body. It's launching an inquiry into the International Boxing Association AIBA over its governance, ethics and financial management. Our sports correspondent Alex Capstick reports. The IOC halted preparations for the Olympic boxing tournament in Tokyo, including the qualifying process following talks among the organization's leading officials in the Japanese capital. For several months, serious concerns have been expressed over the way the sport's governing body has been run. It came to a head earlier this month when Gafur Rahimov was elected as president of AIBA, despite allegations that he's part of an international criminal network, something he's always denied. But whatever is ultimately decided regarding the future of AIBA, the IOC still wants boxing to be part of the Tokyo Games.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181204.jpg](images/bbc-20181204.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n世界各国领导人现正在布宜诺斯艾利斯参加G20峰会，峰会已表现出了紧张和分歧，许多是因为特朗普总统在贸易和气候变化上的好斗态度引发。俄罗斯对乌克兰采取的军事行动又进一步加重了大会的紧张氛围。以下是詹姆斯·兰德尔的报道。普京很有可能会因俄罗斯扣押乌克兰船只而面临尖锐的提问。特朗普表示在对峙解决之前他不会与普京见面。沙特王储穆罕默德·本·萨尔曼也来到了这里，试图挽回一下因沙特记者贾马尔·哈苏及被杀事件而受损的名声。虽然本次大会充满了紧张气氛，欧洲领导人表示最重要的是各国能聚在一起解决世界问题。\n在峰会正式开始之前，美国、加拿大和墨西哥签署了一份新的贸易协议。这被认为是特朗普的胜利，因为他反对之前的协议。以下是安德鲁·沃克的报道。北美自由贸易协定消除或降低了很多美国、加拿大和墨西哥之间的贸易壁垒，该协议在25年之前正式生效，但是特朗普称这是有史以来最差的贸易协议。现在这三名领导人已经签署了一个替代协议，保留了很多之前的协议内容。但是也新增了一些附加条款，比如汽车生产商使用该区域之外零件将会更加昂贵，另外也会更有利于美国奶农向加拿大销售奶制品。协商的过程很激烈，有报道称近期的乳制品问题争端或延长签字仪式。\n国际奥组委称正在冻结2020年东京奥运会的拳击比赛筹备工作，原因其管理机构存在问题。它正在对国际拳击联盟AIBA的管理情况、道德和金融状况进行调查。以下是本台体育通讯员亚历克斯·卡普斯蒂克的报道。国际奥组委停止了东京奥运会拳击比赛的筹备工作，包括资格赛，此前奥组委主要官员在日本首都举行了会谈。几个月以来，国际奥组委一直都在担心该体育机构的运作方式。本月初，加弗尔·拉西莫夫成功当选 AIBA主席，事情也达到了非做不可的地步，拉西莫夫被指是国际犯罪网络成员，但他本人否认。无论AIBA的前景如何，国际奥组委仍然希望拳击项目出现在东京奥运会上。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>9</id>
        <date>December 5, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Yellow Vest Movement in Paris</title>
        <description>
            The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances.
        </description>
        <cover>images/yellow-vest-movement.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181204_3542471yYn.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello. The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances. He was speaking after the latest protest saw the demonstrators attack police and spray graffiti on the Arch of Triumph. This report from Hugh Schofield. Demonstrators, some of them clearly agitators rather than bona fide yellow vests have fought running battles with police. They have torn up cobblestones to serve as projectiles and set fire to cars and even buildings. Police responded with tear gas and anti-riot grenades. What's been happening today takes the "yellow vest" movement to a new level. The scenes unforgettably vivid are of destruction. President Macron who's in Argentina at the G20 needs urgently to find a way out of this confrontation.\nMexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has promised to scrap the neoliberal economic policies of the past twenty five years. Speaking at his inauguration ceremony and Congress, Mr. Lopez Obrador said neoliberalism had led to poverty, crime and mass migration in Mexico and promised a new start. Starting from now, a peaceful and orderly transformation has begun that at the same time will be profound and radical, because we will end the corruption and impunity that impede Mexico's rebirth. The left-wing leader also announced the creation of a free trade zone in a vast area next to the border with the United States, where taxes will be lower and the minimum wage higher.\nThe African Union says it's worried about the lack of progress of peace talks for Burundi and has urged all sides to refrain from taking any judicial action that could cause further rifts. The warning comes a day after the Burundian government issued an international arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya and sixteen high ranking officials. Will Ross reports. The warning from the African Union appears to be aimed at the government of Burundi. Peace talks with the opposition have stalled and some feared the government has risked opening old ethnic wounds by issuing the arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya. The move is an awkward one for the African Union because Mr. Buyoya is now working for the AU as its special representative in Mali. The 1993 assassination of President Melchior Ndadaye, the country's first Hutu leader triggered the civil war in which three hundred thousand people were killed. That was Will Ross. This is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181205.jpg](images/bbc-20181205.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。法国总统马克龙谴责了巴黎反政府游行暴力事件，称这根本不是表达不满的合法方式。在最近的示威活动中，游行人群袭击了警察，还在凯旋门上涂鸦，之后法国总统做了这番讲话。以下是休·斯科菲尔德的报道。许多游行者很明显是鼓动者而不是真正的“黄马甲”抗议人士，他们与警察打起了游击战。他们将鹅卵石当作投掷物，点燃汽车甚至是建筑物。警察用催泪弹和防爆手雷进行了反击。今天发生的事情让“黄马甲”运动再次升级。这里到处都是毁灭的景象，让人历历在目。总统马克龙正在阿根廷参加G20峰会，他正迫切地想解决冲突的方法。\n墨西哥新总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔承诺将会取消施行25年的新自由经济政策。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔在就职仪式和国会上表示新自由经济政策导致了贫穷、犯罪和大规模移民，他承诺墨西哥将会有一个新的开始。现在，一个和平有序的变革已经开始，同时它也是深刻彻底的，因为我们会根除阻碍墨西哥重生的贪污和法外逃脱。这名左翼领导人还宣布将会在与美国接壤的广阔区域开创一个自由贸易区，这里的税率将会更低，最低工资也会更高。\n非洲联盟称他们对布隆迪和平谈判没有进展感到担心，并且敦促各方避免采取可能导致分歧加深的任何司法行动。在非盟发出警告的前一天，布隆迪政府发布了对前总统皮埃尔·布约亚和16名高级官员的国际逮捕令。以下是威尔·罗斯的报道。非盟的警告很明显是针对布隆迪政府的。布隆迪政府与反对党的和平谈判已经陷于僵局，一些人担心政府将会通过发布前总统皮埃尔·布约亚的逮捕令重新揭开之前的民族伤疤。此举让非盟处于一个尴尬的境地，因为布约亚现正为非盟工作，在马里任特派代表。1993年，该国首个胡图族领袖，总统梅尔基奥尔·恩达达耶被刺杀，这引发了国内战争，导致30万人被杀。以上是威尔·罗斯的报道。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>10</id>
        <date>December 6, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Mexico's new President start investigating the disappearance of 43 students</title>
        <description>
            On his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago.
        </description>
        <cover>images/安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1205_2603183KA2.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nOn his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago. The incident sparked weeks of protests. Will Grant reports.\nThe whole government is going to help with this plan. President Lopez Obrador told the victims' families who had gathered for the event, "and I can assure you that there will be no impunity either in this sad and painful case or in any other." It has been more than four years since the group of 43 young men and women were disappeared allegedly by State Security Forces. The lack of meaningful action or any prosecution of those involved was a stain on the previous administration, and human rights groups have long called for a new investigation.\nOne of Afghanistan's top sports officials has admitted for the first time that players in the women's national football squad and in other sports have been sexually abused and the problem must be addressed. The allegations of years of rape, sexual harassment and sexual coercion have been voiced publicly by a former captain of the women's football team. Jill McGivering reports.\nThe comments by Hafizullah Rahimithe, the head of Afghanistan's National Olympic Committee are the first official acknowledgment that the allegations of abuse made by some Afghan women footballers may be credible. Khalida Popal, a former team captain has been trying for years to highlight sexual assault, harassment and bullying by coaches and officials, which she claims to have witnessed and had reported to her. Officials in the Afghanistan Football Federation say the claims are untrue. Women involved in other sports have also spoken to the BBC,but are frightened of being identified.\nAn eighty-year-old woman has become the latest casualty of anti-government protests in France. She died in hospital in the southern city of Marseille after being hit in the face by a tear gas canister as she drew the shutters of her fourth floor apartment during rioting on Saturday. Three other deaths have been blamed on the protests.\nTwo jailed Catalan separatist leaders have announced that they're going on hunger strike from Tuesday, joining two colleagues who stopped eating at the weekend. Joaquim Forn and Josep Rull, said they were protesting against the Constitutional Court's refusal to let them appeal to European Courts against pretrial detention. The trials of nine Catalan separatists who have been held in jail for up to fourteen months are due to begin in January. Uruguay has rejected an asylum request by the former President of Peru Alan Garcia, who's under investigation for corruption. He entered Uruguay's embassy in Lima two weeks ago after a court banned him from leaving the country for the next eighteen months. Mr. Garcia says the allegations are politically motivated. The Uruguayan government praised Peru's legal system.\nThis is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181206.jpg](images/bbc-20181206.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n在墨西哥新任总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔就职的第一天，他签署了一项法令启动一个真相调查委员会，调查4年前43名学生失踪一案。该事件也引发了数周的抗议活动。以下是威尔·格兰特的报道。\n政府将全力协助实施该计划。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔总统对集结的受害者家属表示，“我能向你们保证，在该起沉重悲痛的案中或是在任何其他的案件中，凶手都逃脱不了惩罚。”当时据国家安全部队称有43名年轻男女失踪，此时距此已过去四年多的时间了。上一届政府没有实质性作为，也没有对涉案人员提起诉讼，这已经成为他们的一个污点，另外，人权组织在很久之前就要求对此展开新的调查。\n一名阿富汗体育部门高官首次承认国家女子足球队以及其他体育队的运动员受到性侵害，并称该问题必须要得到解决。女子足球队的前队长公开发声，称她们受到多年的强奸、性骚扰和性胁迫。以下是吉尔·麦吉弗林的报道。\n阿富汗国家奥委会主席哈飞祖拉·拉西梅斯所做出的评论是官方首次承认，阿富汗女足队员提出的性侵指控或许是可信的。哈莉达·博帕尔是一名前队长，多年来她一直试图曝光球队教练和官员的性侵、性骚扰和霸凌行为，她声称曾亲眼目睹也向主席报告过这些行为。阿富汗足协官员表示这些指控并非事实。其他项目的女队员也向BBC说了这件事，但她们害怕被认出来。\n一名80岁的女性成为法国反政府游行活动的又一位遇难者。她在法国南部城市马赛市的医院中去世，死因是在周六暴乱中，她在四楼房间里拉百叶窗时被一枚催泪弹击中面部。还有其他三名遇难者死于抗议活动中。\n两名被监禁的加泰罗尼亚分裂主义领导人宣布他们将从周二开始绝食抗议，他们的两名同事早在上周就开始了绝食。乔吉姆·弗恩和约瑟夫·罗尔表示，他们是在抗议宪法法庭拒绝让他们就审前羁押向欧洲法庭提起上诉，狱中的九名加泰罗尼亚分裂主义分子被判监禁14个月之久，并将从一月份开始服刑。乌拉圭拒绝了秘鲁前总统阿兰·加西亚的庇护请求，现在他正在接受腐败调查。两周之前，法院判定他在未来18个月内不得出国，之后他来到乌拉圭驻利马大使馆。加西亚表示这些指控都带有政治动机的，而乌拉圭则称赞了秘鲁的法律体系。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>11</id>
        <date>December 7, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit</title>
        <description>
            The British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit by warning Parliament that the choice is between her deal, no deal and no Brexit.
        </description>
        <cover>images/brexit.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181206_2216387HVk.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello.\nThe British Prime Minister Theresa May has opened a crucial five-day debate on Brexit by warning Parliament that the choice is between her deal, no deal and no Brexit.\nDon't let anyone here think that there's a better deal to be won by shouting louder. Don't imagine that if we vote this down, a different deal is going to miraculously appear. The alternative is uncertainty and risk. So I promise you today, this is the very best deal for the British people. I ask you to back it in the best interests of our constituents and our country.\nDuring the debate, Mrs. May said the EU had neither the time nor the inclination to reopen negotiations before Britain leaves next March.\nThe US Special Counsel Robert Mueller says Donald Trump's former National Security Advisor Michael Flynn should face little or no prison time for giving what he called substantial assistance to the Russian election meddling probe. Mr. Mueller is leading an investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 US presidential election. In court documents filed on Tuesday, Robert Mueller said Mr. Flynn has given first-hand details of contacts between Mr. Trump's transition team and Russian government officials.\nUS stocks have fallen sharply on fears of an economic slowdown. The Dow Jones Industrial Average had its worst day in nearly three months. All of the major US indexes ended the trading day down by more than three percent.\nWe've seen all of the major indexes down more than three percent. You've got bank stocks leading the way, but it wasn't just bank stocks, it was transportation stocks, industrial stocks, Caterpillar, General Electric. A lot of this has to do with concerns or warning signals flashing from the bond market, suggesting that there's perhaps worries about economic growth lying in the future. The likelihood of a recession is much higher and that's why market watchers are paying so much attention to this and getting spooked today.\nThat was Michelle Fleury and markets in Asia also opened sharply lower.\nA group of US Congress members have called on the Rwandan government to drop charges against Diane Rwigara, a government critic who's facing up to 22 years in prison on charges of incitement and fraud. She's due to be sentenced in Rwanda later today. Supporters say the charges are politically motivated and arose from Ms Rwigara's bid to run against President Paul Kagame in last year's elections.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/TheresaMay.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻，大家好。\n英国首相特蕾莎·梅开启了一场为期五天的重要脱欧辩论，以此警告议会要么接受她的协议，要么无协议脱欧，要么不脱欧。\n不要让在座的人认为通过大喊大叫就能赢得一项更好的协议。不要幻想着否决了这份协议，就会有一份不同的协议奇迹般地出现。替代方案充满了不确定性和风险。所以今天我向你们保证，这是一份对英国民众来说最好的协议。 为了我们的人民和国家的最大利益，我请求你们支持这份协议。\n在辩论中，特蕾莎·梅表示欧盟没有时间也没有意愿在英国明年三月脱欧之前再次开启协商。\n美国特别顾问罗伯特·米勒表示特朗普的前国家安全顾问迈克尔·弗林为俄罗斯干预美国大选的调查提供了实质性的帮助，因此他将面临短期刑期或零刑期。米勒正在带头调查俄罗斯干涉美国2016年总统大选一案。在周六的一份法庭文件中，罗伯特·米勒表示弗林提供了关于特朗普过渡团队和俄罗斯政府官员联系的一手资料。\n出于对经济衰退的担忧，美国股市暴跌。道琼斯工业平均指数达到了近三个月以来的最低点。所有的主要美国指数在交易日结束时都下降了3个百分点以上。\n我们看到所有的主要工业指数都下降了超过3个百分点。银行股票首当其冲，但是不仅仅是银行股票，运输业股票、工业股票、卡特彼勒和通用电气的股票都受到了影响。很多都和债券市场传递出的担忧和警告信号有关，这也暗示了人们对于未来经济增长的担忧。出现经济衰退的可能性变得更高，这也是为什么市场观察者今天如此关注该事件并感到惊慌的原因。\n以上是马歇尔·弗勒里的报道。亚洲市场开盘同样大幅下跌。\n美国国会议员呼吁卢旺达政府撤销对政府批判人士黛安·瑞嘉的指控，因煽动和诈骗指控，她将面临22年之久的刑期。今天晚些时候将在卢旺达进行宣判。支持者表示这些指控带有政治动机，且是由于瑞嘉去年与保罗·卡加梅竞选总统引起的。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>12</id>
        <date>December 8, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in Washington</title>
        <description>
            There have been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the National Cathedral in Washington.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fly-a-flag-at-half-mast.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181207_3945526LE6.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News. The French government is abandoning plans to increase fuel taxes that prompted weeks of sometimes violent demonstrations. Four people died and hundreds were injured. After suspending the measure temporarily earlier this week, the Prime Minister Edouard Philippe has announced that it'll be dropped altogether from legislation on next year's budget. He said the government had to maintain peace. If the state is to remain strong and firm, it is first of all, the guarantor of public peace. To set the course and hold it is necessary in order to govern France. And as I said yesterday, no tax is worth putting the unity of the nation in danger.\nSerbia says it's considering military intervention as a possible response if its former province of Kosovo goes ahead with a plan to create its own army. President Aleksandar Vucic said the proposal was aimed at driving out Serbs still living in Kosovo.\nThe Liberian state energy company says about sixty percent of all electricity generated in the country is stolen. The theft is causing estimated losses of about thirty five million dollars a year as Warren Bull now reports. The Liberia energy corporation says large numbers of people are making illegal connections to their homes and businesses. Speaking to state radio, a spokesman said the theft was diverting cash that would have been used to improve power supplies to the west African country. Liberia is trying to rebuild an energy sector destroyed during a civil war which lasted from 1989 to 2003. The United States is giving financial and technical aid to increase connectivity as part of the Power Africa Initiative launched by the former US President Barrack Obama.\nBut the country still has one of the lowest access rates to energy in the world, only one in eight Liberians have electricity. There have been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the National Cathedral in Washington. Gary O'Donoghue was following the ceremony. With full pomp and ceremony, America paid tribute to its 41st President, a man who spent a lifetime in public service. George W. Bush, eldest son and 43rd President delivered the warmest of eulogies. But in America he leaves behind a country much changed since he controlled the levers of power, a country divided in ways that would have been anathema to his brand of politics. This is the latest world news from the BBC.\n![](images/bush-funeral.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。法国政府将放弃上涨燃油税的计划，该计划也激起了数周暴力时发的游行活动。已有四人死亡，数百人受伤。本周初该计划暂时中止之后，总理爱德华·菲利浦宣布上涨燃油税将从明年的预算法案中移除。他表示政府需要保持和平状态。如果法国要保持强大和稳固的话，首先它要保证治安。在治理法国方面，制定方向和稳固这一方向是必要的。正如我昨天所说的，没有一项税法可以不顾国家的统一。\n塞尔维亚称或考虑武力介入，如果原省份科索沃实施创建军队的计划。总统亚历山大·武契奇表示他们的计划是驱逐仍生活在科索沃的塞尔维亚人。\n利比里亚国家能源公司表示大约60%的国家电力被盗。偷电行为造成了大约每年3500万美元的损失，以下是沃伦·布尔的报道。利比里亚能源公司表示大量民众正在为其家庭和企业非法连接电网。一名发言人对国家广播说，偷电行为所转化的钱本应该用于为这个西非国家改善电力供应。利比里亚正在重建毁于1989年到2003年内战期间的电力部门。美国正在为利比里亚提升电网连接提供财力和技术支持，这也是由美国前总统巴拉克·奥巴马发起的非洲电力计划的一部分。\n但是该国仍然是世界上电网连通率最低的国家之一，只有八分之一的利比里亚人通上了电。美国前总统老布什的国葬在华盛顿的国家大教堂举行，人们向他表达了真挚的悼念。盖里·奥德诺霍正在对葬礼进行报道。在隆重的葬礼上，美国民众向第41任总统致以敬意，他将一生的时间都用在了公共事业上。他的大儿子，美国第43任总统小布什发表了最温暖的悼词。自从他掌控权利杠杆以来，他离开后的美国发生了很大变化，国家的分裂现状也正是他的执政理念所深恶痛绝的。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>13</id>
        <date>December 9, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Russia will respond in kind if US pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles</title>
        <description>
            President Putin of Russia says his country will respond in kind if the United States pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles.
        </description>
        <cover>images/nuclear-missile.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1209_3508560Wg5.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Neil Nunes.\nA new global climate study says carbon dioxide emissions will reach a record high this year, much of it caused by the burning of coal in China and the increasing use of cars. The research says worldwide CO2 output is projected to rise by 2.7% this year, compared to 2017.\nA series of confidential emails between senior figures at Facebook reveal the social media giant gives some companies preferential access to users’ data. That meant the firms could see information about users’ friends. Netflix and Airbnb were among the firms given privileged access.\nThe Liberian state energy company says about 60% of all electricity generated in the country is stolen. Officials from the Liberian electricity corporation told state radio that large numbers of people are making illegal connections to their homes and businesses. They said the theft caused annual loss of $35 million.\nPresident Putin of Russia says his country will respond in kind if the United States pulls out of a cold war nuclear arms control treaty and develops new missiles. It follows a 60-day ultimatum to Moscow to comply with the treaty.\nScientists in Britain have completed the world’s largest gene sequencing project in health care, which is hoped will revolutionize medical treatment for people with cancer and rare diseases. The researchers have mapped 100,000 human genomes. Each one contains a person’s DNA and errors that then can trigger a vast range of disorders.\nThere’ve been warm tributes to the former US President George H. W. Bush at his state funeral in the national Cathedral in Washington. Mr. Bush’s biographer Jon Meacham called George H. W. Bush the last great soldier-statesmen.\nBBC news.\n![](images/Putin.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n尼尔·努内斯为您播报BBC新闻。\n一项最新的全球气候研究指出，二氧化碳排放量今年将达到历史新高。其中很大一部分是由全球汽车使用量升高以及中国的燃煤造成的。该研究指出，全球二氧化碳的排放量今年或同比上升2.7%。\n脸书上两位高层人士的机密一系列机密邮件表明，脸书这家社交媒体授予一些公司特权，让它们可以获取用户数据。也就是说，这些公司可以看到用户朋友是谁等信息。包括网飞公司和爱彼迎在内的一些公司都获得了这样的特权\n利比里亚国家能源公司称，该国近60%的发电量都被窃取了。该公司工作人员在接受国家电台采访时表示，很多人都会非法连接家和企业的电网。他们称，这种窃取行为导致3500万美元的年损失额。\n俄罗斯总统普京表示，如果美国退出冷战时期的核武器控制协议，那么俄罗斯会以牙还牙，并会研制新型导弹。俄罗斯此举是在美国给其下了60天合规的最后通牒后做出的。\n英国科学家完成了世界上最大的卫生保健领域的基因序列测定项目。有人希望这个项目能为癌症和稀有疾病患者带来变革性的医学治疗。研究人员绘制了10万个人类基因组。每个都包含一个人的DNA以及会导致大量失调的误差。\n人们在华盛顿国家大教堂为美国前总统乔治·布什举行了国葬，热切缅怀这位领袖。布什传纪作者乔恩·米彻姆称布什是最后一位伟大的战士及政治家。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>14</id>
        <date>December 10, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines</title>
        <description>
            North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines and improvised explosives after almost a decade of conflict in the region.
        </description>
        <cover>images/mines.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc181209_5909215h4F.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>North-eastern Nigeria is littered with thousands of landmines and improvised explosives after almost a decade of conflict in the region. The Islamist group Boko Haram continues to attack towns and villages and to kidnap hundreds of school girls, most notoriously from the town of Chibok in 2014. The number of people being killed and injured by mines and explosives in Nigeria has greatly increased according to research by the Mines Advisory Group (MAG). Over 160 killed in the past two years, with hundreds more injured. It's had a devastating impact on the region and prevents large areas of land from being farmed, and it's a familiar pattern across the globe.\nSo how many landmines are there around the world? Minefields are often the deadly remnants of war left behind long after the combatants have gone. Under international law when mines are laid they must be mapped so they can be removed safely at a later date. All too often they're not mapped or maps are lost and process of de-mining can be a slow and dangerous one. In 2016, post-conflict clearance operations undertaken by charities such as the Halo Trust destroyed over 200,000 anti-personnel and 20,000 anti-vehicle mines around the world. But this hardly scratches the surface of the problem. There are still an estimated 110 million anti-personnel mines still in the ground with more being laid every year in active conflict areas. In a single year as many as 8,000 people are killed or seriously injured many of them children. That's almost one person killed or injured every hour of every day. That figure has risen as a result of the widespread use of improvised explosive devices by non-government forces.\nBBC news.\n![](images/landmines.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n在尼日利亚东北部地区冲突停止几乎10年后，其地下仍然埋着上千的地雷和简易爆炸装置。而布下这些地雷和爆炸装置的伊斯兰组织“博科圣地”现在仍然在袭击城镇和乡村，并且因在2014年绑架了奇博克上百名学校女生而臭名远扬。根据地雷顾问团的调查，在尼日利亚，因为地雷和爆炸丧命和受伤的人数有了大幅的增长。在过去两年，尼日利亚超过160人因为地雷丧命，还有上百人因此受伤。地雷给尼日利亚东北部地区带来了灾难性的冲击，大面积地区受此影响不能耕种，全世界其他地区也都是类似的模式。\n那么在全世界地下埋着多少地雷？布雷区在参战方离开很久后，经常还是致命的战争遗留物。根据国际法，地雷在被布下后，必须在地图上标注，这样它们过后可以被安全移除。但是经常是，它们没有被标注或者地图遗失了，因此排雷的过程变得非常缓慢和危险。在2016年，像哈洛信托这样的慈善组织在后冲突地区进行了排雷行动，共摧毁全世界范围内的超过20万杀伤人员地雷和2万反载具地雷。但是这几乎没有解决问题。据估计，全世界的地下仍然埋着1.1亿杀伤人员地雷，并且在活跃的冲突地区每年还会布放新的地雷。单单一年，就有8000人因为地雷丧命或严重受伤，很多是儿童。这几乎相当于每天每小时就有一人因为地雷丧命或者受伤。这个数字还在增长，因为非政府武装力量现在广泛使用简易爆炸装置。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>15</id>
        <date>December 10, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei</title>
        <description>
            There's been a renewed selloff on Wall Street with traders alarmed about the arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei.
        </description>
        <cover>images/court-sketch.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1209_0119272DVx.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Jonathan Izard.\nThere's been a renewed selloff on Wall Street with traders alarmed about the arrest in Canada of a senior executive from the Chinese technology firm Huawei. The US national security adviser John Bolton admitted that he had known the arrest in advance. He said Huawei was one company Washington suspected was being used as an arm of the Chinese government.\nRwanda's high court has acquitted the political activist Diane Rwigara and her mother of charges of forgery and inciting insurrection. Miss Rwigara served more than a year in prison after being disqualified from running in presidential elections. She said the charges were politically motivated.\nThe Hungarian National Association of Journalists says it will challenge the government in the constitutional court for establishing a pro-government media conglomerate, and for exempting it from scrutiny. The Central European Press and Media Foundation was established last month by the authorities who said it was in the national interest.\nThe Eiffel Tower and a number of Paris museums and markets will be shut on Saturday amid fears of further street violence involving the “yellow vest” protest movement. The demonstrations began in protest of fueled tax rises, but have broadened amid anger about rising living costs.\nThe Netherlands has ordered an investigation into illegal adoptions by Dutch couples of foreign children. It will focus first on the adoption of children from Brazil, but will also of the cases from Columbia, Indonesia, Sri Lanka and Bangladesh over the 3 decades of the late 1990s.\nA leading human rights group says it has received credible reports that a 4th Saudi women’s rights activist has been tortured while in detention. Saudi Arabia denied earlier reports that 3 leading women activists detained this year have been assaulted and sexually harassed.\nProtests have been taken place in Bolivia in 8 of the country's 9 regional departmental capitals after the court ruled both the President Evo Morales and vice president would be allowed stand for office in primaries in January.\n![](images/MS_Meng.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n乔纳森·伊泽德为您播报BBC新闻。\n华尔街再次出现抛空现象，因为投资者受到警示——中国科技公司华为某高管在加拿大被捕会对股市造成影响。美国国家安全顾问约翰·博尔顿承认在逮捕之前，他已得知此事。他表示，美国政府怀疑华为是中国政府的左膀右臂。\n卢旺达高等法院无罪释放了政治活动家戴安娜及其母亲，赦免了她们的伪造罪和煽动暴动罪。戴安娜曾服刑1年多，此前她欲参加总统竞选但却被认定不符合资格。她表示，这些罪名都是有政治意图的。\n匈牙利全国新闻工作者协会称其会在宪法法院与政府对簿公堂，内容有关政府成立了一个支持政府的传媒集团，并免除该集团审查的事宜。中欧新闻和媒体基金会于上个月由当局成立，当局说这是符合国家利益的。\n埃菲尔铁塔和一些巴黎博物馆和市场将于周六关闭，因为有人担心与黄背心运动有关的街头暴力会愈演愈烈。抗议示威起于赋税的上涨，因民众对生活成本升高恼火而加剧。\n荷兰要求调查本国夫妇非法收养外国儿童。调查将首先关注巴西儿童的收养，但也会考虑哥伦比亚、印尼、斯里兰卡、孟加拉国等国在上世纪90年代末期至今30年间的收养案例。\n某知名人权组织称自己收到了可信报告，报告指出第4位沙特女权活动家在拘留期间受到虐待。沙特否认了此前的报告，而此前报告指出，今年已经有3位知名女性活动家在拘留期间遭到强暴和性骚扰。\n玻利维亚已发生多次抗议事件。全国的9个大城市里有8个发生了抗议事件。原因是法院判决总统埃沃·莫拉莱斯和副总统都可以参加1月的初选。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>16</id>
        <date>December 11, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A pivotal moment in Donald Trump's presidency</title>
        <description>
            Court documents filed ahead of the sentencing of President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen have revealed new details about his contacts with Russia before the 2016 election.
        </description>
        <cover>images/Donald-Trump.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181210_5936360QGP.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is the BBC News with Fiona Macdonald. Court documents filed ahead of the sentencing of President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen have revealed new details about his contacts with Russia before the 2016 election. The memo from the Special Counsel Robert Mueller says Mr. Cohen met a trusted person in the Russian Federation. A separate document filed by federal prosecutors directly implicate President Trump in Michael Cohen's illegal payments to two women. Jon Sopel reports. These two filings could turn out to be a pivotal moment in Donald Trump's presidency. For the first time in a document from federal prosecutors, there's an accusation that in effect, Donald Trump broke the law during the presidential election campaign in buying the silence of two women who claimed to have had affairs with him. Michael Cohen has pleaded guilty to paying off the former porn star Stormy Daniels and a Playboy Model Karen McDougal in breach of Campaign Finance Laws. But the prosecutors say that he acted in coordination with and at the direction of Individual-1. Individual-1 in these court papers is the president.\nNearly 90,000 police are being deployed across France to counter a fourth weekend of protests by the "yellow vest" movement. Shops and metro stations have been closed in Paris. Lucy Williamson reports. Eight thousand security forces will be deployed in the capital, almost double that of last weekend. Another eighty thousand will be spread throughout France. They are expected to be more mobile than before and more proactive in tackling any threat. The government has said it expects extreme violence and that today's protesters include people who are coming explicitly to smash and it says to kill. The Interior Minister described the movement as a monster that was escaping its creators' control.\nA stampede at a nightclub in central Italy has killed at least six people. About a thousand people were in the venue in Corinaldo near Ancona, one of Italy's best-known rapper Sfera Ebbasta was performing at the club. Here's Caroline Rigby. What we're hearing is that people smelt a strong odor that they think might have been something like pepper spray. They fear that that might have been sprayed that caused people to panic inside, try and flee, trampling over each other according to officials and that caused a number of them to be crushed. We're hearing around a hundred have been injured, about ten of them seriously that they've been taken we understand to two nearby hospitals where the injured are being treated. You're listening to the world news from the BBC.\n![](images/nightclub.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，欢迎收听BBC新闻，我是菲奥娜·麦克唐纳德。在特朗普前律师迈克尔·科恩宣判之前，法庭公布的文件透露了他在2016年大选时与俄罗斯联系的新细节。特别顾问罗伯特·米勒的备忘录称科恩曾与一个“受信任”的俄罗斯联邦人士见过面。由联邦检察官发布的一份独立文件直接表明，特朗普与迈克尔·科恩向两名女性非法付款有关。以下是乔恩·苏博尔的报道。因这两个文件的发布，特朗普的总统生涯将会迎来一个关键节点。这是第一次在联邦检察官的文件中有对特朗普的指控，称他在总统竞选活动中花钱让两名女性保持沉默，这两名女性都声称与特朗普有染。迈克尔·科恩承认花钱买通前成人影星斯托米·丹尼尔斯和花花公子模特凯伦·麦克道戈，这违反了竞选金融法。但是检察官称他的行为是协同、并在“一号人物”的命令下实施的，法庭文件的一号人物指的是总统本人。\n法国部署了将近九万名警察，来对抗“黄马甲”运动人士第四周的抗议活动。巴黎的商店和地铁站都已关闭。以下是露西·威廉姆森的报道。八千名安全部队将会被部署在首都，几乎是上周人数的两倍，另外八万名警察将会分布在法国各地。预计他们在处理公共威胁方面将会更具机动性和主动性。政府表示将会迎来极度的暴力事件，今天的抗议人群中就有人明确表示是来破坏的，更有人称将会杀人。内政部长将这场运动称为洪水猛兽，现已脱离了其组织者的控制。\n意大利中部的一家夜店发生了一起踩踏事件，导致至少6人死亡。大约1000人聚集在安科纳市附近的科里纳尔多的一家场馆中，当时意大利一名非常出名饶舌歌手斯菲拉·伊博斯塔正在这家夜店表演。以下是卡罗兰·里戈比的报道。我们当时听到的是人们闻到了刺激的气味，他们认为应该是胡椒喷雾之类的东西。根据官方的消息，他们担心有人喷洒胡椒喷雾，造成了场馆内部人员的恐慌，人们仓皇失措四散逃离，造成了踩踏事件，并造成多人被踩伤。我们收到消息称现有100多人受伤，10人伤势严重，据我们所知伤者已被送往附近的两所医院接受治疗。您正在收听的是BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>17</id>
        <date>December 12, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - UNCCC in Poland failed in keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5℃</title>
        <description>
            Delegates at a UN climate change conference in Poland have expressed dismay over the failure to welcome an international report on keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5 degrees Celsius.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pollution.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181211_0704496Gbq.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Julie Candler with the BBC news. President Trump says his Chief of Staff John Kelly will leave his post at the end of the month. He told reporters he would decide on General Kelly's replacement within the next few days. A former Marine General with deep government know-how, John Kelly first served Mr. Trump as Homeland Security Secretary. As Chief of Staff, he was widely seen as bringing discipline to the White House. Here is Dan Johnson in Washington. The job of Chief of Staff is talked of as an important insider role, someone who can go into the Oval Office and tell the President the hard truth. So people are looking with interest for who Donald Trump will replace John Kelly with because he apparently was prepared to tell the President how it was. That's why their relationship has been fraught over the last eighteen months, why there have been occasions where apparently John Kelly was close to resigning.\nDelegates at a UN climate change conference in Poland have expressed dismay over the failure to welcome an international report on keeping the global rising temperatures under 1.5 degrees Celsius. Our environment correspondent Matt McGrath is at the conference. Here in Poland, efforts to welcome the report and recognize its significance quickly run into difficulties. Saudi Arabia, the US and Russia merely wanted to take note of the report. This dispute over words masks a deep row between countries that want rapid political action on cutting carbon and those who do not. As no acceptable compromise could be found, the text had to be dropped under UN rules. Many delegates were outraged by what they saw as a blatant attempt to weaken the science on climate change.\nSeveral women have come forward in Brazil to accuse an internationally known self-proclaimed spiritual healer of sexually abusing them. Joao Teixeira de Faria better known as Joao of God, has followers all over the world. Our America's editor Candace Piette has more details. On Brazil's Globo TV network, a Dutch woman Zahira Leeneke Maus accused Mr. Faria of manipulating her to perform sex acts and then raping her. Nine other Brazilian women who remained anonymous gave similar accounts. They say the abuse happened at Mr. Faria's spiritual clinic near Brasilia where he said to treat ten thousand people a month, many of them foreigners. In a statement to Globo TV, Mr. Faria's office strongly denied the allegations.\nThe government of Angola says it wants to begin discussions about the ownership and possible return of artifacts that were taken from the country before its independence from Portugal in 1975. The Culture Minister says so far no list of relevant objects has been put together, but that officials had identified several Angolan pieces of art in a museum in Lisbon. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/UNCCC.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是朱莉·钱德勒，欢迎收听BBC新闻。特朗普称白宫幕僚长约翰·凯利将会在月底卸任。他告诉记者称将会在几天内决定凯利将军的替代者。作为一名深谙政事的前海军将军，约翰·凯利最初任特朗普的国土安全部长。作为白宫幕僚长，他因为白宫肃整纪律而被广为所知。以下是丹·约翰逊在华盛顿的报道。幕僚长被认为是一个非常重要的内部角色，因为他可以直接走进总统办公室，向总统谏忠言，所以人们都很关心特朗普将会选谁作为约翰·凯利的替代者，因为很明显他准备告诉总统事情的来龙去脉，这也是为什么二人在过去18个月里关系令人担忧的原因。这也是为什么约翰·凯利多次几近辞职的原因。\n在波兰举行的联合国气候变化大会上，代表们感到十分失望，因为没有在全球控温1.5摄氏度这一国际报告上达成一致。以下是本台环境通讯员马特·麦格拉斯的在会议现场的报道。在波兰，这份报告的推广以及重要性认同方面很快遇到了困难。沙特阿拉伯、美国和俄罗斯仅仅表示会关注该报告。此次争论也隐藏了深层次的争吵，那就是想要立即采取政治措施减排和不想减排国家之间的争论。由于没有能接受的折中方案，这份报告只能按照联合国规定搁置。许多代表因一些国家公然无视气候变化的科学性而感到愤怒。\n在巴西，多名女性提出性侵指控，被指控人享誉国际，且自称是一名心灵治愈师。乔安·特谢拉·德·法里亚被熟知为“上帝的乔安”，他的追随者遍布全世界。以下是本台美洲编辑坎迪斯·皮尔特的报道。在巴西的环球电视台上，荷兰女性扎希拉·里尼卡·摩斯指控法里亚操纵她进行性行为，然后强奸了她。9名匿名的巴西女性也给予了类似的描述。她们称性侵就发生在法里亚在巴西利亚附近的精神诊所中，他称这里每月接待一万名病人，大部分都是外国人。在一份递交给环球电台的声明中，法里亚办公室强烈否认了这些指控。\n安哥拉政府表示希望与葡萄牙讨论1975年安哥拉独立前被抢走的艺术品的所有权并希望葡萄牙归还。葡萄牙文化部长表示目前为止没有相关的文物列表，但是其官员在里斯本的一家博物馆里认出了一些安哥拉艺术品。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>18</id>
        <date>December 13, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The former Nissan Chairman has been officially charged with underreporting his income</title>
        <description>
            The former Nissan Chairman Carlos Ghosn has been officially charged by Japanese prosecutors with underreporting his income by about 44 million dollars over a five-year period.
        </description>
        <cover>images/nissan-symbol.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1212_2312850BRX.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is the BBC News with Fiona Macdonald.\nThe former Nissan Chairman Carlos Ghosn has been officially charged by Japanese prosecutors with underreporting his income by about 44 million dollars over a five-year period. He denies the allegation. Mr. Ghosn was one of the most high-profile car company bosses in the world. From Tokyo, Rupert Wingfield-Hayes reports.\nProsecutors have finally indicted Mr. Ghosn, accusing him of making misstatement on Nissan's annual securities reports. The indictment has come 22 days after Mr. Ghosn's arrest at Tokyo airport, and on the last day prosecutors could hold him without charge. In addition, this morning, the Japanese Securities and Exchange Commission asked prosecutors to indict Mr. Ghosn for suspected violations of financial rules. It's not clear whether this is a new and separate allegation.\nArmenia's acting Prime Minister Nikol Pashinyan has consolidated his authority with a landslide victory in a snap parliamentary election. He came to power in a peaceful revolution earlier this year and has promised to tackle corruption and reform Armenia's economy. Rayhan Demytrie reports.\nNikol Pashinyan's My Step coalition has received around 70% of total votes cast by Armenians in snap parliamentary elections. Two other parties passed the threshold and will be apportioned seats in parliament. But the former governing Republican Party is out. Early results suggest it picked up less than five percent of the vote, a stunning defeat after ruling Armenia for almost two decades. Mr. Pashinian will now have to begin the task of carrying out ambitious reforms to improve his country's economy and raise standards of living for ordinary Armenians.\nExit polls from the Peruvian referendum suggest the country is back the anti-corruption reforms of President Martin Vizcarra. Local media reporting that people have voted in favor of judicial reform, changes to campaign finance laws, and restrictions on the number of consecutive terms able to be served.\nThe French President Emmanuel Macron is due to meet trade unionists and business leaders following another weekend of violent anti-government protests in Paris and other cities. Mr. Macron has remained largely silent over the unrest. He scheduled to make an address to the nation later on Monday.\nThe European Court of Justice is to rule in the next few hours on whether the UK can unilaterally pull out of the process governing its withdrawal from the EU. Last week, a chief legal advisor to the court said Britain could do so without permission from other member states, as long as the decision followed a parliamentary vote, a general election or a referendum.\nBBC news.\n![](images/nissan-chairman.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，欢迎收听BBC新闻，我是菲奥娜·迈克唐纳德。\n日产汽车前会长卡洛斯·戈恩现已被日本检察官正式提起公诉，罪名是在5年期间内未如实上报其收入约四千四百万美元。他本人否认了这项指控。戈恩曾是世界最知名汽车公司的老板之一。以下是鲁珀特·温菲尔德-海耶斯的报道。\n检察官最终向戈恩提起了诉讼，指控他在日产的年度证券报告中造假。戈恩在东京机场被捕22天后检方对他提起了诉讼，那也是检方可以在不起诉他的情况下扣押他的最后一天。另外，今晨日本证券交易委员会要求检察官以涉嫌违反金融法规的罪名起诉戈恩。现尚不明确这是否是一个新的不同的指控。\n亚美尼亚代理总理尼科尔·帕希尼扬以压倒性优势取得了议会提前选举的胜利，巩固了他的政权。他在今年年初的一次和平革命中上台，承诺将会处理贪污腐败问题并改革亚美尼亚的经济。以下是瑞翰·迪米特里的报道。\n在议会提前选举中，尼科尔·帕希尼扬所在的“我的步伐”联盟获得了约70%的选票。另外两个政党得票通过最低门槛，并将在议会中获得席位。但是前执政党共和党却已出局。早期结果表明该政党的选票不足5%，这也是该党执政亚美尼亚近20年来最大的落败。帕希尼扬现在需要开始实施他宏大的改革计划，以改善本国的经济并提高普通亚美尼亚民众的生活水平。\n秘鲁公投后的民调显示本国民众支持马丁·比斯卡拉总统的反腐改革。当地媒体报道称人们支持司法改革、竞选金融法革新以及对连任次数进行限制。\n法国总统埃马纽埃尔·马克龙将会见工会人士和商界领袖此前巴黎和其他城市周末再次爆发暴力反政府游行。马克龙在骚乱之后基本上都在保持沉默，他计划在周一发表全国演讲。\n欧洲法院将会在接下来的几个小时内裁定英国是否可以单方面退出脱欧进程。上周，欧洲法庭的一名首席法律顾问表示英国可以在不经过其他成员国的许可下退出，只要该决议通过议会投票、普选或是全民公投就行。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>19</id>
        <date>December 14, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The President of the European Commission has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit</title>
        <description>
            The President of the European Commission Jean-Claude Juncker has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit deal that the British Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to salvage.
        </description>
        <cover>images/brexit2.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181213_5721302yF6.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is Charles Carroll with the BBC News. The President of the European Commission Jean-Claude Juncker has said there's no room whatsoever to renegotiate the Brexit deal that the British Prime Minister Theresa May is trying to salvage. Mrs. May is on a tour of Europe to ask Mr. Juncker and her Dutch and German counterparts for assurances to try to convince sceptical British MPs to back the agreement. Earlier today, Mr. Juncker addressed the European Parliament. There is room if used intelligently, there is room enough to give further clarifications and further interpretations without opening the Withdrawal Agreement. This will not happen: everyone has to note that the Withdrawal Agreement will not be reopened. Many British MPs fear the country could become permanently stuck in a legally binding backstop plan to avoid re-establishing a hard border in Ireland. Mrs. May canceled a parliamentary vote on her deal due to have taken place today and acknowledged that she would have been defeated.\nThe United Nations has launched a plan to support more than five and a half million refugees from Syria who are being hosted in neighboring countries. The organization is appealing for 5.5 billion dollars to help provide education and other services. Imogen Foulkes reports from Geneva. Since the Syrian conflict began, a million Syrian babies have been born in exile. A trickle of refugees around thirty seven thousand have returned home this year, and that could increase to a quarter of a million next year. But it's just a fraction of the estimated 5.6 million Syrian refugees in neighboring countries. Return is risky. Sporadic fighting continues.\nAt least ten people have been killed in an overnight attack by a rebel group in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo. Local officials say suspected members of the Allied Democratic Forces attacked the town of Oicha in the Beni region where they looted property and animals. The ADF which began as a Ugandan rebel group in the 1990s, has been blamed for hundreds of killings since 2014.\nA Franco-German meeting is underway in Paris to counter the smuggling of illegal firearms from the western Balkans. The French Foreign Minister Jean-Yves Le Drian said that Europol estimated that up to six million firearms were in circulation in the countries of the former Yugoslavia. Forty-four thousand illegal firearms had been destroyed there over the past year, he said, but that was not enough. He stressed the need for tighter checks on the borders of Bosnia-Herzegovina. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/BritishPrimeMay.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是查尔斯·卡罗尔，欢迎收听BBC新闻。欧盟委员会主席让-克洛德·容克表示英国脱欧协议没有重新商讨的余地，英国首相特蕾莎·梅仍在努力挽救该协议。特蕾莎·梅正在欧洲寻访，并希望容克，荷兰和德国领导人能够给予保证，说服持怀疑态度的议员们支持这项协议，今天早些时候，容克在欧洲议会发表了讲话。如果明智的话，我们还有空间来继续阐明，给予更深入的解释，而无需启动脱欧协议。这是不会发生的，所有人都应该知道脱欧协议不会重启。很多英国议员害怕英国将会长期困在受法律约束的后备计划上，以避免爱尔兰再次出现“硬边界”问题。特蕾莎·梅取消了原定于今天举行的脱欧协议议会投票，并承认她有可能会被打败。\n联合国已经启动了一项对超过550万叙利亚难民的支持计划，他们正流落在邻国。该组织正在请求55亿美元的资金向他们提供教育和其他服务。以下是伊莫金·福克斯的报道。自从叙利亚冲突开始之后，有一百万叙利亚婴儿在流亡之路上出生。大约有三万七千人的小股难民已在今年返回故乡，明年这一数字将增加到二十五万人。但这也是逃亡到邻国的五百六十万难民的一小部分。回家之路充满危险，零星冲突还在继续。\n在刚果民主共和国东部，至少有10人在叛军夜袭中死亡。当地官员表示“民主联盟军”成员涉嫌袭击了贝尼地区的奥伊察镇，并抢走了他们的财产和家畜。“民主联盟军”由上世纪九十年代乌干达的一个叛军组织发展而来，因从2014年起杀害了数百人而饱受指责。\n一场法德会议现正在巴黎召开，来应对西巴尔干地区的非法军火走私问题。法国外长让-伊夫·勒德里昂表示欧洲刑警组织预计高达六百万件军火在前南斯拉夫国家流通。他表示，四万四千件非法军火去年在那里被销毁，但是还远远不够。他强调需要加强在波黑边界的检查。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>20</id>
        <date>December 15, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership</title>
        <description>
            The British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership of the governing Conservative Party.
        </description>
        <cover>images/starsbourg-terrorist-shooting.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1214_3534614MX4.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello.\nThe British Prime Minister Theresa May has survived a vote of no confidence in her leadership of the governing Conservative Party. The Party's Members of Parliament backed her by 200 votes to 117 in a secret ballot. The BBC's Laura Kuenssberg has this assessment.\nThis was a clear result in favor of the Prime Minister, but also a clear picture of a party in conflicts and a result brokered only by a promise from Theresa May to go, if not just yet. She'll have now what a loyal minister described as a little more time. And yes Tory rules say that she can stay on undisturbed by the same kind of challenge for another twelve months. But while she is temporarily safer, Theresa May has less clout. A Prime Minister with a sell-by date holds less sway.\nPresident Trump's former personal lawyer Michael Cohen has been sentenced to three years in prison for lying to Congress and violating US Election Finance Laws. Nada Tawfik is at the court in New York.\nMichael Cohen hung his head and shook it in disbelief when the sentence was read. He was hoping for no jail time, but the judge ultimately imposed three years in prison. Substantial but still on the lower end of sentencing guidelines. The judge said that Michael Cohen had lost his moral compass and should have known better as a lawyer, and he said that no future cooperation could be taken into consideration in sentencing.\nFrance remains on its highest level of security alert as the search continues for a gunman who shot dead two people near a Christmas market in Strasbourg on Tuesday. The authorities have issued a photo of the suspect. The French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe has announced the deployment of hundreds more soldiers across the country.\nAs of today, five hundred soldiers have been added to the force, and in the coming days, thirteen hundred will join those already mobilized. The objective is to secure sites open to the public, particularly Christmas markets.\nThe United States has warned Turkey against carrying out unilateral military action in northern Syria. The Pentagon said such a move would be of grave concern and could jeopardize US troops helping to fight the Islamic State group. The statement was issued after Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdogan said his forces would begin a military operation against a US-backed Kurdish militia in the region.\nYou're listening to the world news from the BBC News.\n![](images/conservative-party-vote.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n英国首相特蕾莎·梅挺过执政党保守党对她领导能力的不信任投票。在无记名投票中，党内国会议员给她投了200个支持票和117个反对票。以下是我台劳拉·昆斯伯格的观点。\n对于首相来说这明显是一个有利的结果，但是这也清楚地表明了党内存在分歧，而这一结果的促成源于特蕾莎·梅离任的承诺，离去只是时间问题。正如一名拥护她的大臣所说，她现在又多了一些时间。按照保守党的规定，一年内不会对她发起不信任投票。尽管她暂时安全一些了，但是特蕾莎·梅的影响力已不如从前。一个被加上“保质期”的首相，其影响力也会下降。\n特朗普总统的前私人律师迈克尔·科恩因对国会说谎以及违反美国选举财务法被判刑三年。以下是那达·托菲克在纽约法庭的报道。\n当法官宣判时，迈克尔·科恩俯首摇头，不敢相信这样的结果。他本希望不会被判入狱，但是法官最终判了他三年的刑期。虽获刑，但也是按照量刑标准从轻宣判。法官表示迈克尔·科恩丧失了道德准则，身为律师知法犯法，法官还表示宣判结果没有商量的余地。\n法国仍处于最高级别的安全警戒状态，同时也在继续搜寻一名枪手，周二他在斯特拉斯堡的一家圣诞节市场附近枪杀了两人。政府已经发布了嫌犯的照片。法国总理爱德华·菲利普宣布在全国范围内再部署数百名士兵。\n截至今天，已有500名士兵加入武装力量，接下来的几天里还会有1300名士兵加入到队伍中。他们的任务就是保护开放的公共区域，尤其是圣诞节市场。\n美国警告土耳其不要在叙利亚北部发动单方面军事行动。五角大楼表示这样的举动将会引起严重关切，也会危害帮助与伊斯兰国组织战斗的美国的士兵的安全。在此声明发布之前，土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安曾表示他的军队将会对该区域内美国支持的库尔德民兵组织发动军事行动。\n您正在收听的是BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>21</id>
        <date>December 16, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A Syria refugee living in British Villa as Green Fingers</title>
        <description>
            I have been so lucky to be living here for the last year. My parents, my brothers and sisters, I've sent them so many pictures and they don't believe it because for me this house is a place where I used to see in a movie, in an old English movie.
        </description>
        <cover>images/horticulture.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc181216_1238273D7T.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I have been so lucky to be living here for the last year. My parents, my brothers and sisters, I've sent them so many pictures and they don't believe it because for me this house is a place where I used to see in a movie, in an old English movie. The only reason that I left Syria and my brother who's two years older than me left was the government army, which we didn't want to join. We didn't want to hurt people, we didn't want to kill people.\nThat's not us. This is not what our religion taught us. I was hoping to come back in six months time. So, I was like: 'Mum I'm going to see you in six months time.' But here I am after seven years and I didn't see her. I started my journey through Turkey, Greece, the boat. Complete horror and just, just pure fear. We ended up in the Calais Jungle. The most horrendous place I've ever been in Europe. I've got to the UK, applied for asylum. I met this really nice lady who helped me when I was having trouble with accommodation and I met with the Chair and Trustee of this house, of Southside House. I have always felt lucky in this place. So mostly I work in the garden. I think they say I have green fingers. Green fingers? Is that right? I grew up in a very beautiful farm house with my parents, with animals. And I used to help my mum in the garden. My mum grew vegetables.\n![](images/english-house.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n我过去一年都住在这里，感觉自己太幸运了。我给我的父母还有兄弟姐妹发了很多照片，他们不相信我住在这，因为对我来说，这样的房子只存在于我过去常常看的电影里，英国老电影里。我离开了叙利亚，比我大两岁的哥哥也离开了，我们离开的唯一原因是因为政府军，我们不想加入政府军。我们不想伤害人，我们不想杀人。\n那不是我们想做的事。这不是我们的宗教教我们做的事。我当时希望六个月后就可以回去。所以当时想说：妈妈，我六个月后去看你。但是我在这里七年了，我没有去看她。我是从土耳其和希腊开始我的旅程的，做船。充满了恐怖，纯粹的恐惧。我们在加来丛林结束了旅程。那是我到欧洲后去过的最可怕的地方。我到了英国后，申请了避难。我遇到了这位非常善良的女士，她在我住宿遇到麻烦时帮助了我，我和这个房子——“南侧房”的主席兼受托人见了面。在这个房子里，我总是感觉很幸运。大部分时间我都在这个花园工作。我想他们说我有“绿手指”。绿手指？对吗？我在一个非常漂亮的农舍长大，还有父母和动物陪伴。我过去常常在菜园里帮我妈妈干活。我妈妈种菜。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>22</id>
        <date>December 17, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida has been broken</title>
        <description>
            The UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida that came to effect on Friday has been broken. Fighting erupted on the city's outskirts. Residents said they could hear shelling and gun fire. The Saudi-backed government and the Iranian-backed Houthi rebels had reached the truce after a week of talks in Sweden.
        </description>
        <cover>images/yemen-ruins-children.png</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1216_5431545hMR.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Ally Macue.\nThe UN-brokered cease fire in Yemen's main port of Hodeida that came to effect on Friday has been broken. Fighting erupted on the city's outskirts. Residents said they could hear shelling and gun fire. The Saudi-backed government and the Iranian-backed Houthi rebels had reached the truce after a week of talks in Sweden.\nThe military in Nigeria has accused the United Nation's Children’s Agency of training and deploying spies for Islamist militants, and suspended UNICEF operations in the northeast. The suspension has surprised the agency which told the BBC it would verify the statement.\nPresident Trump's former lawyer says the US leader knew he was wrong toward payments to keep 2 women silent about the alleged affairs with him. Mr. Trump had denied asking Michael Cohen who has been sentence to jail to break the law.\nThe head of the Russian Orthodox Church has accused Ukraine of persecuting believers. These comments come ahead of a meeting to create an independent Ukrainian church, a plan that has infuriated President Putin.\nThe United Nations has launched an emergency appeal to help house and feed around 3.5 million Venezuelan refugees who fled their country's severe economic crisis. The UN says it's the first plan of its kind in the Americas.\nProsecutors in Spain have accused the Columbian pop star Shakira of tax evasion, alleging that she owes more than 16 million dollars. They argued she was living in Spain for 2 years while listing her official residence elsewhere. Shakira denies evading tax.\nThe college campus in the Indian city of Madras has set up separate entrances and wash basins for students eating vegetarian and non-vegetarian food in the canteen. Some students have reportedly called the move untouchability.\nAnd the BBC's African Footballer of the Year award has gone to Liverpool's Egyptian striker Mohamed Salah. It's the second year in the row that he's won.\nBBC news.\n![](images/trump-deny-silence-affair.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nAlly Macue为您播报BBC新闻。\n联合国在也门的重要港市荷台达就停火进行了调解，而调解本来于周五生效，但现在又被打破了。荷台达郊区爆发了冲突。市民称他们听到了枪炮声。由沙特支持的政府军和伊朗支持的胡塞叛军在瑞典进行了一周的会谈后本来达成了停火协议。\n尼日利亚军方控诉联合国儿童基金会为伊斯兰激进分子培训并部署间谍，并终止了自己在东北部的行动。终止行动一举让联合国儿童基金会大为震惊。后者在接受BBC采访时表示会确认该说法的真实性。\n特朗普总统前律师称，特朗普知道自己不应该给2名女子封口费，让她们对与自己的风流韵事保持缄默。特朗普否认曾要求目前已入狱的迈克尔·科恩做违反法律的事情。\n俄罗斯东正教会领袖指责乌克兰迫害信徒。在此番言论之后将召开一场会议，这次会议将创建一个独立的乌克兰教会，而这个计划激怒了普京总统。\n联合国发起了应急呼吁，以帮助收留350万名委内瑞拉难民，并为他们提供食物。这些难民都是为了逃离本国严重的经济危机而来的。联合国表示，这是第一次在美洲发起这样的计划。\n西班牙检察官指控哥伦比亚流行歌手夏奇拉存在逃税行为，并称夏奇拉已逃税1600多万美元。检察官称，夏奇拉在西班牙生活了2年，但却将官方住处登记在其他地方。而夏奇拉本人否认逃税。\n印度马德拉斯市的大学校园在食堂设立了分开的入口和洗手池给素食主义者和非素食主义者。据报道，一些学生称此举完全是贱民制的表现。\n我台非洲足球先生的奖项颁发给了利物浦的埃及中锋穆罕默德·萨拉赫。这是穆罕默德·萨拉赫连续第二年获得该奖项。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>23</id>
        <date>December 18, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Australia now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel</title>
        <description>
            The Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison has said his country now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. But in a speech in Sydney, Mr. Morrison said the Australian embassy would not be relocated from Tel Aviv until the final status of Jerusalem was resolved.
        </description>
        <cover>images/sri-lanka.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181217_0244391RFT.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news. I'm John Shea. Tens of thousands of police have been deployed across France in preparation for the latest protests by the "yellow vests" movement. Paris has been shaken by some of the most serious rioting in decades over the last two weekends. Indications so far are that fewer people will join the demonstrations this week. Here's Hugh Schofield. After President Microns offered to open up the state's coffers on Monday, some in the "yellow vests" movement have acknowledged that that was a major step forward and they are calling for a pause. Others fear that the violence at the last two Saturday protests, much of it actually caused by young opportunists rather than bona fide protestors, is damaging the cause. But there are still "yellow vests" surround the country who feel that now is not the time to ease up the pressure. They feel that if Macron has given once he can give again.\nThe UN climate conference in Poland has been extended to allow negotiators more time to finalize a deal on cutting greenhouse gas emissions. The talks continued through the night on contentious issues, including how poor countries should be compensated for the damage caused by global warming.\nMahinda Rajapaksa has announced his resignation as Sri Lanka's prime minister. In a statement, he said he had no intention of continuing in the post without a general election being held. With the details here's Anbarasan Ethirajan. Mahinda Rajapaksa who strongly believes in astrology, signed his resignation letter in an auspicious time during a religious ceremony held at his home in Colombo. He was controversially appointed two months ago by President Maithripala Sirisena to replace Ranil Wickremesinghe, triggering a political crisis in Sri Lanka. But he failed to command a majority in Parliament and a court also restrained him from acting as Prime Minister. In a statement, Mr. Rajapaksa said his resignation would make way for the president to form a new government. There are suggestions that Mr. Rajapaksa's resignation could lead to Mr. Wickremasinghe returning to power on Sunday.\nThe Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison has said his country now recognizes West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. But in a speech in Sydney, Mr. Morrison said the Australian embassy would not be relocated from Tel Aviv until the final status of Jerusalem was resolved. He said the decision took him to account the interests of both sides. Australia now recognizes West Jerusalem, being the seat of the Knesset and many of the institutions of government, is the capital of Israel. Furthermore, recognizing our commitment to a two-state solution, the Australian government is also resolved to acknowledge the aspirations of the Palestinian people for a future state with its capital in East Jerusalem. This is the latest world news from the BBC.\n![](images/west-jerusalem.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，我是约翰·席亚。法国各地部署了数万名警察，为近期的“黄马甲”抗议活动做准备。在过去的两周内，巴黎受到了数十年来最严重的骚乱活动。到目前为止，有迹象表明本周参加游行的人在减少，以下是休·斯科菲尔德的报道。总统马克龙周一提出将会打开国库，一些“黄马甲”活动人士承认这是重要一步，并且呼吁暂停游行活动。一些人担心最近两个周六的抗议活动是由年轻的机会主义者引起的，而不是真正的游行人员，这将会给游行活动带来不好的影响。但是现在仍有“黄马甲”人士在法国境内游行，他们称现在还不能松懈对政府的压力。他们认为马克龙能让步一次就能让步第二次。\n在波兰举行的联合国气候大会现已延期，目的是给与谈判者更多的时间达成关于削减温室气体排放的协议。会议连夜讨论了争议问题，包括欠发达国家如何弥补气候变暖造成的损失。\n马欣达·拉贾帕克萨宣布将辞去斯里兰卡总理职务。在一份声明中，他表示如果不进行大选，他将没有继续任职的意愿。以下是安巴拉森·安提拉的报道。马欣达·拉贾帕克萨本人深信占星术，他在家乡科伦坡的宗教活动期间选了一个黄道吉日签署了辞职信。两个月之前，他在争议之中被总统迈特里帕拉·西里塞纳任命为总理，代替了拉尼尔·拉贾帕克萨，这也引起了斯里兰卡的政治危机。但是他未能让该党在国会中占据多数席位，法庭同样也限制了他总理的实权。在声明中，拉贾帕克萨表示他的辞职将会给总统组建新的政府扫清道路。有迹象表明，拉贾帕克萨的辞职将会导致拉贾帕克萨在周六重新就职总理。\n澳大利亚总理斯科特·莫里森表示澳大利亚现在承认西耶路撒冷为以色列首都。但是在悉尼的讲话中，莫里森表示，在耶路撒冷首都身份被最终确认之前，澳大利亚大使馆将不会从特拉维夫迁出。他表示考虑了双方利益之后做了这个决定。澳大利亚现在承认西耶路撒冷为以色列首都，这里是国会以及许多政府机构所在地。另外，为了贯彻我们的两国方针，澳大利亚同样决定承认巴基斯坦人民对于东耶路撒冷作为其首都的渴望。以上为最新的BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>24</id>
        <date>December 19, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Pakistani has approved death sentences for fifteen terrorists</title>
        <description>
            The head of the Pakistani Army has approved death sentences for fifteen people convicted by military courts of involvement in Islamic attacks.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pakistani-terrorists.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181218_59273296tg.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News. I'm John Shea. Environmental groups and some countries have criticized Saturday's agreement at the UN climate conference in Poland as lacking in ambition. The deal sought to lay down the rules to implement the 2015 Paris accord. David Shookman has this assessment. Applause and relief in Katowice mask some difficult questions about this latest deal. Under the new rules, countries are expected to publish their plans for cutting their emissions of greenhouse gases. But the Paris Agreement is voluntary, so no government is under any obligation. And even if every country takes the steps that they've promised to, the world will still be on course for what scientists consider dangerous levels of warming. But critics point to the most recent assessment by the UN climate panel, which concluded that emissions must start falling in the next twelve years.\nSri Lanka's ousted Prime Minister Ranil Wickremasinghe has been sworn back into office nearly two months after he was sacked by President Maithripala Sirisena. The move plunged Sri Lanka into a political crisis which saw Mr. Wickremasinghe replaced by the former President Mahinda Rajapaksa, but he's faced political and legal setbacks as Charles Haviland reports. Mr. Wickremasinghe's return to office is likely to end seven weeks of constitutional chaos. In October, his uneasy political ally President Sirisena tried to boot him out and replace him with Mahinda Rajapaksa, the hard-line nationalist ex-president. Mr. Sirisena also tried to dissolve Parliament, but on Thursday the Supreme Court deemed that action illegal. The crisis has rocked a country still grappling with an ugly pattern of human rights abuses during its long ethnic war.\nThe head of the Pakistani Army has approved death sentences for fifteen people convicted by military courts of involvement in Islamic attacks. Twenty other militants were given prison sentences. This report from Charish Haney. The confirmation of the death sentences comes as Pakistan marks the fourth anniversary of an attack on an army-run school in Peshawar in which more than a hundred and fifty people were killed. The attack prompted Pakistan to lift a six-year moratorium on executions, and hundreds are reported to have been put to death since then. The fifteen who had their death sentences confirmed could appeal. Rights groups say military trials are unfair, but the authorities insist they have no choice in a country ravaged by militancy. BBC News.\n![](images/ranil-wickremasinghe.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，我是约翰·席亚。环境保护组织和一些国家批评了波兰联合国气候大会达成的协议，称其缺乏“雄心壮志”。该协议旨在制定规定来落实2015年的《巴黎协定》，以下是大卫·舒克曼的报道。在卡兹委托会议的掌声和欣慰的掩盖之下，这项最新的协议还有很多棘手的问题。在新的规定之下，各国应该公开削减温室气体排放的计划。但是《巴黎协定》是自愿性质的，所以谈不上义务。即使每个国家都按照承诺采取了措施，世界还是会继续升温到科学家所认为的危险水平。但批评人士指向了联合国气候小组近期的评估，该评估称碳排放必须在接下来的12年内开始下降。\n斯里兰卡被罢黜的总理拉尼尔·维克勒马辛哈重新宣誓就职，近两个月之前，他被总统迈特里帕拉·西里塞纳解雇。维克勒马辛哈被前总统拉贾帕克萨替代时，还引起了斯里兰卡的一次政治危机，但是后者遇到了政治和法律上挫折。以下是查尔斯·哈维兰的报道。维克勒马辛哈重新上任有可能会结束七周的宪法危机。然而在十月份，他的政治盟友，总统西里塞纳曾解雇他，并让强硬派民族主义者，前总统马欣达·拉贾帕克萨就职。西里塞纳同样想解散国会，但是周二最高法院认为此举不合法。该危机震动了斯里兰卡，然而这个国家还没有摆脱其漫长民族战争中丑陋的侵犯人权问题。\n巴基斯坦军领导人批准了15人死刑判决，军事法庭判处他们有罪，他们参与了伊斯兰袭击。另外20名武装分子被判服刑，以下是查理士·汉尼的报道。死刑判决确认的同时正值四周年纪念，白沙瓦一所军营学校四年前遭袭，当时有150多人被杀。该袭击促使巴基斯坦取消了6年死刑缓刑制度，据报道已有数百人被执行死刑。被确认死刑判决的这15人可以上诉。人权组织表示军事宣判是不公平的，但是政府表示在一个武装分子肆虐的国家这也是不得已的选择。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>25</id>
        <date>December 20, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - A judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch Bambi</title>
        <description>
            A judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch repeat screenings of the Walt Disney film Bambi as part of his sentence.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fawn-bambi.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1219_4329637Vdw.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News.\nFighting has erupted again around the Yemeni port of Hodeida after a United Nations-brokered ceasefire failed to take hold. Houthi rebels and the Saudi-backed government had agreed to halt the violence at talks in Sweden last week, but government officials accused the Iranian-backed Houthis of shelling government troops east of Hodeidah just minutes after the truce came into force.\nA court in El Salvador has freed a woman who spent a year and seven months in jail accused of trying to abort her baby. The 20-year-old woman Imelda Cortez said that she became pregnant by her stepfather who sexually abused her for many years. Leonardo Rocha has more details.\nImelda Cortez said that she began being sexually abused by her stepfather when she was 12 and in April last year she gave birth to a baby. She says the baby is from her stepfather who's now in his seventies. Doctors in El Salvador, they accuse her of trying to terminate the pregnancy, which in El Salvador amounts to a charge of attempted murder.\nThe family of a dying two-year-old boy in California say his Yemeni mother is being prevented from visiting him by the Trump administration's travel ban on visitors from seven mainly Muslim countries. Doctors say Abdullah Hassan is terminally ill with a brain disease. The boy's father, whose was born in California, brought him to the US. Saad Sweilem is from the Council on American-Islamic Relations.\nThey've been actually waiting for over a year to try to get her to be able to come here. Just a few months ago, they finally realized, you know we can't wait much longer. So the father went ahead and brought Abdullah here to the US in hopes that he'd get medical treatment and in the meantime, his wife would be able to get her visa situation ratified and become joined them. But instead it's taken a turn for the worst and now we find her son Abdullah here and his mother unable to come be by his side.\nA judge in the US state of Missouri has ordered a convicted deer poacher to watch repeat screenings of the Walt Disney film Bambi as part of his sentence. Generations of children and adults have been reduced to tears by the carton film of Bambi released in 1942 in which the young fawn's mother is killed by a hunter. Here's Anthony Zahra.\nA judge in Missouri has sentenced David Berry Jr. to watch the film once a month during a year-long jail sentence. Berry has been convicted of illegally killing hundreds of deer and taking their heads for trophies. Officials said it was one of their largest-ever poaching investigations.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/salvador.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n联合国斡旋下的停火协议未能实现，也门港口城市荷台达再起战火，上周瑞典会谈时，胡塞武装和沙特支持的政府军同意停止暴力，但是政府官员指责伊朗支持的胡塞叛军在荷台达东部向政府军开炮，而此时距离停火协议生效仅几分钟。\n萨尔瓦多的一家法庭释放了一名因意图堕胎而入狱一年零七个月的女性。这名20岁的女性名为伊美黛·科特兹，她表示自己被其继父性侵多年，最终导致怀孕。以下是莱昂纳多·罗查的详细报道。\n伊美黛·科特兹表示她从12岁开始被其继父性侵，并在去年4月生下一名婴儿。她表示孩子是她继父的，而他现已70多岁。萨尔瓦多医生指控她意图终止妊娠，而这在萨尔瓦多被认为是谋杀未遂。\n在美国加州，一名生命垂危的两岁男孩的家人称他在也门的妈妈因特朗普政府对7个主要穆斯林国家的旅行禁令而不能来到他的身边。医生表示阿卜杜拉·哈桑患脑疾且生命垂危。男孩的父亲出生在加州，他将男孩带到了美国。以下是美国伊斯兰关系理事会的萨德·斯韦勒姆的讲话。\n实际上他们已经等了一年多想让孩子的母亲来到美国。几个月之前，他们最终意识到已经不能再等了。于是父亲先带着阿卜杜拉来到了美国，希望他能得到治疗，同时也希望妻子的签证获批从而和他们团聚。但现在男孩的病情恶化，我们看到病床上的阿卜杜拉而他的母亲却无法来到他的身边。\n美国密苏里州的一名法官下令一名小鹿偷猎者反复观看迪士尼影片《小鹿斑比》，并将此作为他判刑的一部分。几代人，不论大人还是小孩都被这部1942年上映动画片《小鹿斑比》感动地流下了眼泪，影片中小鹿的妈妈被猎人猎杀。以下是安东尼·扎赫拉的报道。\n密苏里州的一名法官判处小大卫·贝里有期徒刑一年，并在此期间内每月观看这部影片一次。贝里因非法猎杀数百头鹿并取下鹿头作为战利品而被判刑。相关官员表示这是该州有史以来调查的最大偷猎案件之一。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>26</id>
        <date>December 21, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - New York's Attorney General closed the charity established in President Trump's name</title>
        <description>
            New York's Attorney General has held the closure of the charity established in President Trump's name as a victory for the rule of law.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-charity.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181220_0417129WMe.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm David Harper with the BBC News. New York's Attorney General has held the closure of the charity established in President Trump's name as a victory for the rule of law. Barbara Underwood, who is a Democrat, accused the Trump Foundation of engaging in a shocking pattern of illegality. Our north American editor Jon Sopel has more details on the charity. Far from this being a vehicle for giving and philanthropy, the New York Attorney General has described in the most scathing terms how the Trumps were using this for their own purposes. There was a shocking pattern of illegality, including unlawful coordination with the Trump presidential campaign. Repeated and willful self-dealing, this amounted to the Trump Foundation functioning as little more than a checkbook to serve Mr. Trump's business and political interests. Trump's attorneys said those accusations were inaccurate and politicized.\nA judge in the United States has delayed the sentencing of President Trump's former national security advisor Michael Flynn to give more time for him to cooperate with prosecutors. The judge was fiercely critical of Mr. Flynn, saying it could be argued that he sold out his country. Mr. Flynn pleaded guilty last year to lying to the FBI about his contacts with the Russian ambassador to the US. At a briefing, the White House spokesperson Sarah Sanders expressed the administration's support for Mr. Flynn. The delay is something between General Flynn and the courts, and that's something for them to determine what timeline looks like. In the meantime, we wish General Flynn well, and we'll continue to focus on doing what we do here every single day.\nThe Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has offered his resignation following the withdrawal earlier this month of one of the partners in his governing coalition. Kevin Connolly reports from Brussels. Charles Michel, a French-speaking liberal, has been in government with the conservative movement of Flemish-speaking nationalists, the NVA. When that coalition collapsed last week cause of NVA's rejections to Mr. Michel's decision to agree to the new UN declaration on migration, it left Mr. Michel out on a limb. His resignation is now held in suspension, leaving him as a kind of caretaker Prime Minister. Somehow, Mr. Michel now has to find a way to pass a federal budget. If he can't, the country will edge closer to political crisis. Kevin Connolly reporting from Brussels.\nHuman Rights Watch has called on the authorities in Mali to prosecute militia members and their leaders, saying attacks in the center of the country are spiraling out of control. Earlier this month, an ethnic Dogon militia killed 34 people from the Fulani ethnic group. World news from the BBC.\n![](images/belgian-prime-minister-charles-michel.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是的大卫·哈珀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。纽约总检察长宣布关闭特朗普名下的基金会，并将此视作法制的胜利。芭芭拉·安德伍德是一名民主党人士，她表示特朗普基金会的违法行为令人震惊。以下是本台北美编辑乔恩·苏博尔的详细报道。该基金会不仅不是一个捐赠和慈善的工具，相反纽约总检察长言辞尖刻地描述了特朗普家族是如何用它为自己谋利的。它的违法模式令人震惊，包括与特朗普总统竞选活动的非法合作。通过连续的蓄意自利交易，特朗普基金会只不过是特朗普商业和政治利益的支票簿。特朗普的律师称这些指控不正确，且是政治化的指控。\n美国一法官推迟了特朗普前国家安全顾问迈克尔·弗林的宣判日期，目的是给他更多的时间和检察官合作。这名法官严厉地批判了弗林，称其行为可以认作是卖国。弗林在去年认罪，承认他在与俄罗斯驻美国大使联系一事中向FBI说谎。白宫发言人萨拉·桑德斯在发布会中表达了政府对弗林的支持。宣判推迟是弗林将军与法庭的事，具体的宣判时间也会由他们决定。同时，我们希望弗林将军身体健康，我们也会在处理白宫日常事务的同时继续关注此事。\n比利时首相夏尔·米歇尔提出辞呈，原因是本月初有执政联盟合作伙伴退出，以下是凯文·康诺利在布鲁塞尔的报道。夏尔·米歇尔是一个说法语的自由党人，他与发动保守运动的民族主义人士，“新弗拉芒联盟党”组成了联合政府。执政联盟上周瓦解，因为“新弗拉芒联盟党”拒绝米歇尔签署联合国关于移民问题的新宣言，而这也让他处于一个孤立无援的境地。他的辞职被暂时搁置，这也让他成为了临时首相。米歇尔现在需要设法通过一项联邦预算，如果失败的话，国家将会进入政治危机的边缘。以上是凯文·康诺利的报道。\n人权观察组织呼吁马里政府起诉民兵组织成员及其领导人，称马里中部的袭击活动正失去控制。本月初，多贡族民兵组织杀害了34名富拉尼族平民。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>27</id>
        <date>December 22, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Japan has decided to withdraw from the IWC in order to resume whaling on a commercial basis</title>
        <description>
            In September, Japan launched a controversial bid to ease the moratorium on commercial whaling imposed by the IWC more than thirty years ago. But its argument that whale stocks has recovered sufficiently to justify the resumption of sustainable hunting was voted down. That seems to have paved the way for this decision. According to the Kyoto News Agency, Tokyo would only allow whaling in the seas around Japan and not stray into Antarctic waters.
        </description>
        <cover>images/japan-whaling.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1221_2206384pgR.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News. Hello, I'm Gareth Barlow.\nSenators in the United States, including high-profile Republicans, have condemned President Trump's announcement that he's withdrawing American forces from Syria. Six senators led by the Republican Lindsey Graham have written to Mr. Trump, accusing him of making a costly mistake that threatened US security.\nEarlier, the chair of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Bob Corker, said the move was completely unexpected. We've got allies around the world that have been with us all this time, have been fighting with us. There's probably fifty or sixty countries that have been involved in some form of fashion. To my knowledge, we didn't even communicate with them that this morning we were gonna make this announcement. It's caught everybody off guard. I know that, I doubt there's anybody in the Republican Caucus in the Senate that just isn't stunned.\nBritain, a major ally of the US has expressed concern and questioned Mr. Trump's assertion that Islamic State militants in Syria had been defeated. The British Defense Minister Tobias Ellwood said that on the contrary, the threat from IS was very much alive.\nJapanese government sources say the country has decided to withdraw from the International Whaling Commission in order to resume whaling on a commercial basis. The BBC's Cat Wiener has more details.\nIn September, Japan launched a controversial bid to ease the moratorium on commercial whaling imposed by the IWC more than thirty years ago. But its argument that whale stocks has recovered sufficiently to justify the resumption of sustainable hunting was voted down. That seems to have paved the way for this decision. According to the Kyoto News Agency, Tokyo would only allow whaling in the seas around Japan and not stray into Antarctic waters.\nMeanwhile, a court in Japan has rejected a request by prosecutors to extend the detention of Carlos Ghosn, the former chairman of Nissan who was sacked for alleged financial misconduct. The ruling means he could soon be released. With the details, Steve Jackson reports.\nCarlos Ghosn was first detained on the nineteenth of November when his private jet landed in Tokyo. The 64-year-old French-Brazilian was one of the world's most powerful auto industry executives, but has spent the past month in prison. During that time, he's been charged with lying about his pay for several years. He's accused of hiding eighty million dollars of income and of misusing company funds. He denies all the allegations. The timing of his release is unclear, but Japanese media say it could happen as soon as Friday. The court also rejected an extension to the detention of Greg Kelly, an aide to Mr. Ghosn.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![](images/withdraw-forces-from-syria.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，大家好，我是加雷斯·巴罗。\n包括知名共和党人在内的美国议员对特朗普宣布从叙利亚撤军进行了谴责。以共和党人林赛·格雷厄姆为首的六名议员致信特朗普，指责他犯了一个代价高昂的错误，威胁到了美国的安全。\n早前，参议院外交关系委员会主席鲍勃·考克尔曾表示此举完全出人意料。一直以来，我们的盟友遍布世界各地。他们一直与我们并肩战斗。美国在全世界大约有50到60个这样的盟国。据我所知，我们甚至没有和他们沟通过，他们不知道今晨我们会做出这样的决定。这让每个人都措手不及，我知道，恐怕参议院共和党核心小组内没人不对此感到震惊。\n作为美国的一个重要盟友，英国也对此表示关切，并质疑了特朗普关于叙利亚境内伊斯兰国军事力量已被击败的声明。英国国防部长托比亚斯·埃尔伍德表示，与特朗普所言相反，伊斯兰国组织的威胁依旧很大。\n日本政府消息称日本已决定退出国际捕鲸协会，以恢复商业捕鲸业。以下是BBC记者卡特·温纳的详细报道。\n九月，日本发起了一项具有争议的恢复商业捕鲸提议，要求解除30多年前IWC强制实行的商业捕鲸禁令。日本辩称鲸鱼的数量现已充分恢复可以重新开始持续捕鲸，但遭到否决。这似乎给日本恢复捕鲸的决定铺平了道路。京都新闻社报道称，日本将只允许在日本周边海域捕鲸，并不进入大西洋海域。\n同时，日本一法庭拒绝了检方要求延长日产前董事长卡洛斯·戈恩羁押期的要求，不久前卡洛斯因所谓的财政不当行为遭解雇。法庭的裁定意味着他可能在不久之后会被释放。以下是史蒂夫·杰克森的详细报道。\n卡洛斯·戈恩首次在11月19日被拘押，当时他的私人飞机落地东京。这名64岁的法裔巴西人曾是世界上最强汽车企业高管之一，但是过去半个月却在狱中度过。在此期间，他被指控在多年的薪资问题上说谎。他被指控隐报了八千万美元的收入并挪用了公司的资金。他否认了所有指控。他的释放日期尚不清楚，但是日本媒体称最早周五就会被释放。该法庭也拒绝延长戈恩助手格蕾格·凯利的羁押期。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>28</id>
        <date>December 23, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The US Central Bank has raised interest rate the fourth time this year up to 2.5%</title>
        <description>
            The US Central Bank, the Federal Reserve, has raised interest rate the fourth time this year despite repeated demands by Donald Trump not to do so. It’s gone up by a quarter of a percentage point to 2.5%.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-vs-uscb.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1222_0217428QY7.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Julie Candler.US officials say American troops have begun pulling out of Syria. The unexpected announcement follows a tweet in which President Trump said Islamic State militants in the country had been defeated. The decision was revealed after discussions between Mr. Trump and his Turkish counterpart Recep Tayyip Erdogan. Within the hours of the pullout being made public, the US said it had approved the sale of billions of dollars of missiles to Turkey.\nThe US Central Bank, the Federal Reserve, has raised interest rate the fourth time this year despite repeated demands by Donald Trump not to do so. It’s gone up by a quarter of a percentage point to 2.5%.\nThe Italian Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte has insisted that his government will keep the spending promises it’s made to voters following a budget deal with the EU. He said no concessions had been made in order to avoid EU fines.\nPolice in the Congolese capital Kinshasa have fired tear gas to disperse stone-throwing opposition supporters ahead of Sunday’s presidential election. Earlier, the local governor imposed a ban on all campaign rallies in the city referring to security concerns.Thousands of people have demonstrated in two Sudanese cities over the price of fuel and bread. Videos posted on social media show crowds marching through the street of Atbara and Port Sudan.\nA Supreme Court judge in Brazil has issued a ruling that could lead to the release from jail of the former President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva. Lula is appealing against a 12-year sentence for corruption.\nThe German news magazine Der Spiegel has sacked an award-winning journalist after discovering that he had fabricated some of his stories. Claas Relotius was recently named German Reporter of the Year for an article about a young Syrian boy. Der Spiegel said he had admitted falsifying many of his articles.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nJulie Candler播报BBC新闻。美国官员表示，美国军队已经开始撤出叙利亚了。这次宣布出乎意料，因为此前，特朗普总统还发推文称叙利亚的伊斯兰国（IS）激进分子已被击溃。这次宣布发布前，特朗普和土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安进行了讨论。撤军消息公布的数小时内，美国表示自己已经审批同意向土耳其出售价值数十亿美元的导弹。\n美国央行美联储今年第4次提高了利率，虽然特朗普曾要求不要这样做。利率提高了0.25个百分点，升至2.5%。\n意大利总理朱塞佩·孔特坚持认为，意大利政府要信守其向选民做出的资金支出承诺，虽然已经与欧盟签订了预算协议。孔特表示，虽然政府想要避开欧盟的罚款，但不会做出让步。\n刚果首都金沙萨警方发射了催泪弹，以驱散投掷石头的反对派支持者，毕竟周日就要进行总统大选。此前，金沙萨州长禁止各种形式的竞选集会，因为担心有安全问题。\n无数人在2个苏丹城市就燃料和面包涨价进行抗议。社交媒体上的视频显示，有大批人群在阿特巴拉河和苏丹港游行示威。\n巴西最高法院某法官进行了判决，该判决可能可以让路易斯·伊纳西奥·卢拉·达席尔瓦出狱。卢拉正在就贪污案可能导致的12年刑期进行上诉。\n德国新闻杂志《明镜周刊》解雇了一位获奖记者，因为发现这名记者捏造了部分报道。这位记者名为克拉斯，最近还获得德国年度记者的称号，获奖作品是一篇有关一名叙利亚小男孩的报道。《明镜周刊》表示，该记者已承认篡改过自己的很多文章。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>29</id>
        <date>December 24, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The capacity to survive is an inherent inborn talent or a function of learning certain behavioural tactics?</title>
        <description>
            Hayes was a very successful stock trader on the New York stock exchange. He believed that the capacity to survive and to do well is an inherent inborn talent. He would argue he could be a survivor anywhere. I spent my life in the woods, hunting and fishing. I argue on the other hand that survival is more a function of learning certain behavioural tactics to get by, and that they are environmentally specific.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pistol.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc181223_5445944tpW.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hayes was a very successful stock trader on the New York stock exchange. He believed that the capacity to survive and to do well is an inherent inborn talent. He would argue he could be a survivor anywhere. I spent my life in the woods, hunting and fishing. I argue on the other hand that survival is more a function of learning certain behavioural tactics to get by, and that they are environmentally specific. And I said to Hayes 'If you come up to New Hampshire and went out in the woods with me, you wouldn't have a chance.'\nA friend of mine sent me sent me a catalogue that had in it a pistol, and it shot a little ball of paint about this big round, and it was used by foresters to mark trees to be cut down and so forth. And I have one of those eureka moments. Two things come together. I called Hayes up, and said 'I've figured out how we are going to prove this argument one way or another.' So I ordered two of these guns, and a bunch of the pellets, and Hayes came up to my house. We decided we'd test these guns out because as far as we'd known, nobody had ever shot a person with them. Hayes shot first, and he missed, and I shout him right it in the butt. And it hurt! So then what we did, we went out into forty acres of woods and Hayes went in one end, I went in the other, and we hunted each other. Within about 20 minutes I came around a big maple tree, and Hayes was sitting on a rock, and I walked right up behind him, and put the barrel of the gun right on his neck, and said 'alright, I don't want to shoot you, who wins?!'\n**参考译文：**\n海斯是纽约证券交易所一位很成功的证券交易人。他相信生存的能力和生存的好的能力是一种内在的天生的才华。他认为他在哪里都能生存。我一辈子都生活在树林里，打猎和钓鱼。我则认为生存更多是学习某些行为策略来存活的能力，这些策略和特定环境有关。我对海斯说：“如果你来新罕布什尔州，和我一起去树林里，你不会有机会的。”\n我的一个朋友给我寄了一个产品样品，里面是一个手枪，它会射出这么大这么圆的彩色的小球，这种小球是森林作业者用来标记要砍的树和干其他事情。然后我就有了灵感。两件事连一起了。我给海斯打了电话说：“不管怎么做，我已经知道了证明这场争论谁对谁错的办法。”然后我订购了两把这样的手枪和一把这样的小球，海斯来到了我家。我们决定测试下这些枪，因为据我们所知，还没有人用它来射人。海斯先射的，射歪了，我直接射到他屁股上了。他感觉疼！后来我们做的事就是我们去了一个占地四十英亩的树林里，海斯去了一边，我去了另一边，我们互相猎杀对方。不到20分钟，我绕到了一颗大枫树边，海斯那时坐在一块石头上，我径直走到他后面，把枪管正架在他脖子上说：“好吧，我不想射你，谁赢了？！”
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>30</id>
        <date>December 24, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has handed his government’s resignation</title>
        <description>
            The Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has handed his government’s resignation after a no-confidence vote was tabled in parliament.
        </description>
        <cover>images/belgian-prime-minister-charles-michel.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1223_2204960hR6.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with David Harper.\nA judge in Washington has fiercely criticized President Trump’s former national security adviser Michael Flynn, saying it could be argued that he had sold out his country. At a hearing in Washington, he expressed distain and disgust. The sentencing of Mr. Flynn for lying to the FBI was postponed to allow more time for him to cooperate with investigators.\nDonald Trump has agreed to shut down his family charity, the Trump Foundation. New York’s Attorney General said Mr. Trump had used the foundation as a personal checkbook for his business and political interests. A lawyer for the charity accused the attorney general of issuing a misleading statement.\nBritain’s Defense Secretary says 3,500 soldiers are ready to assist in the event of a no-deal Brexit. Earlier, the cabinet decided to step up preparations for leaving the European without a deal in March.An official report into post-election violence in Zimbabwe earlier this year has found that troops used disproportional force against opposition protesters. Inquiries said soldiers were not justified in shooting dead six demonstrators.\nThe Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel has handed his government’s resignation after a no-confidence vote was tabled in parliament. He’d been trying to run a minority government since his Flemish coalition in parliament withdrew earlier this month. It pulled out a protest at the government’s backing for UN deal on migration.\nThe Brazilian construction firm Andrade Gutierrez has signed a deal with the government as part of a corruption inquiry, and promised to pay back $400 million. The company has admitted paying bribes to government officials.\nEuropean football’s governing body UEFA is investigating alleged anti-semitic chanting by supporters of Chelsea in a match last week in Hungary. A small section of the English fans were heard using a chant that included a derogatory word for Jews.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nDavid Harper为您播报BBC新闻。\n华盛顿某法官猛烈抨击了特朗普的前国家安全顾问迈尔克·弗林，并表示有理由证明他背叛了自己的国家。在华盛顿举行的听证会上，该法官表达了对弗林的蔑视和厌恶。因弗林向美国联邦调查局（FBI）撒谎而对其进行的判决进行了推迟，因为想让他有更多的时间跟调查人员合作。\n特朗普同意关闭其家族慈善团体——特朗普基金会。纽约州总检察长表示，特朗普曾将该基金会作为私人支票簿，用于商业和政治领域。该基金会的一位律师控诉这位总检察长，称他发布的声明有误导性。\n英国国防部部长表示，3500名士兵愿意协助应对无协议脱欧可能带来的后果。此前，英国内阁决定再接再厉，为3月份无协议脱欧做准备。\n有一份官方报告内容与津巴布韦选举后的暴力形势有关，这份报告是今年年初发布的。报告指出，军队动用大量兵力针对反对派抗议者。报告还指出，士兵们在没有充分理由的情况下射杀了6名抗议者。\n比利时总理米歇尔递交了辞呈，根据是议会对他进行不信任投票的结果。米希尔曾试图建立少数派政府，因为他在议会的新弗拉芒联盟本月初已经脱离了组织，并发起了抗议，因为政府支持联合国与移民有关的协议。\n巴西建筑公司安德拉德古铁雷斯与政府签订而来一份协议，该协议是腐败调查的部分内容。该公司还承诺偿还政府4亿美元。该公司承认贿赂政府官员。\n欧洲足球协会联盟（UEFA）正在调查切尔西支持者唱反犹歌曲的事件。此事发生在匈牙利上周举行的比赛期间。有人听到，一部分英国球迷所唱的歌曲中含有对犹太人的侮辱性字眼。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>31</id>
        <date>December 24, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Passengers in Britain second biggest airport are being warned of further disruption because of drones</title>
        <description>
            Police in Britain are questioning a man and a woman who have been detained on suspicion of involvement in the illegal use of drones near Gatwick, the country's second biggest airport.Passengers are being warned of further disruption because of a backlog caused by the cancellation or diversion of about a thousand flights.
        </description>
        <cover>images/merry-christmas-airport.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181224_3654677qrW.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard. Police in Britain are questioning a man and a woman who have been detained on suspicion of involvement in the illegal use of drones near Gatwick, the country's second biggest airport.Passengers are being warned of further disruption because of a backlog caused by the cancellation or diversion of about a thousand flights. Jenny Kumah is in Gatwick with the latest. They have made two arrests in connection with that criminal drone activity and they say that proactive investigations are still ongoing and they're asking the public to contact them if they have any further information. It's very busy here, lots of people making that Christmas getaway, but there are delays. The airport is hoping to run around seven hundred and fifty flights today. We know that already six have been cancelled and there are some delays on other services.\nTwo explosions in the Somali capital Mogadishu have killed at least a dozen people, including a prominent television journalist. Awil Dahir Salad was travelling in his car with other employees at the station Universal TV who were also killed. Mercy Juma reports from Nairobi. The first car bomb went off at a checkpoint near the presidential palace in Mogadishu. The second explosion took place just minutes after, covering huge parts of the capital in smoke. Police say politicians and other officials were near the site of the blasts. One of the injured is the deputy governor of Barnard region. Images circulating on social media show destroyed vehicles in debris littering the streets. Islam's terrorist group al-Shabaab has claimed responsibility for the twin blasts which have shattered nearly a month of calm in Mogadishu. a town there is often the target of attacks by al-Shabaab.\nA sixth consecutive Saturday of protests by the yellow vests movement is beginning in France. In Paris which has seen violence in recent weekends, some demonstrators gathered Montmartre and in the centre of the city. The anti-government protests started over planned rises on fuel taxes but also focus on wider living standards. This protester called on President Macron to deal with the high cost of living. The government doesn't want to help all its citizens get out of penury, help them live a dignified life, dignified, because the salaries, salaries must be salaries. You can't live on them, stop with your one hundred euros, two hundred euros. It's nothing. It's nothing. The cost of living is way up high. Bring it down so that France can succeed. A tenth person has died linked to the demonstrations after a driver crashed into the back of a lorry at a yellow vest roadblock near the southern city of Perpignan. This is the world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。英国警方正在审问一名男子和一名女子，他们因涉嫌在英国第二大的机场盖特威克机场附近非法使用无人机被捕。旅客受到警告航班将会进一步中断，因为约一千架次航班被取消或者转移导致旅客滞留。以下是简妮·库玛的报道。警方已经抓捕了两名与非法操纵无人机有关的嫌犯，他们还表示主动调查正在进行中，他们还要求了解更多信息的公众与他们联系。机场十分忙碌，很多人都在进行圣诞旅行，但是碰到了航班延迟。机场希望今天可以飞750架航班。我们了解到已经有六架次被取消，还有一些其他服务的延迟。\n索马里首都摩加迪沙的爆炸导致至少十二人死亡，其中就包括一名知名的电视节目记者。阿维尔·达希尔·萨拉德当时正与环球电视台的其他员工乘车经过这里，他们也都不幸遇难。以下麦茜·祝马在内罗毕的报道。第一枚汽车炸弹在摩加迪沙总统官邸附近的检查点爆炸，第二枚也在几分钟后爆炸，爆炸引起的烟雾覆盖了首都的大面积区域。警方称政界人士和一些官员当时正在爆炸区域附近。受伤的人群中就包括巴纳德区的副区长。社交网络的传出的图片显示汽车碎片散落在街上。伊斯兰恐怖组织索马里青年党宣称对这两次袭击负责，袭击打破了摩加迪沙一个月以来的平静局面，该镇经常遭到青年党的袭击。\n法国连续第七个周六的“黄马甲”抗议活动开始了。在最近的周末，巴黎发生了不少暴力活动，游行者聚集在蒙马特尔以及城市中心地区。反政府抗议者以计划汽油税上涨为由发动游行活动，但是他们同样关注的是生活水平的巨大差异。抗议者要求总统马克龙处理生活成本过高的问题。政府并不想帮助所有民众摆脱贫困，或是帮他们过上有尊严的生活，人们的薪资必须是实实在在的薪资。而现在的工资已不足维持生活，一两百欧元的薪资根本微不足道。生活成本现在变得太高，只有下调才能让法国变得强大。由游行导致的第十起死亡事故发生，在法国南部城市佩皮尼昂的黄马甲路障附近，一名司机与一辆货车追尾。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>32</id>
        <date>December 25, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Indonesia official said at least 43 people were killed when a tsunami struck several beaches around the Sunda Strait</title>
        <description>
            Indonesia official said at least 43 people were killed when a tsunami struck several beaches around the Sunda Strait, the stretch of water that separates the islands of Java and Sumatra.The Disaster Mitigation Agency said nearly six hundred people were injured and others are still missing. Emergency services are yet to arrive in the affected area.
        </description>
        <cover>images/indonesia-tsunami.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181225_0852289qex.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm David Harper with the BBC News.\nIndonesia official said at least 43 people were killed when a tsunami struck several beaches around the Sunda Strait, the stretch of water that separates the islands of Java and Sumatra. The Disaster Mitigation Agency said nearly six hundred people were injured and others are still missing. Emergency services are yet to arrive in the affected area. Rebecca Henschke reports from Jakarta. We're getting clearer images now of those beach towns along the coast of West Java that face onto the Sunda Strait, images of crumbled buildings along the coast there. We've also seen images from last night of these wave rushing into hotels. We are also hearing about devastation on the other side Sumatra, Lampung with some areas officials say they haven't been able to contact. So they're warning that the death toll is very much likely to rise as they continue to get more information about what happened last night.\nEmperor Akihito of Japan has broadcast his last birthday message before he steps down next April. The emperor who turned eighty-five on Sunday appeared to be overcome with emotion when he thanked the people of Japan and Empress Michiko for having supported him throughout his life on the throne. Now my journey as emperor is reaching the end. I am grateful for the many people in Japan who have accepted my status as a symbol and supported me. And I would like to also express my appreciation to the empress, who was a Japanese citizen who joined me in my life journey and for sixty long years has devoted herself to her role and the people of Japan with sincerity. The emperor said he was relieved that his reign was ending without Japan having again been engaged in a war. He expressed his hopes for the new era to start when Crown Prince Naruhito ascends the throne.\nTens of thousands of people have marched in the Serbian capital Belgrade for the third consecutive weekend to protest against what they say is the president's increasingly autocratic rule. The protesters say President Aleksandar Vucic has consolidated control over the courts and the media, which they say he uses to campaign against opponents.\nThere's been an impassioned debate in Italy's Upper House of Parliament over budget measures which were revised after objections from the European Commission. There were chaotic scenes in the Senate Chamber in Rome when opposition members demanded to see a draft text of the bill. Italy's anti-austerity coalition government has amended the document after the European Commission said it would breach the block's fiscal rules. World news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·哈珀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。印度尼西亚官方表示至少有43人在海啸中丧生，海啸袭击了巽他海峡附近的多个海滩，这片海域分割了爪洼岛和苏门答腊岛。减灾机构称近600人受伤，还有一些人失踪。救灾人员尚未到达受灾区域，以下是蕾贝卡·亨施客在雅加达的报道。我们现在得到了更加清楚的图片，图片显示了西爪哇岛沿岸的海滩城市，这里正对着巽他海峡，我们可以看到沿岸的建筑都已经倒塌。昨晚还有一些图片显示了海浪冲进酒店的场景。\n我们还听说对面的楠榜省苏门答腊也同样受灾，官员表示一些区域暂时还无法联系到。他们警告称死亡人数还有可能上升，随着获取更多关于昨晚灾难的信息。\n日本明仁天皇广播了他最后一次的生日致辞，他将于明年四月退位。明仁天皇周日迎来85岁生日，当时他情绪激动，他感谢了日本民众和皇后美智子在他在位期间的支持。现在，我作为天皇的旅程已经接近终点。我感谢日本人民接受我作为国家的象征并且一直支持我。我还想感谢皇后，她也是一名日本公民，感谢她加入了我的生命旅程并且在这60年来，为了日本人民真诚地献身于她的职责。天皇表示他很欣慰他在位期间日本没有再次参与到战争之中。他表达了对于皇太子德仁亲王即将登基的新时代的美好祝愿。\n数千人在塞尔维亚首都贝尔格莱德开始了连续第三周的游行活动，抗议他们所称的总统日益增长的独裁统治。抗议者表示总统亚历山大·武契奇加强了对于法庭和媒体的控制，用于在竞选中对抗其对手。\n激烈的讨论在意大利上议院展开，讨论内容与修改的预算措施有关，此前曾遭到欧盟委员会反对。当反对派成员要求看法案的草拟文本时，罗马的参议院一度出现混乱的场景。在欧盟委员会称其草案会违反欧盟的财政规定后，意大利的反紧缩联合政府已经修订了其财政方案。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>33</id>
        <date>December 26, 2018</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - Run Through the rain</title>
        <description>
            She had been shopping with her Mom in Wal-Mart. She must have been 6 years old, this beautiful brown haired, freckle-faced image of innocence.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/kid-jacket-mini-figure.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/run-through-the-rain.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Run through the rain**\n**雨中的记忆**\nShe had been shopping with her Mom in Wal-Mart. She must have been 6 years old, this beautiful brown haired, freckle-faced image of innocence. It was pouring outside. The kind of rain that gushes over the top of rain gutters, so much in a hurry to hit the Earth, it has no time to flow down the spout.\n她和妈妈刚在沃尔玛结束购物。这个天真的小女孩应该6岁大了，头发是美丽的棕色，脸上有雀斑。外面下着倾盆大雨。雨水溢满了檐槽，来不及排走，就迫不及待地涌涨上地面。\nWe all stood there under the awning and just inside the door of the Wal-Mart. We all waited, some patiently, others irritated, because nature messed up their hurried day. I am always mesmerized by rainfall. I get lost in the sound and sight of the heavens washing away the dirt and dust of the world. Memories of running, splashing so carefree as a child come pouring in as a welcome reprieve from the worries of my day.\n我们都站在沃尔玛门口的遮篷下。大家都在等待，有人很耐心，有人很烦躁，因为老天在给他们本已忙碌的一天添乱。雨天总引起我的遐思。我出神地听着、看着老天冲刷洗涤这世界的污垢和尘埃，孩时无忧无虑地在雨中奔跑玩水的记忆汹涌而至，暂时缓解了我一天的焦虑。\nHer voice was so sweet as it broke the hypnotic trance we were all caught in, “Mom, let's run through the rain." she said.\n小女孩甜美的声音打破了这令人昏昏欲睡的气氛，“妈妈，我们在雨里跑吧。”她说。\nWhat? Mom asked.\n“什么？”母亲问。\nLet's run through the rain! She repeated.\n“我们在雨里跑吧，”她重复。\nNo, honey. We'll wait until it slows down a bit. Mom replied.\n“不，亲爱的，我们等雨小一点再走。”母亲回答说。\nThis young child waited about another minute and repeated: "Mom, let's run through the rain."\n过了一会小女孩又说：“妈妈，我们跑出去吧。”\nWe'll get soaked if we do. Mom said.\n“这样的话我们会湿透的。”母亲说。\nNo, we won't, Mom. That's not what you said this morning, the girl said as she tugged at her Mom's arm."\n“不会的，妈妈。你今天早上不是这样说的。”小女孩一边说一边拉着母亲的手。\nThis morning? When did I say we could run through the rain and not get wet?\n“今天早上？我什么时候说过我们淋雨不会湿啊？”\nDon't you remember? When you were talking to Daddy about his cancer, you said, If God can get us through this, he can get us through anything!\n“你不记得了吗？你和爸爸谈他的癌症时，你不是说‘如果上帝让我们闯过这一关，那我们就没有什么过不去。’”\nThe entire crowd stopped dead silent. I swear you couldn't hear anything but the rain. We all stood silently. No one came or left in the next few minutes. Mom paused and thought for a moment about what she would say.\n人群一片寂静。我发誓，除了雨声，你什么都听不到。我们都静静地站着。接下来的几分钟没有一个人走动。母亲停了一下，想着应该说些什么。\nNow some would laugh it off and scold her for being silly. Some might even ignore what was said. But this was a moment of affirmation in a young child's life. Time when innocent trust can be nurtured so that it will bloom into faith. "Honey, you are absolutely right. Let's run through the rain. If get wet, well maybe we just needed washing." Mom said. Then off they ran.\n有人也许会对此一笑了之，或者责备这孩子的不懂事，有人甚至不把她的话放在心上。但这却是一个小孩子一生中需要被肯定的时候。若受到鼓舞，此时孩子单纯的信任就会发展成为坚定的信念。“亲爱的，你说得对，我们跑过去吧。如果淋湿了，那也许是因为我们的确需要冲洗一下了。”母亲说。然后她们就冲出去了。\nWe all stood watching, smiling and laughing as they darted past the cars and. They held their shopping bags over their heads just in case. They got soaked. But they were followed by a few who screamed and laughed like children all the way to their cars. And yes, I did. I ran. I got wet. I needed washing.Circumstances or people can take away your material possessions, they can take away your money, and they can take away your health. But no one can ever take away your precious memories. So, don't forget to make time and take the opportunities to make memories every day!\n我们站在那里，笑着看她们飞快地跑过停着的汽车。她们把购物袋高举过头想挡挡雨，但还是湿透了。好几个人像孩子般尖叫着，大笑着，也跟着冲了出去，奔向自己的车子。当然，我也这样做了，跑了出去，淋湿了。我也需要接受洗礼。环境或其他人可以夺去你的物质财富，抢走你的金钱，带走你的健康，但没有人可以带走你珍贵的回忆。因此，记得要抓紧时间，抓住机会每天都给自己留下一些回忆吧！\nTo everything there is a season and a time to every purpose under heaven. I hope you still take the time to run through the rain.\n世间万物皆有自己的季节，做任何事情也有一个恰当的时机。希望你有机会在雨中狂奔一回。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>34</id>
        <date>December 27, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Trade unions and professional associations in Sudan have called for a general strike</title>
        <description>
            Trade unions and professional associations in Sudan have called for a general strike today to demand the resignation of President al-Bashir and the formation of a transitional government.
        </description>
        <cover>images/sudan-strike.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1226_5522282SDR.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News.\nThe Iranian President has told Parliament his country has missed an opportunity to exploit the United States international isolation. Hassan Rouhani spoke as he presented a forty-seven-billion-dollar budget, the first such measure since the reintroduction of US sanctions on Iran. Shihab Mosbut has this report.\nIn a rowdy and often interrupted address, President Hassan Rouhani said corruption and nepotism at the highest levels of society meant Iran had failed to take advantage of American isolationism. He said the reform with banking, tax and economic infrastructure were essential before Iran could advance its cause internationally. Iran, he said, must harness the strength of its oil industry to counter America sanctions.\nThe British government has confirmed that a British-Iranian academic who has spent eight months in jail in Iran has been released. Abbas Edalat, who is a professor of computer science and mathematics, has returned to the UK. He was arrested by Iran's revolutionary guards in Tehran in April. An Iranian news agency alleged at the time that he was a British spy.\nPresident Erdogan of Turkey has invited Donald Trump to visit next year as the two men attempt to coordinate a pullout of US troops from Syria. Key Middle Eastern powers are seeking to capitalize on America's withdrawal from Syria. Sebastian Usher assesses the situation on the ground.\nThe Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan is biding his time, but remains clear in his determination to force Kurdish militias out of Northern Syria. On the ground, militias once united and rebellion now ally to Turkey are reported to have deployed closer to the town of Manbij, while more Turkish troops have moved to the Syrian border in recent days. US soldiers are still in Manbij for now in support of a Kurdish-led alliance they've backed in the battle against IS. The Kurdish fighters were meant to have withdrawn under a deal agreed between the US and Turkey but have yet to leave. President Erdogan says he won't strike against them until the US pulls out.\nTrade unions and professional associations in Sudan have called for a general strike today to demand the resignation of President al-Bashir and the formation of a transitional government. They are planning a march to the presidential palace in Khartoum. Doctors went on strike on Monday as part of the protests sparked last week by anger about the rising price of bread and fuel. On Monday, President Bashir promised what he called real reforms to improve the quality of life of the Sudanese people.\nThis is the world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n伊朗总统告诉国会，伊朗错过了利用美国国际孤立政策的机会。哈桑·鲁哈尼发表讲话的同时提交了一份470亿美元的预算，这是美国重新对伊朗实施制裁之后伊朗发布的首项措施。以下是什哈卜·莫斯巴特的报道。\n在环境喧闹并多次被打断的讲话中，哈桑·鲁哈尼总统表示社会最高层的腐败和裙带关系表明伊朗没能利用好美国的孤立政策。他表示在伊朗向国际化推进之前，对银行、税收和经济结构进行改革是必要的。他还表示伊朗必须要利用其石油产业的优势以对抗美国的制裁。\n英国政府已确认一名在伊朗监狱中度过8个月的英国籍伊朗学者现已被释放。阿巴斯·艾德勒是一名计算机科学和数学教授，他现在已经返回英国。他于四月在德黑兰被伊朗革命卫队逮捕。当时一家伊朗新闻机构称他是一名英国间谍。\n土耳其总统埃尔多安邀请了特朗普明年来访，两人计划共同协调美国从叙利亚撤军相关事宜。中东地区的主要力量都寻求利用美国从叙利亚撤军这一机会。以下是塞巴斯汀·厄舍对该事件的实地报道。\n土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安正在耐心等待，但是对于将库尔德武装赶出叙利亚北部的决心十分明确。在当地，据报道之前联合起来的民兵组织以及现在和土耳其结盟的反对派武装都在向曼比杰靠近，而近些天以来也有更多的土耳其军队向叙利亚边境移动。美国士兵仍在曼比杰支持库尔德领导的武装联盟，在与IS的战斗他们支持该武装联盟。库尔德武装本应该按照美国和土耳其的协议从该地区撤出，但仍未离开。埃尔多安总统表示在美国撤军之前不会向他们开火。\n苏丹工会和专业协会今天号召民众举行了一次大罢工，以要求巴希尔总统辞职并组建过渡政府。他们计划在位于喀土穆的总统官邸游行。上周因面包和燃料价格上涨引发了愤怒的游行活动，周一医生们也加入到了罢工中来。周一，总统巴希尔承诺将进行所谓的实质性改革以改善苏丹人民的生活质量。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>35</id>
        <date>December 28, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - The earthquake in Italy damaged nearby homes and buildings</title>
        <description>
            Reports from Italy say ten people have been injured following an earthquake in the area around Mount Etna in Sicily, the most active volcano in Europe.
        </description>
        <cover>images/earthquake-damage.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181227_2931954Svd.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Ally McHugh with the BBC News. The electoral commission in the Democratic Republic of Congo says it's delaying Sunday's presidential election in three cities until March due to insecurity and an outbreak of the Ebola virus. The decision in effect cancels the vote in Beni and Butembo in North Kivu province and Yumbi in the west of the country because the new president is due to be sworn in by the middle of January. Here's Will Ross. The Congolese electoral commission says it's taken this decision to save lives. There'll be no voting until March in Beni and Butembo in the east of the country because it says there would be a risk the Ebola virus could spread if people travel to the polling stations. A statement also said any election there would provide an opportunity for armed groups to carry out attacks. The timing of this announcement is surprising, considering the Ebola outbreak in eastern Congo began in August, and the numerous rebel groups have been active there for years. Perhaps less surprising is the decision to delay the vote in Yumbi in the west, where more than one hundred people were killed in ethnic clashes earlier this month.\nA UN-led ceasefire monitoring team is reported to have met for the first time in the Yemeni port of Hodeida. Details of what was discussed are yet to emerge. The team is expected to work to secure a shaky truce in the city. Alan Johnston has the details. The monitoring team is being headed by a UN-appointed retired Dutch general, and it includes representatives of both the government and the rebels. The two sides recently agreed to a truce in Hodeida, but sporadic fighting has continued. Now the ceasefire monitoring committee is reported to have held its first meeting. Its efforts to make the truce work will be hugely important. Hodeida is a key link in the effort to ship food aid into Yemen where millions of people are threatened by starvation.\nReports from Italy say ten people have been injured following an earthquake in the area around Mount Etna in Sicily, the most active volcano in Europe. James Reynolds has this report. The earthquake hit the slopes of Mount Etna at around twenty past three in the morning. It damaged nearby homes and buildings. In the village of Fleri, an eighty-year-old man had to be rescued from his home. Some decided to take shelter in their cars or in local gyms, anywhere just to be safe. In recent days, scientists recorded more than a hundred tremors, causing the authorities to restrict flights to the regional airports in the city of Catania. James Reynolds reporting. This is the world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是艾琳·麦克尤，欢迎收听BBC新闻。刚果民主共和国的选举委员会宣布，将原定于周日在三个城市举行的大选推迟到3月，原因是不安全因素以及埃博拉病毒的爆发。该决定实际上取消了在贝尼、北基伍省的布滕博以及西部的永比地区的选举活动，因为新总统将会在一月中旬宣誓就职。以下是威尔·罗斯的报道。刚果选举委员会表示采取该措施是为了挽救生命。三月份之前贝尼，以及东部城市布滕博不会举行选举，因为他们担心人们前往投票站会有传播埃博拉的风险。一份声明也表示该地区的选举活动将会给武装分子发动袭击提供机会。该决定宣布的时机令人意外，因为埃博拉病毒8月份就在刚果东部爆发了，另外多个反叛组织已经在该地区活跃了多年。在西部的永比地区推迟选举就没有那么令人意外，因为本月初这里有一百多人在种族冲突中被杀。\n据报道，一个联合国主导的停火监督小组已经在也门港口城市荷台达举行了首次会议。会议讨论的细节尚未公布。该小组有望保证荷台达脆弱的停火协议继续维持，以下是艾伦·约翰斯顿的报道。该监督小组由联合国任命的荷兰退休将军带领，包括政府和反对派双方的代表。双方近期同意在荷台达停火，但是仍有零星的战斗爆发。现在，据报道停火监督委员会已经举行了第一次会议。他们为停火做出的努力将会至关重要。荷台达是将救援食物送往也门地区的关键节点，在也门有数百万人正受到饥饿的威胁。\n意大利的报道称有10人在西西里岛埃特纳火山附近的地震中受伤，该火山也是欧洲最活跃的火山。以下是詹姆斯·雷诺兹的报道。该地震在早上3:20袭击了埃特纳火山的山坡，导致附近的居民房屋建筑受损。在弗莱里村，一名80岁当地老人现已从家中被救出。一些人决定去车中或者是当地的体育馆等安全的地方避难。最近几天以来，科学家记录到了100多次地震，导致政府限制了飞往卡特尼亚市机场的航班。以上是詹姆斯·雷诺兹的报道。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>36</id>
        <date>December 29, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - President Trump has used a surprise Christmas visit to US troops in Iraq</title>
        <description>
            President Trump has used a surprise Christmas visit to US troops in Iraq to defend his decision to pull American forces out of Syria.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-visit-troops.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1228_31491492Nj.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News.\nPresident Trump has used a surprise Christmas visit to US troops in Iraq to defend his decision to pull American forces out of Syria. Mr. Trump said the withdrawal would be gradual.\nThere will be a strong, deliberate and orderly withdrawal of US forces from Syria, very deliberate, very orderly, while maintaining the US presence in Iraq to prevent an ISIS resurgence and to protect US interests, and also to always watch very closely over any potential reformation of ISIS and also to watch over Iran.\nDuring his visit to an airbase west of Baghdad, President Trump spoke to the Iraqi Prime Minister over the telephone and invited him to Washington.\nShares in Tokyo have closed nearly four percent higher following earlier gains in New York. US shares bounced back after steep falls before Christmas. Kim Gittleson reports.\nAfter suffering their worst weekly performance in a decade, US shares made a roaring recovery, which once more had a knock-on effect on markets around the world. Investors seemed to shake off their pre-holiday jitters after positive US retail sales data soothe concerns about a slowdown in US economic activity. That push shares in companies like Amazon higher even amid thin trading volumes during the post Christmas week. The question of course, is whether this is a one-off rally or something that will be sustained into the New Year. The Dow-Jones Industrial Average would need to rise over eighteen hundred points over the next two days in order to end 2018 in the black.\nPolice in the Democratic Republic of Congo have fired tear gas at crowds protesting against the decision to further delay the presidential election. A BBC correspondent in the city of Goma said demonstrators are being dispersed. The vote which was due to take place on Sunday has now been postponed until March in three areas of the country.\nJapan has executed two inmates on death row. The Justice Minister said they were hanged at a detention center in the city of Osaka. The two men were convicted for the strangling of an investment firm executive and an employee thirty years ago. The hangings bring the total number of executions in Japan this year to fifteen. Japan has about one hundred death row convicts.\nThe US pop star Miley Cyrus has confirmed that she has married the Australian actor Liam Hemsworth, sharing images of their wedding on social media. The couple met nearly a decade ago on the set of the film, The Last Song.\nBBC world news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔•努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n特朗普在圣诞期间意外现身伊拉克访问驻地美军，以此捍卫他从叙利亚撤军的决定。特朗普表示撤军将会循序渐进地进行。\n从叙利亚撤军将会是一次大规模的、经过深思熟虑的并且是有条不紊的行动。该行动将非常谨慎有序地进行，同时也会保留美国在伊拉克的力量以防止ISIS死灰复燃并保护美国的权益，还将一直密切关注ISIS任何可能的复苏迹象并监督伊朗。在特朗普访问巴格达空军基地期间，特朗普总统与伊拉克总理通话并邀请他访问华盛顿。\n受早前纽约股市上涨推动，东京股票收盘上涨近4%。美股在圣诞节前暴跌后出现反弹。以下是金•吉特森的报道。\n在度过了十年中最糟糕的一周后，美股现在实现了大幅回升，又一次对全世界股市产生了影响。美国零售数据回升，缓解了人们对于美国经济活动放缓的担忧，也让投资者在圣诞节前松了一口气，这也促使亚马逊等公司股价走高，尽管圣诞节后一周交易量不高。当然问题是，此次股市回升是暂时性的，还是会延续至新的一年。在未来两天内，道琼斯工业指数增长需要超过1800点才能在2018年年底实现盈利。\n刚果民主共和国警方向抗议进一步推迟总统大选的游行民众投掷了催泪弹。戈马市的一名BBC记者表示游行者正在被驱散。在该国的三个区域内，原定于周日举行的选举现已被推迟到了3月。\n日本现已处决了两名死刑犯，日本法务大臣表示他们在大阪的一个拘留所被处以绞刑。两人因30年前勒死一家投资公司的一名管理人员和一名员工被判处死刑。加上本次绞刑，日本今年实施死刑总次数达到15次。日本约有100名死刑犯。\n美国女星麦莉•赛勒斯已证实与澳大利亚演员利亚姆•海姆斯沃斯完婚，并在社交媒体上分享了他们的结婚照。两人约10年前在电影《最后一支歌》片场相识。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>37</id>
        <date>December 30, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Russia says it’s acquired a new type of nuclear capable hypersonic missile</title>
        <description>
            The Russia President Vladimir Putin said the weapon could penetrate any existing or next-generation missile defense system. Moscow says the Avangard missile launched in the Ural Mountains hit a target 6,000 kilometers away.
        </description>
        <cover>images/russia-nuclear-missile.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1229_5814166mBT.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News with Kris Barrow.\nPresident Trump has made a Christmas visit to US troops in Iraq, his first trip to see soldiers under his command in a combat zone. He comes days after his Defense Secretary Jim Mattis resigned in a dispute over the President’s decision to pull US forces out of Syria and look at a slash of the American contingent in Afghanistan.\nRussia says it’s acquired a new type of nuclear capable hypersonic missile. The Russia President Vladimir Putin said the weapon could penetrate any existing or next-generation missile defense system. Moscow says the Avangard missile launched in the Ural Mountains hit a target 6,000 kilometers away.\nSunday’s presidential election in the Democratic Republic of Congo has been postponed until March in three areas. The authorities claimed insecurity under an outbreak of Ebola for the decision.\nThe electoral authorities in Afghanistan have delayed next year’s presidential poll by three months. Sources have told the BBC that many potential candidates have been unable to meet registration requirements, and extreme weather meant their teams could not be ready for the scheduled vote in April.\nA father whose dead son has become a focus for anti-government protests in Bosnia-Herzegovina has been released after a night in police custody. Lawyers for Davor Dragicevic said police had no grounds for detaining him.\nThe price of gold has hit a six-month high amid fears of slowing global growth and economic volatility, especially in the United States. Confidence in US markets has been hit by a string of concerns, including the partial government shutdown caused by President Trump’s dispute with Congress over funding for his planned border wall.\nA French adventurer has set off to cross the Atlantic Ocean in a barrel-shaped capsule, using ocean currents alone to propel him. 71-year-old Jean Jacques Savin left the Spanish Island of El Hierro and hopes to reach the Caribbean in some 4,500 kilometers away in as little as three months.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nKris Barrow为您播报BBC新闻。\n圣诞节期间，特朗普总统访问了美国驻伊军队，这是他首次看望战区的美国士兵。在此数天前，国防部部长吉姆·马蒂斯离任。因为有争议是关于特朗普决定撤出美国驻叙利亚军队，并且意图削减美国驻阿富汗士兵。\n俄罗斯称其已获得一种新型高超音速核导弹。俄罗斯总统普京表示，该导弹可以穿透任何现有的以及下一代导弹防御系统。俄罗斯政府表示，该导弹，即先锋高超音速核导弹，已在乌拉尔山脉试飞，可以将目标击飞6000公里远。\n预计于周日举行刚果民主共和国总统大选已在3个地区被推迟到了明年3月。当局表示存在不安全隐患，因为有可能爆发埃博拉病毒，所以出此下策。\n阿富汗选举当局将明年的总统票选推迟了3个月。知情人士在接受BBC采访时表示，很多可能当选的候选人无法满足登记要求。而寒冷的天气也意味着选举团队起码要等到4月才能开启票选。\n一位男孩成为波斯尼亚―黑塞哥维亚反政府抗议的焦点。其父亲在警局被监禁一夜后得以释放。这位父亲名为Davor Dragicevic，其律师表示，警方没有理由监禁他。\n黄金价格已达过去半年来的新高，虽然现在有人担心会出现全球经济放缓与经济波动，尤其是美国的经济放缓与波动。外界对美国市场的信心受到了冲击，原因有多个。其中一个就是美国政府部分停摆。停摆是因为特朗普总统与美国国会之间出现争议，争议的主题是是否要为特朗普计划建造的边境墙提供资金。\n某法国探险家已出发，准备跨越大西洋。他乘坐的是一个桶状的容器，只靠洋流的作用来提供推力。今年71岁的他名为让·雅克，他离开了西班牙的耶罗岛，希望能够用3个月的时间抵达4500公里外的加勒比。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>38</id>
        <date>December 31, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - King Salman of Saudi Arabia has replaced his foreign minister Adel al-Jubeir</title>
        <description>
            King Salman of Saudi Arabia has replaced his foreign minister Adel al-Jubeir as part of a cabinet reshuffle.The move follows prolonged international criticism of the authorities in Riyadh sparked by the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi.
        </description>
        <cover>images/saudi-arabia-minister.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1230_1520865pAT.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Jonathan Izard.\nUnited Arab Emirates says it will reopen its embassy in Syria, providing a diplomatic boost for President Bashar al-Assad after more than 7 years of civil war. It's the latest sign that Syria is reconnecting with its neighbors.\nKing Salman of Saudi Arabia has replaced his foreign minister Adel al-Jubeir as part of a cabinet reshuffle. The move follows prolonged international criticism of the authorities in Riyadh sparked by the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi.\nPolice in the Democratic Republic of Congo have fired into the air and used tear gas against protesters angered by the exclusion of their regions from Sunday's planned presidential vote. Demonstrators in the eastern city of Beni attacked a transit area near an Ebola treatment center. The Ebola outbreak was one of the reasons given by officials for further delays in some regions.\nThe US senate is due to convene shortly as a damaging shutdown of parts of government continues for a sixth day. President Trump has criticized the democrats for blocking his amendment for the budget bill which will add $5 billion to build a wall along the border with Mexico. Analysts say the standoff is not likely to be resolved before the New Year.\nThere've been significant falls again on US stock markets as political and economic uncertainty hits confidence among investors. The Dow Jones Index was down by more than 2.5%, one point. Market volatility has been fueled by concerns about US government shutdown as well as fears of a faltering global economy.\nThe US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo will travel to Columbia next week to discuss the economic situation in neighboring Venezuela. About 1 million Venezuelans have crossed to Columbia over the past three years as the crisis has worsened. The Columbian president said he would meet Mr. Pompeo next Wednesday.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nJonathan Izard为您播报BBC新闻。\n阿联酋表示其将在叙利亚重新开放大使馆，为巴沙尔·阿萨德总统提供外交支持。在此之前，内战已进行了7年多。这是最近的迹象，可以表明叙利亚正在与其邻国联系。\n沙特国王萨尔曼撤掉了外长阿德尔·朱拜尔，这是沙特内阁大洗牌的部分举措。此举之前，国际上一直在抨击沙特政府。其导火索是沙特记者贾马尔·哈沙吉遭遇谋杀。\n刚果警方向空中鸣枪，并对抗议者使用催泪弹。激怒抗议者走上街头的原因是他们所在的地区被剥夺了周日参加总统大选投票的权利。刚果东部城市贝尼的抗议者们袭击了某埃博拉治疗中心附近的中间集结区。\n美国参议院不久后将召开会议，因为美国政府的部分机关遭遇停摆，影响不利，目前已经是第六天了。特朗普总统谴责民主党人，称是后者阻碍了自己的预算提案修正案，该修正案就为其建造美墨边境墙补给额外的50亿美元。分析师表示，这种僵持的局面可能新年之后才能解决。\n美国股市再次暴跌，因为政治和经济领域的不确定性让投资者丧失了信心。道琼斯指数下降了2.5%，即一个点。市场的波动是因有人担心美国政府停摆以及全球经济波动而造成的。\n美国国务卿迈克·蓬佩奥下周将前往哥伦比亚，以讨论邻国委内瑞拉的经济形势问题。近100万委内瑞拉人跋山涉水来到哥伦比亚，这是过去3年来的统计数字。他们逃离的原因是本国危机逐渐恶化。哥伦比亚总统表示其将于下周三与蓬佩奥会晤。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>39</id>
        <date>January 1, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - A special letter</title>
        <description>
            Dear World:My son starts school today.It's going to be strange and new to him for a while, and I wish you would sort of treat him gently.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/pen-letter.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/a-special-letter.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**A special letter**\n**一封特殊的信**\nDear World:\n亲爱的世界：\nMy son starts school today.\n我的儿子今天就要开始上学读书了。\nIt's going to be strange and new to him for a while, and I wish you would sort of treat him gently.\n一时之间，他会感觉陌生而又新鲜。我希望你能待他温柔一些。\nYou see, up to now, he's been king of the roost.\n你明白，到现在为止，他一直是家中的小皇帝。\nHe's been boss of the backyard.\n一直是后院的王者。\nI have always been around to repair his wounds, and to make him calm.\n我一直在他身旁，忙着为他治疗伤口，哄他开心。\nBut now--things are going to be different.\n但是现在--一切都将不同了。\nThis morning, he's going to walk down the front steps, wave his hand and start on his great adventure that will probably include wars and tragedy and sorrow.\n今天清晨，他就要走下前门的楼梯，冲我挥手，然后开始他的伟大的历险征程，其间或许有争斗、不幸以及伤痛。\nTo live his life in the world he has to live in will require faith and love and courage.\n既然活在这个世上，他就需要信念、爱心和勇气。\nSo, World, I wish you would sort of take him by his young hand and teach him the things he will have to know.\n所以，世界啊，我希望你能够时不时握住他稚嫩的小手，传授他所应当知晓的事情。\nTeach him - but gently, if you can.\n教育他吧--而如果可能的话，温柔一些。\nTeach him that for every scoundrel there is a hero; that for every crooked politician there is a dedicated leader; that for every enemy there is a friend.\n教他知道，每有恶人之地，必有豪杰所在；每有奸诈小人，必有献身义士；每见一敌人，必有一友在侧。\nTeach him the wonders of books.\n教他感受书本的神奇魅力。\nGive him quiet time to ponder the eternal mystery of birds in the sky, bees in the sun, and flowers on the green hill.\n给他时间静思大自然中亘古绵传之奥秘：空中的飞鸟，日光里的蜜蜂，青山上的簇簇繁花。\nTeach him it is far more honorable to fail than to cheat.\n教他知道，失败远比欺骗更为光荣。\nTeach him to have faith in his own ideas, even if everyone tells him they are wrong.\n教他坚定自我的信念，哪怕人人予以否认。\nTeach him to sell his brawn and brains to the highest bidder, but never to put a price on his heart and soul.\n教他可以最高价付出自己的精力和智慧，但绝不可出卖良心和灵魂。\nTeach him to close his ears to a howling mob...and to stand and fight if he thinks he's right.\n教他置暴徒的喧嚣于度外……并在自觉正确之时挺身而战。\nTeach him gently, World, but don't coddle him, because only the test of fire makes fine steel.\n温柔地教导他吧，世界，但是不要放纵他，因为只有烈火的考验才能炼出真钢。\nThis is a big order, World, but see what you can do.\n这一要求甚高，世界，但是请尽你所能。\nHe's such a nice little fellow.\n他是一个如此可爱的小家伙。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>40</id>
        <date>January 2, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - Eternal Promise</title>
        <description>
            Dear World:My son starts school today.It's going to be strange and new to him for a while, and I wish you would sort of treat him gently.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/school-earthquake-ruins.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/eternal-promise.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Eternal Promise**\n**永恒的承诺**\nIn 1989 an 8.2 earthquake almost flattened America, killing over 30,000 people in less than four minutes. In the midst of utter devastation and chaos, a father left his wife safely at home and rushed to the school where his son was supposed to be, only to discover that the building was as flat as a pancake.\n1989年，一次8.2级的地震几乎铲平美国，在短短不到4分钟的时间里，夺去了3万多人的生命！在彻底的破坏与混乱之中，有位父亲将他的妻子在家里安顿好后，跑到他儿子就读的学校，而触目所见，却是被夷为平地的校园。\nAfter the unforgettably initial shock, he remembered the promise he had made to his son: "No matter what, I’ll always be there for you!" And tears began to fill his eyes. As he looked at the pile of ruins that once was the school, it looked hopeless, but he kept remembering his commitment to his son.\n看到这令人伤心的一幕，他想起了曾经对儿子所作的承诺："不论发生什么事，我都会在你身边。"至此，父亲热泪满眶。目睹曾经的学校成为了一堆瓦砾，真叫人绝望。但父亲的脑中仍然牢记着他对儿子的诺言。\nHe began to direct his attention towards where he walked his son to class at school each morning. Remembering his son s classroom would be in the back right corner of the building; he rushed there and started digging through the ruins.\n他开始努力回忆每天早上送儿子上学的必经之路，终于记起儿子的教室应该就在那幢建筑物后面，位于右边的角落里，他跑到那儿，开始在碎石砾中挖掘，搜寻儿子的下落。\nAs he was digging, other helpless parents arrived, clutching their hearts, saying: "My son!" "My daughter!" Other well meaning parents tried to pull him off what was left of the school, saying: "It s too late! They’re all dead! You can’t help! Go home! Come on, face reality, there s nothing you can do!"\n当这位父亲正在挖掘时，其他束手无策的学生家长赶到现场，揪心地叫着："我的儿子呀！" "我的女儿呀！"一些好意的家长试图把这位父亲劝离现场，告诉他"一切都太迟了！"他们全死了！"这样做没用的"，"回去吧，这样做只会使事情更糟"。\nTo each parent he responded with one line: "Are you going to help me now?" And then he continued to dig for his son, stone by stone. The fire chief showed up and tried to pull him off the school s ruins saying, "Fires are breaking out, explosions are happening everywhere. You’re in danger. We’ll take care of it. Go home." To which this loving, caring American father asked, "Are you going to help me now?"\n面对种种劝告，这位父亲的回答只有一句话："你们愿意帮我吗？"然后继续进行挖掘工作，在废墟中寻找他的儿子。消防队长出现了，他也试图把这位父亲劝走，对他说："火灾频现，四处都在发生爆炸，你在这里太危险了，这边的事我们会处理，你回家吧！"对此，这位慈爱、关切的父亲仍然回答："你们要帮我吗？"\nThe police came and said, "You’re angry, anxious and it s over. You’re endangering others. Go home. We’ll handle it!" To which he replied, "Are you going to help me now?" No one helped.Courageously he went on alone because he needed to know for himself: "Is my boy alive or is he dead?" He dug for eight hours...12 hours...24 hours...36 hours...then, in the 38th hour, he pulled back a large stone and heard his son s voice. He screamed his son s name, "ARMAND!" He heard back, "Dad!?! It s me, Dad! I told the other kids not to worry. I told them that if you were alive, you d save me and when you saved me, they d be saved. You promised, No matter what happens, I’ll always be there for you! You did it, Dad!" "What s going on in there? How is it?" the father asked.\n警察赶到现场，对他说："你现在又气又急，该结束了，你在危及他人，回家吧！我们会处理一切的。"这位父亲依旧回答："你们愿意帮我吗？" 然而，人们无动于衷。为了弄清楚儿子是死是活，这位父亲独自一人鼓起勇气，继续进行他的工作。他挖掘了8小时，--12小时，24小时，36小时--38小时后，父亲推开了一块巨大的石头，听到了儿子的声音。父亲尖叫着："阿曼德！"儿子的回音听到了："爸爸吗？是我，爸，我告诉其他的小朋友不要着急。我告诉他们如果你活着，你会来救我的。如果我获救了，他们也就获救了。你答应过我， 不论发生什么，我永远都会在你的身边， 你做到了，爸！""你那里的情况怎样？"父亲问。\nThere are 14 of us left out of 33, Dad. We’re scared, hungry, thirsty and thankful you re here. When the building collapsed, it made a triangle, and it saved us.\n我们有33个，只有14个活着。爸，我们好害怕，又渴又饿，谢天谢地，你在这儿。教室倒塌时，刚好形成一个三角形的洞，救了我们。\nCome out, boy!\n快出来吧！儿子！\nNo, Dad! Let the other kids out first, cause I know you ll get me! No matter what happens, I know you’ll always be there for me!\n不，爸，让其他小朋友先出来吧！因为我知道你会接我的！不管发生什么事，我知道你永远都会来到我的身边！
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>41</id>
        <date>January 3, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Presidential election polling stations have opened in Congo</title>
        <description>
            Polling stations have opened in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo for the country's long delayed presidential election.It could result in the country's first peaceful transfer of power.
        </description>
        <cover>images/congo-election.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0102_2509557LDq.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Nick Kelly with the BBC News.\nPolling stations have opened in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo for the country's long delayed presidential election. It could result in the country's first peaceful transfer of power. President Joseph Kabila is stepping down after seventeen years. From Kinshasa, Louise Dewast reports.\nAs polling stations open across this vast country, almost the size of Western Europe, tensions are high. It's still unclear if all polling stations are ready. For the first time, voting will be done using electronic voting machines despite concerns they could be used to rig the vote in favor of the ruling party's candidate. The front runners are Emmanuel Ramazani Shadary, a close ally of President Kabila, and two opposition candidates Martin Fayulu and Felix Tshisekedi.\nBangladesh is holding a general election with more than a hundred million people eligible to vote. Heavy security is in place after a campaign marred by violence and allegations of a crackdown against the opposition. The Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina is seeking a third successive term. Yogita Limaye is in Dhaka.\nEven before eight am when polls opened, there were lots of people waiting outside. It is still largely a paper ballot, so it's on a piece of paper that they will make their choice. But for the first time in a national election in Bangladesh, electronic voting machines are also being used in six constituencies. In the run-up to this election, we've seen several violent instances, several people being killed, scores being injured. And so there's a heavy security deployment all across the city as well as the country and in fact, even mobile internet has been slowed down for security reasons.\nThe Colombian Foreign Minister Carlos Holmes Trujillo says his government is investigating a possible plot to assassinate the President Ivan Duque. He said investigators were trying to establish where the three Venezuelans arrested earlier this month in Colombia with military weapons are connected to the alleged plot.\nFor several months, intelligence services have been investigating possible attacks on the life of the president. On top of this, we have the recent capture of three Venezuelan citizens who were found with weapons of war. This increases the concerns of the authorities in this matter.\nPresident Duque is due to meet the US Secretary of State next week to discuss escalating tensions with Venezuela. He's asked countries not to recognize the new government of the Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼克•凯利，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n刚果民主共和国东部的总统选举投票站已经开放，该国总统选举被长期推延。这可能将是该国权力的首次和平移交。总统约瑟夫•卡比拉在执政17年后即将下台。以下是路易斯•德瓦斯特在金沙萨的报道。\n刚果民主共和国幅员辽阔，接近整个西欧的大小，随着投票点的开放，紧张气氛也日益增加。现在还不清楚是否所有的选举点都做好了准备。在投票中将首次使用电子投票机，虽然有人担心这些机器会被用来操纵投票，从而为执政党候选人谋利。得票领先的候选人包括伊曼纽尔•拉马扎尼•沙迪尔，他是总统卡比拉的亲密盟友，以及两名反对党候选人马丁•法尤鲁和费利克斯•齐塞克迪。\n孟加拉国正在举行大选，有资格投票的选民超过一亿。因为此前选举期间的暴力活动和以及对反对党的镇压活动，严格的安保措施已经就位。总理谢赫•哈西娜正在寻求第三届连任。以下是尤吉塔•利玛耶在达卡的报道。\n在早上8点投票开始之前，就有很多人在外等候。投票形式绝大部分都是纸面选票，也就是说人们将会在纸上做出自己的选择。但是在孟加拉的全国大选中，电子投票机也首次在六个选区使用。在选举的准备阶段，我们看到了一些暴力事件，数人被杀，多人受伤。所以现在有大量的安全力量被部署在该市以及全国，甚至移动互联网都因安全因素而降速。\n哥伦比亚外长卡洛斯•奥尔梅斯•特鲁希略表示政府正在调查疑似密谋刺杀总统伊万•杜克一案。他表示调查人员正在尝试找到本月初在哥伦比亚逮捕的三名持有军方武器的委内瑞拉人与这起刺杀阴谋的联系。\n几个月以来，情报人员一直在调查有可能对总统发起的刺杀行动，此外我们还逮捕了三名携带战争武器的委内瑞拉市民。这也增加了政府对该事件的担忧。\n总统杜克将于下周会见美国国务卿，讨论与委内瑞拉不断升级的紧张关系。他呼吁各国不要认可以尼古拉斯•马杜拉为总统的委内瑞拉新政府。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>42</id>
        <date>January 3, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - A box full of kisses</title>
        <description>
            The story goes that some time ago, a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper. Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/a-box-full-of-kisses.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/a-box-full-of-kisses.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**A box full of kisses**\n**装满吻的盒子**\nThe story goes that some time ago, a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper. Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree. Nevertheless, the little girl brought the gift to her father the next morning and said, "This is for you, Daddy.”\n有这样一个故事，爸爸因为三岁的女儿浪费了一卷金色的包装纸而惩罚了她。家里很缺钱，当孩子想要用包装纸装饰一个挂在圣诞树上的盒子时，爸爸生气了。然而，第二天早上小女孩把盒子作为礼物送给了爸爸，“这是给你的，爸爸。”\nThe man was embarrassed by his earlier overreaction, but his anger flared again when he found out the box was empty. He yelled at her, stating, "Don't you know, when you give someone a present, there is supposed to be something inside? The little girl looked up at him with tears in her eyes and cried, "Oh, Daddy, it's not empty at all. I blew kisses into the box. They're all for you, Daddy."\n女儿的这个行为让爸爸感到尴尬。但是当他发现盒子是空的时候，他的怒火再一次燃烧了。他对女儿喊道，“难道你不知道给别人礼物的时候，里面应该放有东西吗？”多女孩抬头看着父亲，眼里含着泪水，“爸爸，盒子不是空的。我把吻放在了盒子里，都是给你的，爸爸。”\nThe father was crushed. He put his arms around his little girl, and he begged for her forgiveness. Only a short time later, an accident took the life of the child. It is also told that her father kept that gold box by his bed for many years and, whenever he was discouraged, he would take out an imaginary kiss and remember the love of the child who had put it there.\n爸爸感动极了，他搂住女儿，恳请她的原谅。之后不久，一场事故夺走了小女孩的生命。据说，父亲便将那个小金盒子放在床头，一直陪伴着他的余生。无论何时他感到气馁或者遇到难办的事情，他就会打开礼盒，取出一个假想的吻，记起漂亮女儿给予了自己特殊的爱。\nIn a very real sense, each one of us, as humans beings, have been given a gold container filled with unconditional love and kisses... from our children, family members, friends, and God. There is simply no other possession, anyone could hold, more precious than this.\n从一个非常真实的意义上说，我们每个人都被赠与过一个无形的金色礼盒，那里面装满了来自子女，家人，朋友及上帝无条件的爱与吻。人们所能拥有的最珍贵的礼物莫过于此了。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>43</id>
        <date>January 4, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - New Horizons probe has successfully encountered the most distant object in the solar system</title>
        <description>
            Scientists with the American Space Agency NASA believed their New Horizons probe has successfully encountered the most distant object ever to be explored in the solar system. The robotic craft was due to fly past the icy massive Ultima Thule.
        </description>
        <cover>images/new-horizons-probe.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190103_0605747LEa.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Debbie Russ with the BBC News. Scientists with the American Space Agency NASA believed their New Horizons probe has successfully encountered the most distant object ever to be explored in the solar system. The robotic craft was due to fly past the icy massive Ultima Thule. The scientists cheered to mark the moment, but it will take several hours for the probe to communicate with home. Planetary scientist Dr. Carly Howett of the Southwest Research Institute in Colorado is waiting for the information to come back from the probe. It's traveling so fast that we are, entire encounter is about three hours long. The target is very small. Ultima Thule, we think is somewhere between sort of probably around twenty miles across, but it's very far from earth. It's about 6.5 billion kilometers. So this is exciting because it's exploring something that we really have never seen before. This is an object like we've seen never seen. So it's true exploration at its finest. So we're waiting with bated breath for the data to come down.\nThe North Korean leader Kim Jong-un has warned that he may change his approach to relations with the United States if it maintains sanctions. Laura Bicker reports. Sitting in his office flanked by huge portraits of his father and grandfather, Kim Jong-un made his annual televised address to the North Korean people. But at the end, there was a message for Donald Trump. Mr. Kim said that if Washington continued with its pressure and sanctions on Pyongyang and misjudged his country's patience, then he would have no choice but to seek a new path. This may mean that North Korea is waiting for the US to act in 2019, and unless it does, the current pause on nuclear weapons testing could be over.\nThe new Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro will be sworn in later today. The far-right politician has promised to immediately relax gun laws. Katy Watson has this report from the capital Brasilia. Today marks a new direction for Brazil, but the political path of this country is uncertain. Mr. Bolsonaro campaigned as an outsider, pledging to drain the swamp of corrupt politicians. For those who voted him in, he represents change. People here are fed up with the political establishment, many of whom have been embroiled in corruption scandals in the past few years. While financial markets are hopeful, he could help turn around Brazil's troubled economy, many fear his conservative politics and aggressive attitude will only worsen the lives of poorer and more vulnerable Brazilians. BBC News.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是黛比·罗斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。美国宇航局NASA的科学家称新视野号探测器已经成功飞掠太阳系目前已被探索的最远天体。该探测器将会飞掠冰冷天体“天涯海角”。科学家也在庆祝这一激动人心的时刻，但是探测器还需要几个小时才能与总部取得联系。科罗拉多州西南研究所的天体科学家卡利·霍韦特正在等待探测器传回的信息。探测器飞行速度很快，整个邂逅过程大约为三个小时。这个名叫“天涯海角”的天体很小，我们认为直径大约在20英里左右，但是它离地球很远，大约有65亿千米远。所以说这是一个令人激动的消息，因为它正在探索我们之前从未见过的东西。这是一个我们从未见过的天体，这也将是一次真正有价值的探索。我们现在焦急得等待着回传的数据。\n朝鲜领导人金正恩警告称，如果美国继续对其制裁，他可能会改变与其关系的方针，请听劳拉·贝克的报道，金正恩在贴有其父亲和祖父巨幅画像的办公室里向朝鲜人民做了年度电视致辞。在致辞的末尾，他向特朗普传达了一个消息。金正恩表示如果美国继续对朝鲜施压制裁，并错误判断朝鲜的耐心，那么他将别无选择，只能寻找新的道路。这或许意味着朝鲜在等着美国在2019年采取相关措施，如若不然，朝鲜对核武测试的暂停将会中止。\n巴西新总统雅伊尔·博尔索纳罗将会在今天晚些时候宣誓就职。这名极右翼政治家承诺将会立即放宽枪支法令。以下是凯蒂·华生在首都巴西利亚的报道。今天对于巴西来说是一个新的方向，但是该国的政治方向变得不确定起来。博尔索纳罗在竞选中自称是一个局外人，并承诺清理官僚腐败问题。对于那些支持他的人来说，他代表了改变。人们已经受够了当前的政治体制，很多人在过去的几年里都被牵扯进了腐败丑闻之中。尽管金融市场充满希望，他可能会设法逆转巴西糟糕的经济，但是很多人担心他保守的政策以及积极的态度只会让巴西人变得更穷更脆弱。BBC 新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>44</id>
        <date>January 4, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - On Christmas Eve</title>
        <description>
            A friend of mine named Paul received an automobile from his brother as Christmas present. On Christmas eve, when Paul came out of his office, a street urchin was walking around the shining new car, admiring it.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/christmas-car.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/on-christmas-eve.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**On Christmas Eve**\n**圣诞之夜**\nA friend of mine named Paul received an automobile from his brother as Christmas present. On Christmas eve, when Paul came out of his office, a street urchin was walking around the shining new car, admiring it.\n我有个朋友，保罗，在圣诞节那天收到了一份来自他哥哥的礼物，一辆轿车。在圣诞前夜，当保罗从他的办公室走出来时，一个街头顽童正围着他的新车打转地看，非常羡慕。\nIs this your car, Mister? he said.\n“这是您的汽车吗，先生？”他说。\nPaul nodded, "My brother gave it to me for Christmas."\n保罗点了点头，“我哥哥给我的圣诞礼物。\nThe boy was astounded, "You mean your brother gave it to you, and didn't cost you anything?"\n小男孩诧异了，“你是说你哥哥给你的，不用花你一分钱？”\nBoy, I wish... he hesitated.\n“兄弟，我希望...”他迟疑了。\nOf course Paul knew what he was going to wish for. He was going to wish he had a brother like that. But what the lad said jarred Paull all the way down his heels.\n保罗当然清楚他希望什么，他希望他也有个那样的哥哥。但这个小家伙说的话，使保罗大吃了一惊。\nI wish, the boy went on, "that I could be a brother like that."\n“我希望，”小男孩继续说道，“我可以做一个那样的哥哥。”\nPaul looked at the boy in astonishment, then inpulsivly he added, "Would you like to take a ride in my car?"\n保罗惊奇地看着小男孩，然后激动地说了句，“你想不想做我的车去兜兜风？”\nOh, yes. I'd love that.\n“哦，想！我喜欢！”\nAfter a short ride, the boy turned his eyes aglow, said, "Mister, would you mind driving in front of my house?"\n跑了一小段路后，小男孩眼光水灵闪闪地说道，“先生，您可以把车开到我家门前吗？”\nPaul smiled a little. He thought he knew what the lad wanted. He wanted to show his neighbours that he could ride home in a big automobile. But Paul was wrong again.\n保罗微微一笑。他觉得他知道这个小家伙想要干什么，他想要向他的邻居炫耀他可以坐一辆大汽车回家。但是，保罗又一次想错了。\nWould you stop at those with two steps? the boy asked.\n“您可以在那有两个台阶的房子前停下吗？” 小男孩问道。\nHe ran up stairs. Then in a little while, Paul heard him coming back, but he was not coming fast. He was carrying his little crippled brother. He set him down on the bottom step. Then a sort of squeezed up against him and pointed to the car.\n他跑着上楼去了。然后一小会儿，保罗听到他回来的脚步声，但他没再用跑的了。保罗看见他正搀扶着他的跛脚的弟弟，他扶着他坐在最底层的台阶上，然后拥抱着他，指着这部车。\nThere she is, buddy, just like I told you upstairs. His brother gave it to him for Christmas and didn't cost him a cent. And some day, I'm gonna give you one just like it. Then you can see for yourself all the pretty things in the chirstmas windows that I was trying to tell you about.\n“小弟，那就是我在楼上跟你说的那部车。他哥哥给他的圣诞礼物，不用花他一分钱。将来某天我也要给你一部像那样的车，那样你就可以自己去看我以前尽力想让你知道的那些窗边的圣诞饰品了。”\nPaul got off and lifted the lad into the front of his car. The shinning eyed old brother crimbed in beside him. And three of them began a memorable holiday ride.\n保罗下车把跛脚的小孩抱上了车的前座，他的眼睛水灵灵的哥哥爬上了车，坐到了他旁边。然后他们三个开始一段令人难忘的旅程。\nThat Christmas eve, Paul learned what Jesus meant, when he said, "It is more blessed to give than to receive..."\n那个圣诞前夜，保罗收获了很多，他真正体会了耶稣所说的那句话，“施舍比接受更有福...”
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>45</id>
        <date>January 5, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The budget dispute closed American government departments</title>
        <description>
            President Trump is due to meet congressional leaders to discuss the budget dispute that closed government departments, leaving 800,000 federal workers without pay. Earlier, Mr. Trump said he was prepared to maintain the shutdown for as long as it took, for the Democratic Party to give in to his demand for $5 billion for his border wall.
        </description>
        <cover>images/the-white-house-closed.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190105_05095853nm.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Stuart Macintosh.\nPresident Trump is due to meet congressional leaders to discuss the budget dispute that closed government departments, leaving 800,000 federal workers without pay. Earlier, Mr. Trump said he was prepared to maintain the shutdown for as long as it took, for the Democratic Party to give in to his demand for $5 billion for his border wall.\nThe family of a U.S citizen held on spying charges in Moscow have told the BBC he has been visited by consular officials. Paul Whelan's brother David said the family was told he looked healthy. Washington has said it wants to learn more about the charges against Paul Whelan. His family say he is innocent.\nBrazil's new economy minister Paulo Guedes has said the new far-right government will start a privatization program which will include the mining and energy sectors. Guedes said he will also introduce austerity measures and cut taxes.\nThere has been an uneasy start on this year's trading amid continued uncertainty about the global economic outlook. There were falls in Asia, and the downward trend continued in Europe and the U.S, although both have now regained most of the early losses.\nA boat carrying New Year revelers has capsized off the coast of Guinea, killing at least 2 people. Officials told the French news agency that at least 30 other passengers are missing.\nGreece has conferred citizenship on three migrant fishermen who rescued dozens of people trapped on the shore by a raging wildfire near Athens last July. President Pavlopoulos said the men who are originally from Egypt and Albania exemplified the spirit of European humanism.\nNASA revealed the first clear images of Ultima Thule, the most distant object ever visited by a spacecraft. They showed an icy figure of modern appearance which looks a bit like a snowman. The pictures were taken by the space probe New Horizons.\nThat's the BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nStuart Macintosh为您播报BBC新闻。\n特朗普总统将会见多名国会领袖，以讨论预算争议的问题。预算争议已导致多个政府部门停摆，并致80万名联邦政府工作人员拿不到工资。此前，特朗普曾表示他已经做好准备让国会一直停摆，多久都没关系，只要民主党能让步，并同意特朗普用50亿美元建造美墨边境墙。\n一位美国公民受到从事间谍活动的指控而被捕，其在俄罗斯的家人在接受BBC采访时表示，已经有多位领事馆工作人员去看望过他了。这位市民名为保罗·惠兰，其哥哥大卫表示，有人告诉他的家人他看起来很健康。美国政府表示其要对保罗·惠兰的指控了解更多信息。保罗的家人称其是无辜的。\n巴西新上任的经济部长保罗·盖德斯表示，新上任的极右翼政府将启动一个私有化项目，该项目将包含采矿业和能源业。盖德斯表示其也会采取紧缩措施，并减免赋税。\n新年伊始，贸易形势十分不易，全球经济前景的不确定性依然存在。亚洲贸易形势愈发恶化，欧美走势下滑，虽然欧美市场现在已经从初期的损失中回了本。\n载有新年狂欢人群的一艘船在几内亚海岸附近翻船，导致至少2人死亡。官员在接受法国新闻社采访时表示，至少还有30名乘客下落不明。\n希腊向3名移民来的渔民授予了国籍，因为这几位渔民援救了数十名困在岸上的人，而这些人之所以困在岸上是因为去年7月希腊附近发生了一场大火。希腊总统帕夫洛普洛斯表示，这几位移民有来自埃及的，也有来自阿尔巴尼亚的，他们诠释了欧洲人道主义精神。\n美国宇航局公布了天涯海角的首批高清图像。天涯海角是人类航天器去过的最远的地方。从图像上可以看到一个具有现代模样的冰状物体，看起来有点像雪人。这些图像都是探测器新视野号拍摄到的。\n感谢收听BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>46</id>
        <date>January 5, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Chinese Chang'e-4 probe first lands on the far side of the moon</title>
        <description>
            A Chinese robotic probe has become the first spacecraft to land on the far side of the moon. State media in Beijing have confirmed within the last hour that the Chang'e-4 probe had touched down successfully.
        </description>
        <cover>images/change-land-farside-moon.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190105_05095857pt.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC news.\nA Chinese robotic probe has become the first spacecraft to land on the far side of the moon. State media in Beijing have confirmed within the last hour that the Chang'e-4 probe had touched down successfully. John Southworth is in Beijing.\nIt marks a milestone in space exploration. Never before attempted, the mission faced serious challenges, including landing on the much more rugged terrain of the moon's far side and the need for a relay satellite to bring the signals back home. The Chang'e-4 probe named after a Chinese goddess has touched down close to the moon's south pole in its oldest and deepest crater. The experiments on board are expected to offer important insights into the formation of our solar system.\nDeadlock continues in Washington after discussions between President Trump and leaders of Congress failed to resolve the budget dispute that's caused the partial government shutdown. David Willis has more.\nA new session of Congress convenes later today with Democrats now in control of the House of Representatives, and the party's leadership is planning to pass legislation which would provide sufficient funds to end the partial shutdown, all be it with none of the five billion dollars President Trump wants for the wall. Such legislation will be dead on arrival in the Senate, however, where Republicans still hold the majority. President Trump has said the current partial government shutdown would last as long as it takes for him to get the border wall funding that he requires.\nScientists say they have discovered the source of a cholera outbreak in Yemen, which has become one of the worst epidemics of the disease in recorded history. British and French researchers have identified the cholera strain as one that originated in eastern Africa and was probably carried to Yemen by migrants. Yemen has seen more than a million cases of cholera.\nZimbabwe's biggest drinks company Delta has announced that from Friday it will only accept payment in hard currency such as US dollars. The firm said it had been hit by a shortage of foreign currency needed to pay its overseas suppliers. The government says the move is illegal.\nPolice in Britain have arrested two men suspected of arranging the illegal movement of migrants across the Channel. The men, one British, the other Iranian, were held in the city of Manchester. In the past two months, more than two hundred people have reached the southern English coast in small inflatable boats.\nThat's the latest bbc world news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n中国机器人探测器首次成功着陆月球背面。北京官方媒体在最后时刻证实嫦娥四号已成功着陆。以下是约翰·索斯沃斯在北京的报道。\n这是太空探索的里程碑。这项之前从未尝试的任务面临着很多严峻的挑战，包括在更加崎岖不平的月球背面降落以及需要用一个中继卫星将信号传回地球。嫦娥四号探测器以一位中国神话人物命名，它现已在月球南极附近最古老、最深的撞击坑着陆。登陆实验有望为我们理解太阳系的形成提供重要见解。\n特朗普总统与国会各领袖未能讨论出预算问题的解决办法，部分政府部门因而关闭。现在华盛顿的僵局还在继续。以下是大卫·威利斯的报道。\n今天晚些时候，现掌控众议院的民主党将在国会召开新的会议，该党领导层计划通过法案，提供充足的资金以结束部分停摆，但其中并不包括特朗普要求的50亿美元边境墙拨款。该法案将会终结于共和党占多数席位的参议院。特朗普表示目前政府停摆还会继续下去，直到他获得他提出的边境墙拨款为止。\n科学家称他们已经发现了也门霍乱爆发的根源，此次疫情也成为了有史以来最严重霍乱疫情之一。英国和法国的研究人员已经确认该霍乱菌株起源于东非，有可能是由移民带到也门的。也门现已出现了一百多万例霍乱。\n津巴布韦最大的饮品公司德尔塔宣布从周五开始只接受像美元这样的强势货币。该公司表示受外币短缺打击，他们可以支付给海外供应商的外币不足。该国政府表示此举属违法行为。\n英国警方已经逮捕了两名涉嫌安排移民从英吉利海峡偷渡的嫌疑人。两人一人为英国人，另一人为伊朗人，均在曼彻斯特被捕。在过去的两个月中，超过200人通过小型汽艇到达了英国南海岸。\n以上是BBC最新的国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>47</id>
        <date>January 6, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - Not a Simple Dress</title>
        <description>
            “Do you like my dress?"she asked of a passing stranger.My mommy made it just for me.She said with a tear in her eyes.My mommy made it just for me.She said with a tear in her eyes.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/mom-gril-dress.png</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/not-a-simple-dress.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Not a Simple Dress**\n**不凡的连衣裙**\n“Do you like my dress?"she asked of a passing stranger."\n“你喜欢我的连衣裙吗？“她问一位正走过她身边的陌生人。\nMy mommy made it just for me.She said with a tear in her eyes.\n我妈妈专给我做的。”她说道，眼里冒出了泪珠。\nWell,I think it's very pretty,so tell me little one,why are you crying?\n“嗯，我认为你的裙子真漂亮。告诉我，小姑娘，你为什么哭呢？”\nWith a quiver in her voice the little girl answered."After Mommy made me this dress,she had to go away."\n小姑娘声音有些颤抖，回答道：“我妈妈给我做完这条裙子后就不得不离开了。”\nWell,now,said the lady,"with a little girl like you waiting for her,I'm sure she'll be right back."\n“哦，是这样，”陌生的女士说，“有你这样一个小姑娘等着她，我敢肯定她很快就会回来的。”\nNo Ma'am,you don't understand,said the child through her tears,"my daddy said she's up in heaven now with Grandfather."\n“不，女士，您不明白，”女孩透过泪水说，“我爸说她现在和我爷爷在天堂里。”\nFinally the woman realized what the child meant,and why she was crying.Kneeling down she gently cradled the child in her arms and together they cried for the mommy that was gone.\n女士终于明白孩子的意思了，也明白她为什么哭泣。她跪下，温柔地把女孩搂在怀里，她们一起为离去的妈妈哭泣。\nThen suddenly the little girl did something that the woman thought was a bit strange.She stopped crying,stepped back from the woman and began to sing.She sang so softly that it was almost a whisper. It was the sweetest sound the woman had ever heard,almost like the song of a very small bird.\n忽然小姑娘又做了件让女士感到有点奇怪的事。她停住了哭泣，从女士怀抱中抽出身，向后退了一步，然后开始唱歌。她唱得如此轻柔，几乎像章晨低语。这是女士听到过的最甜美的声音，简直就像一只非常小的小鸟在吟唱。\nAfter the child stopped singing she explained to the lady,"My mommy used to sing that song to me before she went away,and she made me promise to sing it whenever I started crying and it would make me stop."\n小女孩唱完后解释说：“妈妈离去前经常给我唱这支歌，她让我答应她我一哭就唱这支歌，这样我就不哭了。”\n"See",she exclaimed,"it did,and now my eyes are dry!"\n“您瞧，”她惊叫道，“真管用，现在我的眼睛里没有眼泪了！”\nAs the woman turned to go,the little girl grabbed her sleeve,"Ma'am,can you stay just a minute?I want to show you something."\n女士转身要走时，小女孩抓住她的衣袖：“女士，您能再停留一小会儿吗？我想给您看点东西。”\nOf course,she answered,"what do you want me to see?"\n“当然可以，”她回答，“你想要我看什么呢？”\nPointing to a spot on her dress,she said,"Right here is where my mommy kissed my dress,and here,"pointing to another spot,"and here is another kiss, and here,and here.Mommy said that she put all those kisses on my dress so that I would have her kisses for every booboo'that made me cry."\n小女孩指着裙子上的一处，说：“就在这里，我妈妈亲了我的裙子，还有这里，”她指着另外一处，“这里有另外一个吻，还有这里，这里。妈妈说她把所有这些吻都留在我的连衣裙上，这样我遇到什么事哭了，就会有她的亲吻。”\nThen the lady realized that she wasn't just looking at a dress,no,she was looking at a mother…who knew that she was going away and would not be there to kiss away the hurts that she knew her daughter would get.\n这时，女士意识到在她眼前的不是一件连衣裙，不是的，她在凝视一位母亲……这位母亲知道她将离去，无法随时守候在女儿身边，吻去她知道女儿必然会遇到的种种伤心事。\nSo she took all the love she had for her beautiful little girl and put them into this dress,which her child now so proudly wore.\n所以她将所有对她美丽女儿的爱倾注在这件连衣裙上。现在，女儿如此骄傲地穿在身上。\nShe no longer saw a little girl in a simple dress. She saw a child wrapped…in her mother's love.\n她看到的不再是身穿一件简单的连衣裙的小女孩。她看到的是一个……被妈妈的爱裹着的孩子。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>48</id>
        <date>January 7, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - US stock has fallen hit by bad news from Apple and weak manufacturing figures</title>
        <description>
            US stock has fallen hit by bad news from the technology giant Apple and weak manufacturing figures. At one point, the Dow Jones index was 2.4% down. Apple’s shares fell more than 9% at the start of the trading after the Company cut its revenue forecasts sharply for the final quarter of 2018.
        </description>
        <cover>images/apple-stock.png</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/tingvoa.com_BBC07094133vy.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Nick Kelly.\nThe veteran Democratic Party legislator Nancy Pelosi has been elected Speaker of the US House of Representatives for historical second time as her party takes charge of the chamber. The Democrats have vowed to pass bills designed to end the partial government shutdown caused by a roar of funding for Mr. Trump’s border wall.
            Russian news agency say a former US marine arrested in Moscow last week has been charged with spying. Paul Whelan was detained 6 days ago by Russia Security Service, the FSB.\nPope Francis has said the credibility of the US Catholic churches has been severely damaged by the sexual abuse scandal and efforts to cover it up. In a letter to a meeting of US bishops, the Pope called for unity.\nUS stock has fallen hit by bad news from the technology giant Apple and weak manufacturing figures. At one point, the Dow Jones index was 2.4% down. Apple’s shares fell more than 9% at the start of the trading after the Company cut its revenue forecasts sharply for the final quarter of 2018.\nThe United States has warned Iran not to go ahead with the series of plans of space rocket launches, saying it would violate UN resolutions intended to curb Tehran’s missile development program. The US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said the launches would be provocative.\nThe American pharmaceuticals giant Bristol Myers Squibb has announced plans to acquire the cancer drug therapeutics group Celgene in the 74-billion-dollar deal. If the merge goes ahead, it will one of the largest in the sector’s history, creating a biotech giant producing drugs for cancer, immune disorders and cardiovascular disease.\nAnd archaeologists in Mexico have discovered the earliest known temple in a sacrifice altar dedicated to the pre-Aztec god Xipe Totec, or flayed lord. Priests worshipped him by wearing the skin of human sacrifices. The site is believed about a thousand years old.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nNick Kelly为您播报BBC新闻。\n资深民主党议员南希·佩洛西当选众议院议长，这是她第二次当选该职位。众议院由民主党占多数席位。民主党承诺会多项议案，以终结政府部分部门的停摆。此次停摆的原因是特朗普要求为建造边境墙提供资金。\n据俄罗斯通讯社报道，某美国前海军陆战队队员上周在莫斯科被捕，其罪名是从事间谍活动。此人名为保罗·惠兰，他6天前被俄罗斯联邦安全局海岸警卫队（FSB）逮捕。\n方济各教皇表示，美国天主教堂的信誉受到了严重损害，原因是所发生的性丑闻和企图掩盖性丑闻的行为。在写给美国各主教会议的信中，方济各教皇呼吁大家团结起来。\n美国股市暴跌，原因是科技巨头苹果公司传来噩耗以及制造业疲软不振。道琼斯指数最低下降了2.4%。苹果公司市值开盘时就暴跌9%以上，因为该公司大幅降低了2018第四季度的收益预测。\n美国警告伊朗不要继续进行航天火箭发射的计划，并表示伊朗此举会违背联合国决议，而决议的目的就是扼制伊朗政府的导弹研制项目。美国国务卿迈克·蓬佩奥表示，发射航天火箭的行为极具挑衅性。\n美国制药业巨头百时美施贵宝公司宣布计划收购研制抗癌药物的公司——新基生物制药，收购价格为740亿美元。如果收购成功，此举将成为制药业历史上最大的收购之一，并将造就生物技术领域的巨头，主打方向是研制针对抗癌、免疫紊乱、冠心病的药物。\n墨西哥考古学家在某祭坛中发现了最早的寺庙，该寺庙是为了供奉古文明阿兹特克的神明希佩托特，也就是剥皮之主。信徒们朝拜的方式是穿着献祭的人皮。据信，此地已有近1000年的历史。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>49</id>
        <date>January 8, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Opposition demonstrators in Hungary are due to resume protest shortly against Viktor Orban</title>
        <description>
            Opposition demonstrators in Hungary are due to resume protest shortly against the policies of the far-right government of Viktor Orban.The rallies began last month in response to a controversial law that extends overtime.
        </description>
        <cover>images/hungary-protest.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/tingvoa.com_BBC08094253nr.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news. I'm John Shay.\nRussia's Deputy Foreign Minister Sergei Ryabkov says the country is not willing to consider a prisoner swap involving the former US Marine Paul Whelan. He was arrested in Moscow over a week ago on suspicion of spying. His families say he's innocent. From Moscow, here's Sarah Rainsford. Sergei Ryabkov described the arrest of Paul Whelan as very serious and said that at this stage, talk of swapping him for any Russian detainee was inappropriate, counter-productive and politically unjustified. His comments came after days of speculation that the former US Marine may have been arrested to exchange for Maria Butina who has pleaded guilty in the US to conspiring to act as an unregistered agent of Moscow. Russia's Foreign Ministry and President Putin have condemned that case repeatedly and loudly. Sergei Ryabkov said there is no link between Mr. Whelan's arrest here in Moscow and other detentions.\nA document officially recognizing the independence of Ukraine's Orthodox Church from Russia has been signed at a ceremony at St. George's Cathedral in Istanbul. The Ukrainian President Petro Poroshenko attended the signing of the document known as "tomos". Jonah Fisher is in Kiev. What the "tomos" does is it recognizes that Ukraine has its own branch of the Christian Orthodox Church, crucially a branch that is separate from the Russian Orthodox Church, because for the last three hundred years or so, the Ukrainian parishes have been under the overall responsibility of the Russian Orthodox Church. That will no longer be the case. This "tomos" has been signed. It now grants official recognition to the Ukrainian Orthodox Church. That's why the Russians are so upset and the Ukrainians are so happy.\nOpposition demonstrators in Hungary are due to resume protest shortly against the policies of the far-right government of Viktor Orban. The rallies began last month in response to a controversial law that extends overtime. Nick Thorpe is in Budapest. Today's demonstration is a litmus test to the degree of anger in Hungary against the overtime law, and of the determination of those willing to come out onto the streets. Heavy snow in the past twenty four hours across the country could reduce numbers. They're threatening nationwide strikes unless their four main demands are met. The scrapping of the overtime law, double-digit wage increases, the removal of limitations on the right to strike and a far-reaching pension reform. The Fidesz government has already offered an eight percent wage increase this year, followed by another eight percent next year in an attempt to head off the discontent.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，我是约翰·席亚。\n俄罗斯外交部副部长谢尔盖·里亚布科夫表示俄罗斯不会考虑交换前海军陆战队队员保罗·韦兰。一周前，韦兰因间谍指控被捕。他的家人称他是无辜的。以下是萨拉·雷恩福德在莫斯科的报道。谢尔盖·里亚布科夫表示逮捕保罗·韦兰是非常严肃的，在此节点上讨论用他来交换俄罗斯在押人员是不合适的、起反作用的并且在政治上也是不公正的。在他发表此番言论的前几天，人们猜测逮捕韦兰的目的是交换玛丽亚·布缇娜。她已在美国承认是俄罗斯的一名未注册间谍。俄罗斯外交部和总统普京曾多次强烈地对该案进行谴责。谢尔盖·里亚布科夫表示，逮捕韦兰与其它扣押无关。\n一份官方承认乌克兰东正教会从俄罗斯独立的文件现已在伊斯坦布尔圣乔治大教堂的一个仪式中签署。乌克兰总统佩特罗·波罗申科参加了这份名为“tomos”的文件签署仪式。以下是乔纳·费希尔在基辅的报道。这份“tomos”文件承认了乌克兰有了自己的东正教分支，最重要是独立于俄罗斯东正教的分支。因为在过去的300多年里，乌克兰教区一直都在俄罗斯东正教会的全权负责之下。情况将不再如此，这份“ tomos”文件已签署，它官方承认了乌克兰东正教正教会的合法性。这也是俄罗斯人如此沮丧而乌克兰人如此开心的原因。\n匈牙利的反对派示威人员将不久后重启游行活动，抗议维克托·欧尔班极右翼政府的政策。抗议集会开始于上个月，是为了反对一项有争议的延长加班时间的法律。以下是尼克·索普在布达佩斯的报道。今天的抗议活动将会检验人们对于这项延长加班时间的法律愤怒程度以及人们出门参加游行的决心。在过去的24小时内匈牙利全国范围内下了大雪，这可能会减少游行人群的数量。他们威胁称，如果他们的四项主要要求不能满足，将会发起全国范围内的罢工。这四项要求是取消延长加班时间的法律，两位数的工资增长，取消对于罢工权的限制以及彻底的退休金改革。匈牙利青年民主党政府今年已经为他们提供了8%的工资增长，为了防止民众不满意，明年还会继续增长8%。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>50</id>
        <date>January 9, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The planned withdrawal of American troops from Syria is still under debate</title>
        <description>
            The US National Security Advisor John Bolton is in Turkey for what is expected to be tense talks on the planned withdrawal of American troops from Syria.
        </description>
        <cover>images/syria-crisis.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/tingvoa.com_BBC09081645jy.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Rosemary Crick with a look at the latest BBC news.\nCarlos Ghosn, the former chairman of the Japanese Carmaker Nissan, has appeared in public for the first time since his arrest in November on suspicion of financial misconduct. He's attended a hearing at the Tokyo District Court. Here is Rupert Wingfield-Hayes.\nMr. Ghosn came in wearing a dark suit without a tie on. He was handcuffed around the waist. He then went on to make a very robust statement in which he categorically denied the allegations against him. He said he had been wrongly accused on meritless and unsubstantiated allegations and he said he had not received any compensation from Nissan Motor Corporation that was not disclosed. So a very direct rebuttal of the allegations and the legal accusations that have been made against him by the prosecutors here.\nThe US National Security Advisor John Bolton is in Turkey for what is expected to be tense talks on the planned withdrawal of American troops from Syria. Last month, Donald Trump promised that all US forces would leave immediately, but on Sunday, Mr. Bolton insisted they stay until the last Islamic State militants were defeated. From Istanbul, Celine Garrett reports.\nDonald Trump first announced the withdrawal of US troops from Syria, after a phone call with Turkey's President Recep Tayyip Erdogan last month. This was a move Ankara had long hoped for. Once US troops pulled out of northern Syria, the Turkish military would be able to cross the border to drive out Kurdish forces, which Turkey sees as terrorists. But with the Kurds turning to Russia for protection, Washington felt obliged to take a step back from Mr. Trump's announcement. His National Security Adviser John Bolton is trying to reassure Kurdish forces that they are still America's allies. That has left Turkey frustrated and it is very difficult to see Ankara agreeing to protect the Kurds. In today's talks, both sides will need to strike a delicate balance as neither wants to damage their relationship.\nThe governor of the US state of Tennessee has granted clemency to a woman who was sentenced to life in prison for murder when she was just sixteen. Cyntoia Brown said she was forced into prostitution and feared for her life when she shot a man dead in Nashville in 2004. She will be freed on parole in August but must remain under supervision for a further ten years.\nPresident of the World Bank Jim Yong Kim is stepping down three years before the end of his term. The bank gave no reason, though it said Mr. Kim would join the private sector and would focus on increasing infrastructure investments in developing countries.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n我是罗丝玛丽·克里克，欢迎收听最新的BBC新闻\n日本汽车生产商日产的前董事长卡洛斯·戈恩公开露面，这是他自去年11月因涉嫌不当金融行为被捕后的首次露面。他出席了东京地区法院的听审。以下是鲁珀特·温菲尔德-海耶斯的报道。\n戈恩身穿黑色正装走进法院，但是没有打领带。他双手被手铐铐在腰侧。之后他做了强硬的声明，坚决否认了关于他的指控。他表示自己受到了错误的、不道德的且无事实根据的指控，他还坚称没有私拿日产汽车公司的任何报酬。总的来说，他对当地检察官的指控和法律诉讼做了直接的反驳。\n美国国家安全顾问约翰·博尔顿正在土耳其就美国拟从叙利亚撤军问题进行的紧张会谈。上个月，唐纳德·特朗普总统承诺所有美国军队将立即撤军，但是周日，博尔顿坚称在彻底打败伊斯兰国组织之前不会撤军。以下是赛琳·盖瑞特在伊斯坦布尔的报道。\n唐纳德·特朗普在上个月与土耳其总统雷杰普·塔伊普·埃尔多安通话后首次宣布从叙利亚撤军。这也是土耳其一直以来希望的结果。一旦美国从叙利亚北部撤军，土耳其军队将可以穿越边境驱逐被他们视为恐怖分子的库尔德武装。但随着库尔德武装转而向俄罗斯寻求帮助，美国认为不得不暂缓实施特朗普的决定。特朗普的国家安全顾问约翰·博尔顿正试图向库尔德武装保证他们仍是美国的盟友。而这也让土耳其受挫，而且土耳其同意保护库尔德的可能性很小。在今天的谈判中，由于双方都不想损害彼此间的关系，他们将需要取得一个微妙的平衡。\n美国田纳西州的州长给予了一名女犯人宽大处理，该女性在16岁时因杀人被判终身监禁。辛托妮亚·布朗表示，2004年在纳什维尔，当时的她被迫卖淫且担心自己的生命安全因而开枪打死一人。她将在8月份被保释，但是在接下来的10年内将必须受到监控。\n世界银行行长金墉将提前三年卸任。世界银行并没有给出具体原因，虽然该行表示金墉将会进入私营领域并将关注增加对发展中国家基础设施投资的问题。\nBBC新闻
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>51</id>
        <date>January 10, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - A Father's Love</title>
        <description>
            Daddy just didn’t know how to show love. It was Mom who held the family together. He just went to work every day and came home; she’d have a list of sins we’d committed and he’d scold us about them.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/father-teach-ride-bicycle.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/a-father-love.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**A Father's Love**\n**父爱**\nDaddy just didn’t know how to show love. It was Mom who held the family together. He just went to work every day and came home; she’d have a list of sins we’d committed and he’d scold us about them.\n爸爸根本不知道怎样表达爱。把这个家维系在一起的人是妈妈。爸爸天天去上班，回家，然后是妈妈向他数落我们所做的一连串错事，爸爸再为了这些事把我们骂一顿。\nOnce when I stole a candy bar, he made me take it back and tell the man I stole it and that I’d pay for it. But it was Mom who understood I was just a kid.\n有一次我偷了一根棒棒糖。爸爸硬是要我送回去，还要我告诉卖糖的人是我偷了糖，并说我愿意帮他拆箱开包作为赔偿。但妈妈却理解我，她知道我只不过是个孩子。\nI broke my leg once on the playground swing and it was Mom who held me in her arms all the way to the hospital. Dad pulled the car right up to the door of the emergency room and when they asked him to move it saying the space was reserved for emergency vehicles, He shouted, “What do you think this is? A tour bus?”\n再有一次，我在操场荡秋千摔坏了腿，一路抱着我到医院的人是妈妈。爸爸将车正好停在急诊室门口。因为那儿是专供急救车停靠的，医院里的人就叫我爸爸把车开走。爸爸大声吼叫起来：“你以为这是什么车？难道是旅游车吗？”\nAt my birthday parties, Dad always seemed sort of out of place, He just busied himself blowing up balloons, setting up tables, and running errands, it was Mom who carried the cake with the candles on it for me to blow out.\n在我的生日聚会上，爸爸总显得有点不得其所。他不是忙于吹气球，就是摆桌子，或做些跑腿的活儿。将插着蜡烛的生日蛋糕捧进来让我吹灭的人总是妈妈。\nWhen I leaf through picture albums, people always ask, “What does your Dad took like?” “Who knows? He was always fiddling around with the camera taking everyone else’s picture. I must have a zillion pictures of Mom and me smiling together.”\n我随便翻阅相册时，别人总会问“你爸爸长什么模样？”这还真说不出。他总是摆弄着相机为别人拍照。我和妈妈在一起微笑的照片一定多得都数不清了。\nI remember when Mom told him to teach me how to ride a bicycle. I told him not to let it go, but he said it was time. I fell and Mom ran to pick me up, but he waved her off. I was so mad I showed him,I got right back on that bike and rode it myself. He didn’t even feel embarrassed and just smiled.\n我还记得有一次妈妈叫爸爸教我骑自行车。我叫他扶着车子别松手，他却说是时候了。我摔了下来，妈妈跑来扶我，他却挥手让妈妈开走。我真是气得发疯，决心非要让他看看我的本事不可。我马上骑上车，竟能一个人骑了。爸爸却一点也不尴尬，只是笑笑。\nWhen I went to college, Mom did all the writing. He just sent checks and a little note about how great his lawn looked now that I wasn’t playing football on it.\n我上大学了，给我的信总是妈妈写的。爸爸只知道寄钱，顶多附上一张便条，告诉我他的草坪现在修整得多么好，而如今我却不能在上面踢球。\nWhenever I called home, he acted like he wanted to talk, but he always said, “I’ll get your mother.”When I got married, it was Mom who cried. He just blew his nose loudly and left the room. All my life he said, “Where are you going? What time are you coming home? No, you cannot go.”\n每次我打电话回家，爸爸总像是有话要说，但结果他总是说“我把你妈叫来接”。我结婚的时候，妈妈哭了，爸爸只是大声打着鼻响，离走出了房间。在我一生中，他总是说：“你去哪儿？你什么时候回家？不，你不能去。”\nDaddy just didn’t know how to show love, unless…\n爸爸就是不知道怎样表达爱，只会这样……\nIs it possible he showed it and didn’t recognize it?\n爸爸向我们表达了爱，难道他只是没有意识到吗？
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>52</id>
        <date>January 12, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Mysterious energy bursts from an unknown origin in deep space</title>
        <description>
            Mysterious energy bursts from an unknown origin in deep space have been detected for only the second time since 2007. Some scientists suggest the radio flashes could have be generated by phenomena such as black holes.
        </description>
        <cover>images/enery-brust.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/tingvoa.com_BBC12083636hc.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Stewart Macintosh.\nThe Democratic Republic of Congo is braced for the announcement of the presidential election result after a delay that has raised fears for the country's stability. Riot police have been deployed around the commission’s headquarters in Kinshasa amid fears that a disputed outcome could trigger violence.\nBritain is ending its policy requiring women saved from forced marriages abroad from taking out a government loan to cover the cost of their rescue. The decision follows a newspaper investigation which found that some were made to pay for their food, shelter and flights back to Britain.\nSpain's center-right People's Party [PP] has reached an agreement with the far-right anti-immigrant Vox Party, enabling a PP-led coalition to take power in the southern region of Andalusia. The PP will unseat the socialists who held power there for 36 years.\nSpain's center-right People's Party [PP] has reached an agreement with the far-right anti-immigrant Vox Party, enabling a PP-led coalition to take power in the southern region of Andalusia. The PP will unseat the socialists who held power there for 36 years.\nIran has acknowledged for the first time that a US citizen was arrested in the country last month. The spokesman for the Iranian Foreign Ministry said the US government had been informed of the arrest of Michael White in the city of Mashhad. No reason was given.\nThe Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has urged Mexicans not to panic as petrol shortages bite as a result of his crackdown on fuel theft and corruption. Long lines have been reported at petrol stations in at least six days.\nMysterious energy bursts from an unknown origin in deep space have been detected for only the second time since 2007. Some scientists suggest the radio flashes could have be generated by phenomena such as black holes. Others hypothesize that they could be the product of complex alien technology.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nStewart Macintosh为您播报BBC新闻。\n刚果民主共和国即将宣布总统大选结果。此前推迟宣布结果的举动让外界担心该国的稳定性。防暴警察已部署在选举委员会位于金沙萨的总部附近。有人担心，选举结果如果存在争议，会导致暴力争端出现。\n英国废除了一项政策，该政策要求在境外遭遇强迫婚姻的女性不得用政府贷款来抵消援救费用。在做出该决定之前，某报纸进行了一项调查。该调查发现，一些女性被要求自费支付粮食、避难所和返回英国的费用。\n西班牙右翼的人民党跟反对移民的极右派民声党达成了一项协议。这样，由人民党领导的联盟就能在南部地区安大路西亚掌权了。人民党将取缔已经在该地执政长达36年的社会主义民声党。\n极右翼的意大利副总理马泰奥?萨尔维尼呼吁本国和波兰的民粹主义者发起所谓的“欧洲之春”，以代替德国和法国所带来的右翼影响。\n伊朗首次承认一位美国公民上个月在伊朗被捕。伊朗外交部发言人表示，伊朗在那之前已经通知了美国政府迈克尔怀特在马什哈德被捕一事。不过被捕原因尚未说明。\n墨西哥总统奥夫拉多尔敦促墨西哥人民不要因汽油短缺加剧而惊慌。石油短缺加剧是因为他打击燃料盗窃和贪污腐败的行为所引发的。据报道，在最近至少6天的时间里，各加油站排起了长队。\n深空中出现了神秘的能量爆发现象，其来源尚不可知。这是自2007年以来，人类第二次检测到这样的能量爆发。一些科学家表示，这种电波爆发现象是由黑洞等现象所引发的。还有一些科学家假设称，这种现象可能是复杂外星技术所产生的。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>53</id>
        <date>January 13, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - The Key of a Car</title>
        <description>
            A young man was getting ready to graduate from college. For many months he had admired a beautiful sports car in a dealer's showroom, and knowing his father could well afford it, he told him that was all he wanted.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/tesla-key.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/the-key-of-a-car.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Key of a Car**\n**一把车钥匙**\nA young man was getting ready to graduate from college. For many months he had admired a beautiful sports car in a dealer's showroom, and knowing his father could well afford it, he told him that was all he wanted.\n从前，有位年轻人即将大学生毕业。数月来，他一直渴望得到某汽车商产品陈列室中的一辆跑车。他知道，他那富有的父亲肯定买得起这辆车，于是，他便跟父亲说他很想得到那辆漂亮的跑车。\nAs Graduation Day approached, the young man awaited signs that his father had purchased the car. Finally, on the morning of his graduation, his father called him into his private study. His father told him how proud he was to have such a fine son, and told him how much he loved him. He handed his son a beautiful wrapped gift box. Curiously, but somewhat disappointed, the young man opened the box and found a lovely, leather-bound Bible, with the young man's name embossed in gold. Angrily, he raised his voice to his father and said, "With all your money you give me a Bible?" Then stormed out of the house, leaving the Bible.\n在毕业典礼即将来临的日子里，年轻人等待着父亲买下跑车的消息。终于，在毕业典礼那天上午，父亲将他叫到自己的书房，并告诉他，有他这么出色的儿子自己感到非常自豪而且非常爱他这个儿子。接着，父亲递给儿子一个包装精美的礼品盒。年轻人感到好奇，但带着些许失望地打开礼品盒，却发现里面是一本精美的精装本《圣经》，上面以金子凸印着年轻人的名字。看罢，年轻人怒气冲冲地向父亲大喊道：“你有那么多钱，却只给我一本《圣经》？”说完，便丢下《圣经》，愤怒地冲出房子。\nMany years passed and the young man was very successful in business. He had a beautiful home and a wonderful family, but realizing his father was very old, he thought perhaps he should go to see him. He had not seen him since that graduation day. Before he could make the arrangements, he received a telegram telling him his father had passed away, and willed all of his possessions to his son. He needed to come home immediately and take care of things.\n多年以后，年轻人已事业有成。他拥有一所漂亮的房子，一个温馨的家庭。但当得知父亲年事已高，他想，或许应该去看看他。自从毕业那天起他就一直不见父亲。就在起程时，他收到一封电报－－父亲已逝世，并已立下遗嘱将其所有财产转给儿子。他要立即回父亲家处理后事。\nWhen he arrived at his father's house, sudden sadness and regret filled his heart. He began to search through his father's important papers and saw the still new Bible, just as he had left it years ago. With tears, he opened the Bible and began to turn the pages. As he was reading, a car key dropped from the back of the Bible. It had a tag with the dealer's name, the same dealer who had the sports car he had desired. On the tag was the date of his graduation, and the words... "PAID IN FULL".\n在父亲的房子里，他突然内心感到一阵悲伤与懊悔。他开始仔细搜寻父亲的重要文件，突然发现了那本《圣经》－－还跟几年前一样崭新。他噙着泪水打开《圣经》并一页一页地阅读着。忽然，从书的背面掉出一把钥匙。钥匙上挂着一个标签，上面写着一个汽车经销商的名字－－正是他曾渴望的那辆跑车的经销商。标签上还有他的毕业日期及“款已付清”的字样。\nHow many times do we miss blessings because they are not packaged as we expected? I trust you enjoyed this. Do not spoil what you have by desiring what you have not; but remember that what you now have was once among the things you only hoped for.\n我们多少次地与祝福擦肩而过，仅仅因为他们没有按我们想象中的样子包装好？我相信你也有这样的经历。不要在渴望得到没有的东西时损坏你已经拥有的东西，但要记住一点：你现在所拥有的恰恰正是你曾经一心渴望得到的。\nSometimes we don't realize the good fortune we have or we could have because we expect "the packaging" to be different. What may appear as bad fortune may in fact be the door that is just waiting to be opened.\n有时，我们并没有意识到我们已经拥有或本该拥有的好运，仅仅因为它的外表与我们想象中的有所不同。其实，表面上看起来像是坏运气的东西或许正是等待开启的幸运之门.
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>54</id>
        <date>January 13, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - FCA has agreed to pay more than 600 million dollars to settle claims</title>
        <description>
            Fiat Chrysler Automobiles has agreed to pay the U.S Justice Department and the State of California more than 600 million dollars to settle claims that it used illegal software to falsify diesel vehicle emission tests.
        </description>
        <cover>images/FCA.png</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0113_3559585jJB.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Stewart Macintosh. \nPresident Trump has arrived in Texas to publicize and win support for his controversial plan to build a wall along the U.S-Mexico border. In his first comments in the southern state, Mr. Trump blamed democrats for the ongoing government shutdown, saying they were pursing an open-border policy.\nThe runner-up in the presidential election in the Democratic Republic of Congo Martin Fayulu has told the BBC that he will mount a legal challenge to the result. Earlier, the Catholic Church which is highly influential in Congo said its own tallied results didn't match with the official result.\nThe Macedonia Prime Minister Zoran Zaev has delayed a final vote on the country's proposed change of name as he haggles to reach the necessary 2/3 majority. Renaming the country the Republic of North Macedonia will end a long-running dispute with its neighbor Greece, and open the way to EU and NATO membership.\nFiat Chrysler Automobiles has agreed to pay the U.S Justice Department and the State of California more than 600 million dollars to settle claims that it used illegal software to falsify diesel vehicle emission tests. The firm denies that it was involved in deliberate wrong-doing.\nVenezuela's President Nicolas Maduro is beginning his second term in office despite calls for him to step down. Mr. Maduro accused the United States of leading an economic war against its government.\nA court in the Zimbabwean capital Harare has heard that a suitcase containing 150,000 dollars in cash was stolen from the ousted President Robert Mugabe. Mr. Mugabe was often accused of a lavish life style even as the Zimbabwean suffered under his rule.\nOfficials in South Africa say they intercepted a consignment of rhino horns worth over 1.5 million dollars at the international airport in Johannesburg.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nStewart Macintosh为您播报BBC新闻。\n特朗普已抵达德克萨斯州为自己备受争议的计划造势并赢取支持。他的计划就是建造美墨边境墙。他落地后在德克萨斯州发表的第一次讲话中就谴责民主党，称其为当前政府停摆的罪魁祸首，并表示民主党主张美国大门向世界敞开的政策。\n刚果民主共和国总统大选的第二名，即马丁·法尤卢，在接受我台采访时表示自己将就选举结果发起诉讼。此前，在刚果极具影响力的天主教表示其自己统计的选举结果与官方公布的结果不一致。\n马其顿总理扎埃夫推迟了本国改名的最终投票日，因为他还在为争取2/3的大多数票数而努力，2/3是通过改名方案的最低票比。如果能将马其顿改名为北马其顿共和国，就能结束与邻国希腊长期以来的争议，并为成为欧盟和北约成员国铺路。\n菲亚特克莱斯勒汽车同意向美国司法部和加州支付6亿多美元，以平息后两者的说法——该公司通过非法软件伪造柴油车尾气释放的检测结果。该公司否认自己曾故意做过错事。\n委内瑞拉总统马杜罗将开启第二届任期，虽然外界有呼声表示希望他下台。马杜罗指责美国针对委内瑞拉政府发动经济战争。\n津巴布韦首都哈拉雷某法院召开了听审会，判定某装有15万美元现金的手提箱系已被驱逐的总统穆加贝所偷。穆加贝曾被指责挥霍无度，就连津巴布韦人民在其统治下处于水深火热的境地时也不例外。\n多位南非官员表示他们截获了一批犀牛角，价值150万美元，截获地点是约翰尼斯堡国际机场。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>55</id>
        <date>January 14, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The continuing government shutdown in the United States is now in its 22nd day</title>
        <description>
            The continuing government shutdown in the United States is now in its 22nd day, the longest in US history. President Trump is refusing to sign budget measures to reopen parts of the government because Democrats in Congress won't include funding for his promised border wall with Mexico.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-aid-russia.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190114_3606526RFS.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, This is David Austin with the BBC News. The continuing government shutdown in the United States is now in its 22nd day, the longest in US history. President Trump is refusing to sign budget measures to reopen parts of the government because Democrats in Congress won't include funding for his promised border wall with Mexico. Here's David Willis. Hundreds of thousands of government workers have now missed out on what should have been their first paycheck of the year, and with airport screening staff, air traffic controllers and FBI officers among those who are affected, union officials are warning that public safety could be compromised if the shutdown drags on. Despite calls by the president for Democrats to negotiate, no further talks between the two sides are planned.\nThe White House has dismissed this absurd report by the New York Times, saying that FBI opened an inquiry into whether President Trump was working secretly on behalf of Russia. Here's Michael Duncan. These allegations go much further than mere collusion between the Russians and the Trump election campaign. The report in the New York Times says that the officials were so concerned that the FBI began an investigation into whether Mr. Trump was in fact working on behalf of Russia and constituted a threat to US national security. Days later, that counter-intelligence inquiry became part of Robert Mueller's investigation, which has yet to publish its conclusions. Mr. Trump's Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders dismissed the report as absurd. She said James Comey was sacked because he was a disgraced partisan hack and his deputy Andrew McCabe, who launched the inquiry was a known liar who had been dismissed by the FBI.\nA British cabinet minister has warned that there could be a surge in far-right extremism in the UK if Brexit is blocked. The Transport Secretary Chris Grayling told the Daily Mail newspaper that if Britain's departure is prevented, the seventeen million people who voted for Brexist will feel cheated. Mr. Grayling endorses the Prime Minister's withdrawal deal, which faces likely defeat next week in Parliament. Chris Mason reports. Chris Grayling is not suggesting there would be riots if Brexit is weakened or reversed, but he is blunt about what he fears would be the consequences. People should not underestimate this, he says, we would see a different tone in our politics, a less tolerant society, a more nationalistic nation. He then adds, if MPs who represent seats that voted 70% to leave say sorry, guys we are still going to have freedom of movement, they will turn against the political mainstream. BBC News.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·奥斯汀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。美国政府停摆现已延续了22天，达到了美国历史上时间最长的一次。特朗普拒绝签署预算措施以重启部分政府，因为国会的民主党不愿意为特朗普承诺的美墨边境墙拨款。以下是大卫·威利斯的报道。几十万名政府工作人员现已错过了他们新年的第一笔薪水，机场安检人员，交通管制人员以及FBI人员都在受影响之列，工会官员警告称如果停摆继续下去将会危及公共安全。尽管总统呼吁与民主党进行磋商，但双方没有计划进一步会谈。\n白宫没有理会《纽约时报》的一份荒唐报告，该报告称FBI曾进行过一项关于特朗普是否秘密地为俄罗斯工作的调查。这些指控要比特朗普涉嫌在竞选活动中通俄严重的多。引起美国官员担忧的《纽约时报》的报道称，FBI曾进行过一项调查，目的在于查清特朗普是否真的为俄罗斯工作，以及是否对美国国家安全造成威胁。几天之后，罗伯特·穆勒就开启了反情报调查，但现在还没有公布结论。特朗普的新闻发言人萨拉·哈科比·桑德斯否认了该报道，并称其荒唐可笑。她表示詹姆斯·科米被解雇是因为他是一个可耻的党派黑客，发起这项调查的副局长麦凯布则被公认为是一个骗子，也被FBI所辞退。\n英国一名内阁大臣警告称，英国脱欧如果失败则可能会导致极右极端主义的暴增。交通大臣克里斯·格雷灵告诉《每日邮报》称如果英国脱欧失败，一千七百万支持脱欧的民众将会感觉收到了欺骗。格雷灵支持首相的脱欧协议，但是该协议有可能会在下周的国会中被否决。以下是克里斯·梅森的报道。克里斯·格雷灵的意思并不是如果脱欧受阻或是失败就会引起暴动，但是他也明确表示这也是他所担心的后果。他表示，人们不能低估这件事，如果脱欧失败，我们的政治将会有更多的反对声音，社会也将变得不宽容，国家也会更具民族主义。他之后补充道，如果70%同意脱欧的国会议员说不好意思，我们仍可以自由移动，民众将会转而反对主流政治。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>56</id>
        <date>January 15, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - South African President has urged men to unite against violence against women</title>
        <description>
            President Cyril Ramaphosa has urged South African men to unite against what he described as a national crisis of violence against women.
        </description>
        <cover>images/south-africa-deer.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190115_1616410ErG.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard. The British Prime Minister Theresa May has warned that failing to ensure the country leaves the EU would be a catastrophic and unforgivable breach of trust in British democracy. Just two days before a crucial parliamentary vote on her Brexit deal that she is expected to lose, Mrs. May has written in a newspaper article that MPs must not let the people down. Chris Mason reports from Westminster. We stand at the start of a momentous week at Westminster. The government is just a few days away from a widely expected defeat over its Brexit plan and the stakes already towering have grown higher. The Sunday Times reveals the government fears losing its ability to govern in the event of defeat on Tuesday. Its advisers have warned that back benches could seize control of Parliamentary business and so for instance legally compel the government to request that Brexit is delayed. Rarely in recent times has had been so much uncertainty about the government and the country's future.\nPresident Cyril Ramaphosa has urged South African men to unite against what he described as a national crisis of violence against women. He was launching an election manifesto for the governing ANC in the port city of Durban. Andrew Harding reports. President Cyril Ramaphosa urged every man in Durban's packed stadium to stand and they did. He said women were being raped and killed on a continuous basis in South Africa. It was a national crisis, he said, and we must pledge to end it. It was a passionate and unexpected moment. Forty thousand rapes are reported here every year, almost certainly a fraction of the real total. And President Ramaphosa said it was time South Africa took steps to ensure that it was no longer defined by the crisis of gender-based violence.\nJulian Castro, the former mayor of San Antonio in Texas has launched his bid for the US presidency in 2020. The 44-year-old joins Tulsi Gabbard and former Maryland Congressman John Delaney in the race for the Democratic nomination. David Willis in Washington has more details. He gave a speech at the Democratic National Convention four years ago and was the youngest member of Barack Obama's cabinet. More than anything else, he's looking to become America's first hispanic president and it's a real American dream story. And he, Mr. Castro said today that his grandmother Victoria, who came to the United States from Mexico nearly a century ago would have been amazed to know that one of her grandchildren would end up a member of the US congress. The other would end up running for president. This is the world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n欢迎收听BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。英国首相特蕾莎·梅警告称脱欧失败将会对英国民主制度信任度造成灾难性和不可原谅的破坏。两天之后，国会将会对她的脱欧协议进行投票，预计她将会输掉。梅在一篇报纸文章中写到，议员绝对不能让人们失望。以下是克里斯·梅森从威斯敏斯特发来的报道。在威斯敏斯特，至关重要的一周即将开启。大部分人预计几天之后政府的脱欧计划将面临失败，原本失败几率很高的计划还在不断增加。《星期日泰晤士报》表示政府害怕在周二的落败中失去执政的机会。其顾问警告称普通议员可能会夺取议会的控制权，并将合法强迫政府推迟脱欧计划。最近几次关于政府和国家的未来充满了不确定性，这是很罕见的。\n总统西里尔·拉马福萨要求南非人民团结起来应对针对女性的全国性暴力危机。他在港口城市德班对执政的“南非非洲人国民大会”发起了一项竞选宣言。以下是安德鲁·哈丁的报道。总统西里尔·拉马福萨要求德班体育场的人全体起立，人们纷纷响应。他表示在南非不断地有女性被强奸的和杀害。他表示，这已经成为了国家危机，我们必须保证结束它。这一刻人们情绪激动也出人意料。南非每年报告的强奸案例达4万多起，这也占据全国女性总数很大一部分。总统拉马福萨表示，南非是时候该采取措施彻底结束这场性别暴力危机了。\n前德克萨斯州圣安东尼奥的市长朱利安·卡斯特罗拉开2020竞选大幕。44岁的卡斯特罗将与图尔西·加伯德，以及前马里兰岛国会议员约翰·德莱尼参加民主党的提名竞选。以下是大卫·威利斯在华盛顿的详细报道。他曾在四年前的民主党全国代表大会发表了演讲，也是巴拉克·奥巴马内阁中最年轻的成员。他现在最想做的就是成为美国第一位西班牙裔总统，而这也是一个真实的美国梦的故事。卡斯特罗表示他的祖母维多利亚一个世纪之前从墨西哥来到美国，如果她还活着也会为她的孙辈感到惊讶，因为他们一人当上了美国议员，另一人正在竞选美国总统。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>57</id>
        <date>January 16, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The cockpit voice recorder from a Lion airplane that crashed in October has been recovered</title>
        <description>
            Indonesian officials say they have recovered the cockpit voice recorder from a Lion airplane that crashed into the Java Sea in October.
        </description>
        <cover>images/crashed-lion-airplane.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190116_5057716QLA.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Neil Nunes with the BBC News.\nTurkey has responded angrily to President Trump's threat to devastate the country economically if it attacks Kurdish forces in Syria after US troops pull out. But Mr. Trump also asked Kurdish groups who are regarded by Ankara as terrorists not to provoke Turkey. More from Barbara Plett Usher.\nMr. Trump has threatened Turkey with devastating its economy if the Turks attacked these Kurds after the Americans leave and now the Turkish President has responded and he's said, you know, we expect you to behave like a strategic partner. You cannot equate terrorists with partners. In the meantime, Mr. Trump has actually given away a few details about this troop withdrawal. He talked about a twenty-mile safe zone presumably along the border between Turkey and northern Syria. He also said if Islamic State militants come back in Syria, we can always attack them from a nearby military base, responding to criticism that the US is retreating and allowing a situation where Islamic State can regroup.\nIndonesian officials say they have recovered the cockpit voice recorder from a Lion airplane that crashed into the Java Sea in October. Reports say it was found eight meters deep under mud on the seafloor. Officials say human remains were also discovered. Rebecca Henschke reports.\nThe budget airline flight lost contact shortly after takeoff from Jakarta airport and crashed into the Java Sea, killing all 189 people on board. Investigators have said in their early reports that the plane, a nearly brand new Boeing 737 MAX 8 had technical problems. And some families of the victims have started legal action against Boeing.\nThe head of a South Korean animal rescue organization CARE is under pressure to resign after a whistleblower accused her of secretly instructing her staff to euthanize dozens of stray dogs. More details now from Celia Hatton.\nOne of CARE's former employees said the organization had been covering up its real stance on animal euthanasia, charging the CARE CEO Park So-yeon had lied about killing more than two hundred dogs due to the organization's public stance against the practice. Ms. Park reportedly told the charity supporters some of the animals that had actually been killed had instead been adopted in order to encourage donations. CARE has said that a small number of dogs were euthanized, mostly because of illness and had tried its best to respond to what it said was an overwhelming number of requests to save animals.\nBBC world news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼尔·努内斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n特朗普威胁称，如果土耳其在美国撤军后袭击库尔德武装，就会在经济上摧毁土耳其，土耳其对此作出了愤怒的回应。但特朗普也要求被土耳其视为恐怖分子的库尔德武装不要挑衅土耳其。以下是芭芭拉·普莱特-亚瑟的报道。\n特朗普威胁称如果美国撤军后土耳其袭击库尔德武装，美国将会摧毁其国内经济；土耳其总统回应称我们把你当作战略伙伴，你不能把恐怖分子也当作伙伴。同时，特朗普也给出了一些撤军的详细信息。他谈到可能要在土耳其和叙利亚北部之间建立一个20公里的安全区。他表示如果伊斯兰国组织武装从叙利亚返回，美国可以从附近的军事基地赶来对抗他们，这也是特朗普对美国撤军和任由伊斯兰国组织复苏的批评做出的回应。\n印度尼西亚官方表示他们已经找到了去年10月坠入爪洼海的狮航客机驾驶舱上的语音记录器。报道称，这个记录器在海床下8米深的淤泥中被找到。官员表示他们也找到了遇难者的遗体。以下是蕾贝卡·亨施客的报道。\n该趟廉价航班从雅加达机场起飞后不久失联，并坠入爪洼海，机上189人全部遇难。调查人员在早期报告中称这架近乎全新的波音737 MAX 8飞机存在技术问题。一些遇难人员家属已经对波音公司提起法律诉讼。\n韩国动物营救组织CARE的负责人正面临着辞职的压力，因为有告密者指控她秘密地让员工对数十条流浪犬实施安乐死。以下是西利亚·哈顿的报道。\nCARE的一名前员工称该组织一直都在掩盖对于动物实施安乐死的真实立场，并指控其CEO朴素妍掩盖了杀死200条狗的事实，因为对动物实施安乐死与该组织的公开立场相背。据报道，朴素妍告诉慈善组织支持者们，这些实际上已经被杀的动物都被人领养了，以此鼓励捐赠。CARE表示一小部分狗被安乐死了，大多是因为生病，并且他们已经应人们的要求尽最大努力去拯救动物了。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>58</id>
        <date>January 17, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Brazil loosed the country's gun laws</title>
        <description>
            The Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro is due to sign a decree today loosening the country's gun laws.Mr. Bolsonaro who took office earlier this month, made the pledge a key part of his presidential campaign.
        </description>
        <cover>images/red-gold-shotgun-shells.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190117_5212103GWt.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News. Hello. Britain's Prime Minister is facing defeat later in a parliamentary vote on her proposed terms for the country's departure from the European Union. The vote comes more than two and a half years after a referendum in which British voters opted to leave the EU. The government's opponents argue the withdrawal deal is legally and constitutionally unsound. Here's our political correspondent Ian Watson. To say this is a big day for Prime Minister would be a huge understatement. Everyone keeps talking about the worst, which is hard since well last week, but this time she is on a verge of suffering potentially a major defeat on a deal she's negotiated with the EU. More than a hundred of MPs are still saying they cannot support it. We'll see if she can bring those numbers down today. There'll be various changes proposed to her deal which might make it look a bit more attractive. But as things stand, it looks as though the Prime Minister will not be able to get enough support to get a deal through parliament.\nA senior member of the Afghan Taliban has been detained in Pakistan. Taliban sources said the man held is Hafiz Mohibullah, the Religious Affairs Minister in the Taliban administration in Afghanistan before 2001. Our Pakistan correspondent Secunder Kermani has more details. He had been living in the northern Pakistani city of Peshawar for a number of years, but he was detained by Pakistani authorities in the past few days. And now our sources, the senior Taliban figures speaking to us on condition of anonymity, has said that this move is part of a strategy by Pakistan to pressurize the Taliban into taking part in peace talks with US officials which they have already been doing it in Qatar and the United Arab Emirates but also crucially taking part in peace talks with the Afghan government who so far the Taliban have refused to meet because they dismissed them as puppets.\nThe Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro is due to sign a decree today loosening the country's gun laws. Mr. Bolsonaro who took office earlier this month, made the pledge a key part of his presidential campaign. Candace Piette reports. Brazilians are desperate for better public security. In 2017, almost 64,000 people were murdered, two thirds died from gunshot wounds. But the latest polls say most Brazilians believe making firearms more available will pour gas on a raging fire. That hasn't stopped President Bolsonaro who says that by freeing up the existing gun laws, he can reduce crime. As a first step, Brazilians will only have to renew their gun license every ten years instead of five. They also won't have to work so hard to convince the police they need a firearm. BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是斯图尔特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。英国首相的脱欧计划面临着在议会投票中失败的危险。两年半之前，英国举行全民公投，英国公民选择了离开欧盟。政府反对党认为该脱欧方案在法律上和宪法上都是不稳妥的，以下是本台政治通讯员伊恩·华生的报道。首相今天将会面临一个巨大的考验，这么说有点轻描淡写。从上周开始每个人都在讨论着最坏的结果，而现在她濒临遭受一场重大协议失败，她曾与欧盟商讨该协议。一百多名议员仍表示他们不会支持该方案。今天她是否能减少反对者的人数，我们拭目以待。她的方案还会有多项修改提议，这也许让它看起来更有吸引力。从目前的情况来看，首相将不会得到足够的支持让这份方案从国会通过。\n一名阿富汗塔利班高级成员在巴基斯坦被捕。塔利班消息人员称哈菲兹·穆哈卜拉是阿富汗塔利班政府2001年之前的宗教事务部长。以下是本台巴基斯坦通讯员赛康德·科芒尼的报道。他在巴基斯坦北部城市白沙瓦生活了数年，但是在几天前被巴基斯坦政府拘捕。我们的消息人士，匿名塔利班高级官员告诉我们称，巴基斯坦此举是在向塔利班施压，让他们加入到与美国官员的和平谈判中来，在卡塔尔和阿联酋他们已经开始了和平谈判。另外，这也是在迫使塔利班与阿富汗政府进行和平谈判，但是目前为止塔利班都拒绝与其会谈，因为他们认为阿富汗政府就是傀儡。\n巴西总统雅伊尔·博索纳罗今天将会签署一项法令，放宽该国的枪支管制。博索纳罗本月初上台，这项措施就是他的总统竞选时的重要承诺。以下是坎迪斯·皮尔特的报道。巴西民众正渴求一个更好的公共安全环境。2017年，大约有64000人被谋杀，三分之二死于枪伤。最新的民调显示大多数的巴西人认为放宽枪支管控无异于火上浇油。但这并没有阻止总统博索纳罗签署该法令，他表示通过放宽现行的枪支法规，可以减少犯罪。作为第一步，巴西民众未来只需每隔10年更新枪支执照，之前为5年。而且现在他们可以更加容易地说服警察他们需要一把枪。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>59</id>
        <date>January 21, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - A Gift of Love</title>
        <description>
            "Can I see my baby?" the happy new mother asked.When the bundle was nestled in her arms and she moved the fold of cloth to look upon his tiny face, she gasped. The doctor turned quickly and looked out the tall hospital window. The baby had been born without ears.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/ear-structure.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/a-gift-of-love.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**A Gift of Love**\n**爱的礼物**\n"Can I see my baby?" the happy new mother asked.\n“我可以看看我的宝宝吗？”初为人母的她开心地问道。\nWhen the bundle was nestled in her arms and she moved the fold of cloth to look upon his tiny face, she gasped. The doctor turned quickly and looked out the tall hospital window. The baby had been born without ears.\n当裹着的婴儿放到她臂弯里，她掀开裹着婴儿的布，在看到他的小脸时，她不禁倒吸了一口气。医生快速地转过身，透过医院的高层窗户向外看去。婴儿生下来就没有耳朵。\nTime proved that the baby's hearing was perfect. It was only his appearance that was marred. When he rushed home from school one day and flung himself into his mother's arms, she sighed, knowing that his life was to be a succession of heartbreaks.\n时间证明婴儿的听力毫无问题，只是有损他的相貌。一天，当他匆匆从学校跑回家，扑向母亲的怀抱时，她叹了口气，意识到他的生活注定会受到一连串的打击。\nHe blurted out the tragedy. "A boy, a big boy...called me a freak."\n他脱口诉说遭到的不幸：“一个男孩，一个大个子男孩……他喊我怪胎。”\nHe grew up, handsome except for his misfortune. A favorite with his fellow students, he might have been class president, but for that. He developed a gift, a talent for literature and music.\n他长大了，虽然不幸但还是长得挺帅。颇受同学的欢迎，要不是有缺陷，他很可能当了班长。他对文学和音乐很有天赋和潜质。\nBut you might mingle with other young people, his mother reproved him, but felt a kindness in her heart.\n“但你可能会和其他年轻人一样。”母亲责备地说，但从心底里觉得很欣慰。\nThe boy's father had a session with the family physician... "Could nothing be done?"\n男孩的父亲与家庭医生商量……“难道真无法补救吗？”\nI believe I could graft on a pair of outer ears, if they could be procured, the doctor decided. So the search began for a person who would make such a sacrifice for a young man.\n“我认为可以移植一双外耳，如果能够找到的话。”医生做了决定，于是他们开始寻求一个愿意为这个年轻人做出牺牲的人。\nTwo years went by.Then, "You're going to the hospital, son. Mother and I have someone who will donate the ears you need. But it's a secret." said the father.\n两年过去了。对儿子说，“孩子，你要住院了。我和你妈找到愿意为你捐献耳朵的人了。但要求保密。”\nThe operation was a brilliant success, and a new person emerged. His talents blossomed into genius, and school and college became a series of triumphs.\n手术获得了巨大成功，一个新人诞生了。他的潜力发展成一个天才，在中学和大学都取得了一连串的成功。\nLater he married and entered the diplomatic service. "but I must know," he asked his father, "Who gave me the ears? Who gave me so much? I could never do enough for him."\n后来他结婚了，进入外交行业工作。一天，他问父亲：“是谁给我的耳朵？谁给了我那么多？我做多少都无法报答他/她。”\nI do not believe you could, said the father, "but the agreement was that you are not to know...not yet."\n“我也这样认为，”父亲说，“但是协议上说你不能知道……还不到时候。”\nThe years kept their profound secret, but the day did come. One of the darkest days that ever pass through a son. He stood with his father over his mother's casket. Slowly, tenderly, the father stretched forth a hand and raised the thick, reddish brown hair to reveal that the mother had no outer ears.\n他们的秘密遵守了很多年，但这天终于来了，这也是儿子度过的最黑暗的日子。他和父亲站在母亲的棺材前，慢慢地，轻柔地，父亲向前伸出一只手，掀开母亲浓密的、红褐色的头发：母亲竟然没有耳朵！\n"Mother said she was glad she never let her hair be cut," he whispered gently, "and nobody ever thought mother less beautiful, did they?"\n“你母亲说过她很高兴，她从不理发，”父亲轻柔地低声说，“但没人觉得母亲没以前美丽，是吧？”
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>60</id>
        <date>January 21, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - President Trump will hold a second summit with the North Korean leader Kim Jong Un</title>
        <description>
            President Trump will hold a second summit with the North Korean leader Kim Jong Un near the end of February. It's expected to focus on the denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-kim-jong-un.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0119_02318443ed.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Julie Candler.\nPresident Trump will hold a second summit with the North Korean leader Kim Jong Un near the end of February. It's expected to focus on the denuclearization of the Korean Peninsula. The White House didn't say anything about how to advance the nuclear talks that have made very little progress since the first summit last year.\nThe White House has condemned the categorically false allegations that President Trump ordered his former lawyer Michael Cohen to lie to congress about his business links with Russia before he took office. If substantiated, the allegations could trigger impeachment proceedings. Mr. Trump's current lawyer has denied the claims.\nThe U.S. government has confirmed that an American-born Iranian journalist has been detained since Sunday as a material witness in an undisclosed federal investigation. A federal court order said Marzieh Hashemi is expected to be released after she testifies before a grand jury.\nThe rights group Amnesty International says its analysis of satellite imagery of the town of Rann in northwest Nigeria reveals extensive destruction following an attack by Boko Haram militants on Monday. Amnesty said the images confirmed previous descriptions of the town as like a graveyard.\nPolice in the Sudanese capital Khartoum have opened fire at mourners attending the funeral of a man killed during clashes with the security forces. Doctors have announced a strike at a large private hospital after a doctor and a boy were also shot dead on Thursday.\nHuman rights groups in Zimbabwe said at least 12 people have been killed this week during violent protests sparked by a sharp increase in the price of fuel. Hospitals and clinics have reportedly treated more than 70 people who have been shot by security forces.\nHundreds more Central American migrants have crossed into Mexico without waiting for a humanitarian visa. They are joining the caravans heading towards the U.S border.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nJulie Candler为您播报BBC新闻。\n特朗普总统将与朝鲜领导人金正恩举行第二次会晤，时间在二月末左右。这次会晤预计将以朝鲜半岛无核化为主题。美国政府并未就如何推进无核化会谈表态。自去年第一次特金会以来，无核化事宜进展缓慢。\n特朗普政府谴责具有本质性错误的指控。该指控称特朗普总统命令其前律师迈克尔·科恩向国会撒谎，而撒谎内容与特朗普上任前通俄有关。如果上述指控得到证实，则会触发弹劾流程。特朗普的现任律师否认了上述指控。\n美国政府已确认，某在美伊朗裔从周日开始就被拘禁，声称此人是某秘密联邦调查的重要证人。联邦法院的命令中写道，名为哈希米的这名美伊朗裔预计在大陪审团面前提供证词后才能得到释放。\n人权组织国际特设组织称其分析了尼日利亚西北莱恩镇的卫星影像，发现周一博科圣地的激进分子实施袭击后，该镇受到了大范围的破坏。国际特设组织表示，卫星影像证实了此前人们对该镇的描述——与墓地别无两样。\n苏丹首都喀土穆的警方向参加某男子葬礼的哀悼者们开火。这名男子在与安全部队发生冲突期间被杀。多名医生宣布罢工，因为某私立医院内，一名医生和一名男孩在周四被射杀身亡。\n津巴布韦的多个人权组织表示，本周至少12人在暴力抗议中死亡。抗议的导火索是燃料价格飙升。据报道，多家医院和诊所已医治了70多人。这些人都是被安全部队所伤。\n又有数百名中美洲移民进入了墨西哥，但还未等到获得人道主义签证。这些移民跟移民大潮一起向美国边境进发。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>61</id>
        <date>January 22, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The partial shutdown of the US government has entered its fifth week</title>
        <description>
            The partial shutdown of the US government has entered its fifth week with Donald Trump saying he'll make what he described as a major announcement on Saturday.
        </description>
        <cover>images/gov-snow-down.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190121_2346846JsJ.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Rosemary Crick with the BBC News. Hello. At least 21 people have been killed and more than seventy injured in a huge explosion at a leaking oil pipeline in central Mexico. Hundreds of people were scrambling to steal some of the fuel when they were engulfed in flames. Electra Nasmyth reports. The blast happened near the Tula refinery in Hidalgo state. Video footage showed a huge fireball and desperate people running away from the flames. One man described having to claw his way through charred bodies as he tried to help. The state oil company Pemex blamed on illegal fuel tap for the fire, a dangerous but highly profitable business which the government says caused Mexico three billion dollars last year. The Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador announced a major crackdown in December but the controvertial plan has led to feul shortages and long lines at petrol stations in some states.\nThe office of the US Special Counsel Robert Mueller has disputed the accuracy of a news report that President Trump ordered his former lawyer Michael Cohen to lie to Congress. Buzzfeed News has said that Mr. Trump instructed Mr. Cohen to lie about plans to build a Trump Tower in Moscow. Buzzfeed said it stood by its report. David Willis reports. Another roller coaster week for the president ended with claims that he may have sought to obstruct justice. An impeachable offense if true, but true, it may not be. The White House flatly denied the claim, and later it emerged that the Special Counsel who is investigating allegations of collusion between the Trump campaign and Russia didn't buy it either. Buzzfeed's description of specific statements to the Special Council's office are not accurate read a statement. President Trump was clearly ecstatic. Last night, he tweeted "a very sad day for journalism, but a great day for our country".\nThe partial shutdown of the US government has entered its fifth week with Donald Trump saying he'll make what he described as a major announcement on Saturday. Reports from Washington suggest that senior officials, including the Vice President Mike Pence, have come up with new proposals to resolve the crisis.\nThe government of Burkina Faso has unexpectedly resigned. No explanation was given. But the tiny west African nation has been hit by a wave of Jihadi's attacks and kidnappings of foreigners, including a Canadian geologist who was found dead earlier this week.\nFor the first time, officials in Pakistan have briefed parliament on the country's growing export of human hair. A statement by the Commerce Ministry said Pakistan earned 1.6 million dollars from the sale of hair in the last five years. China, which has an expanding beauty industry, was one of the main buyers taking more than a hundred thousand kilos of hair from Pakistan. BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是罗丝玛丽·克里克，欢迎收听BBC新闻。墨西哥中部输油管道泄漏引发爆炸，导致至少21人死亡，70多人受伤。当时数百人正争夺着偷窃燃油，之后大火将他们吞没。以下是伊莱克特拉·内史密斯的报道。大火发生在伊达尔戈州图拉精炼厂附近。视频显示现场燃起了巨大的火球，惊慌失措的人们正在逃离火焰。一人描述称，他不得不扒开烧焦的尸体来帮助幸存者。墨西哥国家石油公司将火灾归咎于非法偷油，这在墨西哥是一个危险但却高利润的行为，政府称去年因此造成了30亿美元的损失。墨西哥总统奥夫拉多尔在去年12月宣布进行了严打活动，但是这项有争议的计划导致一些州燃油短缺，加油站前也排起长队。\n美国特别检察官罗伯特·米勒的办公室称特朗普指示其原私人律师迈克尔·科恩向国会说谎的报道不准确。Buzzfeed新闻称特朗普曾指示迈克尔·科恩在莫斯科建造特朗普大楼的问题上向国会说谎。Buzzfeed新闻认为他们的报道是正确的。以下是大卫·威利斯的报道。对于特朗普而言，这又是一个大起大落的一周，人们说他试图阻碍司法公正。如果消息属实，这是一个可以招致弹劾的罪行，但这或许不是真的。白宫明确地否认了该指控，之后正在调查特朗普竞选团队与俄罗斯涉嫌勾结的特别检察官也表示不认可该报道。Buzzfeed在一份声明中表示，特别检察官办公室的声明是不准确的。特朗普本人也明显很激动。昨天晚上，他在推特中表示这是新闻业悲哀的一天，但却是美国伟大的一天。\n美国政府停摆已经持续了到第五周，特朗普宣布他将在周六做出重要宣布，华盛顿的报道称，包括副总统迈克·彭斯在内的高级官员已经想出了解决危机的方案。\n布基纳法索政府出乎意料地解散了，官方没有给出解释。这个西非小国已经遭到了一波圣战组织的袭击，并有外国人遭到绑架，其中就包括一名加拿大地理学家。他在上周早些时候被发现死亡。\n巴基斯坦官员第一次向议会汇报了该国不断增长的假发出口业务。商务部长的报告称巴基斯坦最近5年里从假发销售中赚了160万美元。中国的美容美发业正不断扩张，成为了巴基斯坦假发的主要买家，进口了超过10万千克的假发。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>62</id>
        <date>January 23, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - India's most senior politician Amit Shah recovered from swine flu</title>
        <description>
            One of India's most senior politicians Amit Shah, the president of the governing party BJP has been released from hospital in the capital Delhi after being treated for swine flu.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pink-pig-figurine.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190122_2712310eEx.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Eileen McHugh with the BBC News. The Constitutional Court in the Democratic Republic of Congo has officially declared the opposition candidate Felix Tshisekedi, the winner of last month's presidential election. It rejected an appeal by another opposition candidate Martin Fayulu who's accused Mr. Tshisekedi and the outgoing president of striking a deal. Mr. Fayulu insists he is the only legitimate president of Congo. I call on the whole international community to not recognize a power that has neither legitimacy nor legal quality to represent the Congolese people. Dear compatriots, I launch an urgent appeal to our people so that they take charge and organize peaceful demonstrations across the whole of the national territory in order to defend its sovereignty.\nDemocrats in the US Congress have dismissed a proposal by President Trump on immigration policy, which aims to end the partial shutdown of the US government. Mr. Trump offered what he called a compromise in return for funding his border wall with Mexico, but the Democrats say President Trump is only giving back what he had earlier taken away. From Washington, here's David Willis. Senior Democrats find the very notion of a wall repugnance and believe the president is holding government workers' hostage in a desperate bid to make good on a central promise of his campaign. They declared his new offer a nonstarter and continue to insist that only once the government is reopened will they discuss border security. Where the dispute goes from here is anyone's guess, but White House officials are not ruling out the possibility that the president could walk away from the negotiations and circumvent Congress by declaring a national emergency.\nOne of India's most senior politicians Amit Shah, the president of the governing party BJP has been released from hospital in the capital Delhi after being treated for swine flu. Our South Asia editor Jill McGivering reports. Amit Shah is one of the closest aides of India's Prime Minister Narendra Modi and seen as a key architect of his campaign to be reelected. So there's been a particular focus on his health when he was treated for swine flu in one of the country's top hospitals. Now he says he's made a full recovery. In recent years, India has seen a series of outbreaks of the virus which is highly contagious and can be fatal. Already this month, almost fifty people have died in Rajasthan and more than a thousand tested positive. Jill McGivering. And that's the latest BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是艾琳·麦克尤，欢迎收听BBC新闻。刚果民主共和国的宪法法院正式宣布反对党候选人费利克斯·齐塞克迪在上个月的总统大选中胜出。法院拒绝了另一位反对党候选人马丁·法尤卢的上诉申请，他指控齐塞克迪与即将卸任的总统进行了交易。法尤卢表示他才是刚果唯一合法的总统。我呼吁国际社会不要认可该政权，因为它既不合理也不合法，不能代表刚果人民。亲爱的同胞们，我向我们的人民发出了紧急呼吁，希望他们能过行动起来，并在全国范围内组织和平的示威活动来推翻这个政权。\n美国国会的民主党否决了特朗普在移民问题上的提议，该提议旨在解决美国政府部分部门停摆的问题。特朗普称该提议是他做出的一个妥协，以此来为他的墨西哥边境墙计划换取资金。但是民主党称特朗普只是让出了他之前拿走的东西罢了。以下是大卫·威利斯在华盛顿的报道。一名资深民主党人表示边境墙的提议令人厌恶，他认为特朗普通过让政府工人停工来实现他在竞选时做的承诺。他们称特朗普的新提议毫无意义，他们依然表示只有政府重启，才会讨论边境安全问题 。这项争端何时结束谁也不知道，但是白宫官员不排除总统将会退出协商并避开国会来宣布国家进入紧急状态。\n印度最资深的政治家之一，同时也是执政党印度人民党党首的阿玛特·沙阿在首都德里的医院接受猪流感治疗后，现已出院。以下是本台南亚编辑吉尔·麦吉弗林的报道。阿玛特·沙阿是印度首相纳伦德拉·莫迪最亲密的助手之一，并被认为在莫迪连任选举中起了关键的作用。所以，当他在印度顶级医院接受猪流感治疗时，人们对他的健康格外关注。现在，她表示已经完全康复了。在最近几年，印度发生了一系列的猪流感疫情爆发，这种病毒传染性极强，还有可能导致死亡。本月，在拉贾斯坦邦已有55人死于猪流感，还有一千多人被检测出感染病毒。吉尔·麦吉弗林报道。以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>63</id>
        <date>January 24, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - South Africa turned down a request from Zimbabwe for an emergency loan of 1.2 billion dollars</title>
        <description>
            South Africa has disclosed that it turned down a request from Zimbabwe for an emergency loan of 1.2 billion dollars in December.Soon after the request was rejected, the Zimbabwean government was forced to announce a steep increase in the price of fuel, sparking angry protest.
        </description>
        <cover>images/one-hundred-trillion-dollars-zimbabwe.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190123_1215747hQx.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Eileen McKue with the BBC News.\nSouth Africa has disclosed that it turned down a request from Zimbabwe for an emergency loan of 1.2 billion dollars in December. Soon after the request was rejected, the Zimbabwean government was forced to announce a steep increase in the price of fuel, sparking angry protest. Perm Zufanany reports from Johannesburg.\nAsked whether loan was turned down, Treasury spokesperson Jabulani Sikhakhane told the BBC Zimbabwe is in a dire financial situation, but South Africa does not have that kind of money. It is believed that Zimbabwe had hoped to use the cash injection to stabilize the ailing economy and resolve fuel shortages in the country. President Emmerson Mnangagwa announced a drastic fuel hike last week, leading to widespread and violent protest which saw at least 12 people killed in clashes with security forces.\nIsrael has announced that it struck a number of sites inside Syria as part of its increasingly open effort to dislodge Iranian forces there. The Russian Defense Ministry says four Syrian soldiers were killed, but monitors based in Britain say eleven people died in the attack. Israel said it was responding to Iranian rocket fire which intercepted on Sunday.\nEuropean Foreign Ministers are expected to impose sanctions today on two Russian military intelligence officers blamed by the West for a nerve agent attack in the British city of Salisbury last year. They're among nine people facing new EU penalties for using chemical weapons in breach of international treaties.\nEU Foreign Ministers meeting in Brussels have said it's up to Britain to decide what it wants to do next about Brexit, as the British Prime Minister Theresa May prepares to address parliament again. The Spanish Foreign Minister said she needed to come up with something substantially different to secure the backing of the British parliament. But our correspondent Rob Watson says Mrs. May's plan appears not to have deviated.\nI think people would say rather cynically that her hope is what it has been all along, but essentially those on the hard right of the Conservative Party enthusiastic about Brexit will be incredibly frightened about all this talk of efforts to stop Brexit or put a delay on it or have some other option and that those who are on the remain side of the Conservative Party will be utterly terrified at the prospect of a no-deal Brexit all together. So I think in many ways her plan hasn't changed very much and I don't think her tactics have changed very much. Now whether they'll work is an entirely different matter. Rob Watson reporting.\nThat's the latest BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是艾琳·麦克尤，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n南非披露称在12月拒绝了津巴布韦12亿美元的紧急贷款请求。请求遭拒后，津巴布韦政府被迫宣布大幅度上调燃油价格，这也导致了愤怒的抗议活动。以下是本·兰尼在约翰内斯堡的报道。\n当被问及贷款是否被拒后，财政部发言人亚布拉尼·斯卡哈尼告诉BBC称津巴布韦财政状况十分严峻，但是南非并没有那么多钱可供贷款。据称，津巴布韦曾希望用注入资金的方式来稳定国内病态的经济，解决国内的燃油短缺问题。上周埃默森·姆南加古瓦总统宣布大幅上调燃油价格，导致了大范围的暴力抗议活动，至少有12人在与安全部队的冲突中死亡。\n以色列宣布他们打击了叙利亚境内的多个目标地点，这是他们加大力度驱逐当地的伊朗武装计划的一部分。俄罗斯国防部表示有四名叙利亚士兵死亡，而驻英国的观察机构则表示有11人在袭击中丧生。以色列表示伊朗周日对其进行了火箭弹袭击，但被拦截，而这是对该袭击的反击。\n欧洲国家外交部长将于今天对两名俄罗斯军事情报人员实施制裁，西方国家指控他们去年用神经毒素袭击了英国城市索尔兹伯里。因违反国际条约使用化学武器，包括他们在内的9名人员将面临新的欧盟处罚。\n在布鲁塞尔会面的欧盟各国外交部长称接下来脱欧如何进行将由英国决定，英国首相特蕾莎·梅准备再次向国会发表讲话。西班牙外交部长表示她需要想出一个有本质上区别的方案来确保得到英国议会的支持。但我台记者罗勃·华生表示梅的计划似乎没有改变。\n我认为人们一都对特蕾莎·梅的希望持以讽刺，但本质上那些对脱欧保持乐观的保守党极右翼分子将非常害怕脱欧计划停止，或是被推迟，抑或是出现别的选择，保守党中剩下的一部分人将会非常害怕无协议脱欧的出现。所以，我认为她的计划在很多方面来说都没有太多的改变，并且我认为她的战略也没有太大的变动。现在，这些能否起作用都是另一回事了。罗勃·华生报道。\n以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>64</id>
        <date>January 24, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - A leader of an ethnic Pashtun Movement campaigning against enforced disappearances has been arrested</title>
        <description>
            The arrest of Alamzeb Mehsud and other members of the Pashtun Protection Movement came two days after the group held a rally in the southern city of Karachi. Amnesty International has urged the Pakistani authorities either to bring Mr. Mehsud to court or release him immediately.
        </description>
        <cover>images/pakistan-pashtun-leader.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190124_4722372eq2.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Chris Barrow with the BBC News. The President of Zimbabwe Emmerson Mnangagwa has returned home after breaking off from a foreign tour to address days of violent protests. He said chaos and insubordination would not be tolerated. Andrew Harding is in Harare. Mixed message from Mnangagwa. I think it was inevitable that he was gonna condemn the protesters. What I think was most surprising and interesting was quite how tough he was on his own security forces. These of course the men in the military, the police who staged the coup that brought the president to power that ousted Robert Mugabe more than a year ago. He basically warned them that if they were using indiscriminate violence that will be a betrayal, he said, of the new Zimbabwe and that heads would roll. Some people here are speculating that there are plots against Mr. Mnangagwa that perhaps a new coup is in the offing and Mnangagwa was taking a bit of a risk threatening them so publicly.\nA former US Marine arrested in Russia on suspicion of spying is appearing in court in Moscow. Paul Whelan is appealing against the decision to refuse him bail while he awaits trial. He was detained by Russian security agents late last month, allegedly as he received state secrets. Mr. Whelan insists he is innocent. The case has prompted speculation that Mr. Whelan may have been arrested in order to swap him for Russian citizens in the United States. Moscow denies this.\nActivists in Pakistan say a leader of an ethnic Pashtun Movement campaigning against enforced disappearances has been arrested on terrorism charges. Here is Anbarasan Ethirajan. The arrest of Alamzeb Mehsud and other members of the Pashtun Protection Movement came two days after the group held a rally in the southern city of Karachi. Amnesty International has urged the Pakistani authorities either to bring Mr. Mehsud to court or release him immediately. The movement has shaken Pakistan's powerful military with this campaign to end alleged abuses by security forces targeting ethnic Pashtuns in the northwestern region.\nBritish members of Parliament are stepping up their efforts to influence the Brexit process before a key vote next week on a European Union withdrawal plan backed by the Prime Minister Theresa May. A number of amendments have been put forward, including some by the opposition Labor Party. Norman Smith reports. Supporters of another referendum have been buoyed by Labor's decision to include in its motion opposing Mrs. May's deal, a call for Parliament to have the option of a vote to trigger another referendum. Backers of a so called People's Vote have described it as a big step forward. Mr. Corbin's office, however, have been a good deal more circumspect, insisting it simply reflects the Party's existing policy. BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，克里斯·巴洛为您播报BBC新闻。津巴布韦总统埃默森·姆南加古瓦已经中断了外交访问回国，来处理数日来的暴力抗议活动。他表示这种暴乱和反抗活动是不能容忍的。以下是安德鲁·哈丁在哈拉雷的报道。姆南加古瓦话中隐藏了多种含义。我认为他将不可避免地谴责抗议人员。我认为最令人吃惊也是最有意思的是，他将对自己的安全部队采取多严厉的手段。一年前，是这些军人和警察发动政变推翻了罗伯特穆加贝的政权，让姆南加古瓦上台。他曾警告称，如果他们滥用武力，将被视作对新津巴布韦的背叛，背叛者将遭受惩罚。一些人猜测称有人在密谋反对姆南加古瓦，或许有一场新的政变即将发生，而姆南加古瓦在冒险公开威胁他们。\n前美国海军陆战队员因涉嫌从事间谍活动被捕，现在他正在莫斯科的一家法院出庭受审。俄罗斯拒绝他在候审期间保释，保罗·惠兰正在对此提起上诉。他在上个月月末被俄罗斯安全人员拘留，指控他涉嫌获取国家机密。惠兰坚称他是无辜的。该案件引起人们怀疑，惠兰被捕是因为俄罗斯想用他来交换在美国的俄罗斯人员。莫斯科否认了这一说法。\n巴基斯坦的活动人士表示一名反对强制失踪的普什图族运动领导人因恐怖主义的指控被捕。以下是安德布里森·安迪罗杰的报道。阿拉姆泽伯·莫苏德以及其他普什图族保护运动成员在南部城市卡拉奇发动集会活动两天后被捕。大赦国际敦促巴基斯坦政府称要么把莫苏德交由法庭审理，要么立即释放他。该运动震动了巴基斯坦的强大军队，他们的运动是结束安全部队的虐待行为，他们在西北部地区攻击普什图少数民族。\n英国国会成员正在加紧步伐来影响脱欧进程，下周他们将会对首相特蕾莎梅的脱欧协议进行关键性的投票。脱欧协议收到了大量的修改意见，其中一些是由反对党工党提出的。以下是诺曼·史密斯的报道。寻求下一次全民公投的人得到了工党的支持，他们提出动议反对梅的方案，请求国会进行投票以进行下一次全民公投。所谓的“人民的投票”的支持者们将其看作是迈出的一大步。科尔宾的工党则表现得十分谨慎，称该决定明确反映了工党的现行政策。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>65</id>
        <date>January 25, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The sister of India's main opposition leader Rahul Gandhi has formally joined politics</title>
        <description>
            With just months to go for the national election, Ms Gandhi's appointment is being seen as a major push by the Congress Party to try and win back power in India. In 2014, it's suffered a humiliating defeat to Prime Minister Narendra Modi's BJP party.
        </description>
        <cover>images/gandhi-sister.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190125_5808811NpY.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Eileen McKue with the BBC News.\nThe sister of India's main opposition leader Rahul Gandhi has formally joined politics months ahead of general elections. Priyanka Gandhi Vadra has been appointed as one of the General Secretaries of the Congress Party. Here's Yogata Lemoye.\nWith just months to go for the national election, Ms Gandhi's appointment is being seen as a major push by the Congress Party to try and win back power in India. In 2014, it's suffered a humiliating defeat to Prime Minister Narendra Modi's BJP party. Questions have often been raised about the popularity of the Congress' President Rahul who is Priyanka Gandhi's brother. In comparison, she thought to be more charismatic and someone who connects easily with voters. The siblings come from India's leading political family. Their father, grandmother and great-grandfather all served as Prime Ministers of India.\nThe government of Zimbabwe has defended the operation by its security forces following violent protests over a sharp rise in fuel prices. The country's Human Rights Commission said opposition activists have been subjected to severe beatings. Andrew Harding is in Harare.\nA spokesman Nick Mangwana told the BBC that when things get out of hand, a bit of firmness is needed. The country's Human Rights Commission has accused the police and army of indiscriminate attacks on civilians as young as eleven. Soldiers in Harare were seen beating a large group of minibus drivers in the city on Tuesday evening. President Emmerson Mnangagwa's proposal of a national dialogue with opposition parties has been rejected by the MDC which insists that the authorities should first release several of its MPs and hundreds of civilians. The government says its tough economic reforms will continue, arguing that there can be no progress without pain. Some union leaders and human rights activists remain in hiding.\nRussia has given foreign military attaches a briefing on a contentious new missile system, and it again insisted it's in full compliance with a key arms control treaty dating back to the Cold War. The United States says it will pull out of the Intermediate-range Nuclear Forces Treaty unless Russia destroys the missiles as they breach its terms.\nThe authorities in Ethiopia have arrested a former government minister on suspicion of embezzlement. Bereket Simon, a close ally of the former Prime Minister Meles Zenawi was detained at his home early on Wednesday as well as the former head of a state-own company. There have been a string of arrests of ministers and officials associated with the governments of Mr. Meles and his successor since the reformist Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed took office\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是艾琳·麦克尤，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n印度主要反对党领袖拉胡尔·甘地的妹妹在大选前数月正式宣布从政。琵艳卡·甘地·瓦德拉已被任命为印度国大党秘书长之一。以下是约格塔·勒莫邪的报道。\n距离全国大选还有几个月的时间，琵艳卡·甘地的任命被视作是国大党重新夺回印度大权的重要一步。在2014年，该党惨败于纳伦德拉·莫迪总理的印度人民党。国大党主席拉胡尔的支持率一直受到人们的质疑，而他就是琵艳卡的哥哥。相比之下，她被认为更具魅力也更容易与选民进行联系。兄妹二人出身于印度主要的政治家族。他们的父亲、祖母以及曾祖父都曾担任印度总理。\n因燃油价格急剧上涨，津巴布韦爆发了暴力抗议活动，津巴布韦政府为其安全部队采取的行动进行了辩护。津巴布韦的人权委员会表示抗议人士遭到了严重的殴打。以下是安德鲁·哈丁在哈拉雷的报道。\n发言人尼克·莫古瓦那告诉BBC称，局势失控之后，需要一些维稳措施。该国的人权组织指控警方和军队肆意攻击小至11岁大的民众。有人在周二晚上看到哈拉雷的士兵殴打一群小型巴士司机。总统埃莫森·姆南加古瓦与反对党进行全国对话提议被民革运拒绝，他们坚持当局应该先释放数名议员以及数百名平民。政府称这项艰难的经济改革还将继续，他解释称不经历痛苦就不能取得进步。一些工会领导人和人权活动人士仍在躲藏之中。\n俄罗斯向国外武官简单介绍了一个充满争议的新导弹系统，俄罗斯再次坚称它完全符合冷战时期签订的一项关键武器管控条约。美国表示俄罗斯违反了《中导条约》，如果他们不销毁这些导弹，美国将会退出该条约。\n埃塞俄比亚当局以涉嫌贪污罪名逮捕了一名前政府部长。贝拉克特·西蒙曾是前总理梅莱斯·泽纳维的亲密盟友，他于周三早些时候在家中被捕，同时被捕的还有一名国有公司的前董事长。改革主义者阿比·艾哈迈德总理上台后逮捕了多名部长和官员，他们都与梅莱斯政府以及其继任者的政府有关联。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>66</id>
        <date>January 27, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The United States has recognized its interim president of Venezuela</title>
        <description>
            The United States has recognized its interim president of Venezuela, the head of the opposition national assembly, Juan Guaido. President Trump said he will use the full weight of America's economic and diplomatic power to restore Venezuelan democracy.
        </description>
        <cover>images/venezuela-juan-guaido.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0126_3659356afi.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Maria Marshall.\nThe United States has recognized its interim president of Venezuela, the head of the opposition national assembly, Juan Guaido. President Trump said he will use the full weight of America's economic and diplomatic power to restore Venezuelan democracy. The announcement came minutes after Mr. Guaido declared himself interim president during widespread anti-government protests in Caracas. He claimed to have the support from military and promised free elections. Regional powers, such as Brazil, Colombia, Chile and Peru have also given their backing to Mr. Guaido. In his reaction, Venezuela's president Nicolas Maduro said he is breaking off diplomatic relations with Washington. A leading Maduro ally says Juan Guaido has violated Venezuela's constitution. And he doesn't care what U.S and other countries in the America say. Reports say government forces have been firing tear gas during large opposition protests in Caracas.\nPresident Trump says he wants to go ahead with his State of Union address next Tuesday, despite concerns over security arising from the government shutdown. The House Speaker Nancy Pelosi responded by saying Mr. Trump will not give the speech in the House of Representatives chamber until the government was fully reopened.\nDonald Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen has postponed his testimony to congress due two weeks from now. According to his legal adviser Lanny Davis, the delay is because of ongoing threats to Mr. Cohen's family from President Trump.\nPolice in Arizona have arrested a nurse after a patient in a long-term vegetative state at a care facility gave birth. The 36-year old man is being charged with sexual assault and abusing a vulnerable adult.\nProsecutors in Germany have charged an Iraqi asylum seeker with the rape and murder of a 14-year old girl in a high-profile case. The suspect left Germany soon after the incident, but was tracked down.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nMaria Marshall为您播报BBC新闻。\n美国已承认委内瑞拉临时总统，即国民大会反对派领袖胡安·瓜伊多的身份。特朗普总统表示自己将竭尽全力，动用经济和外交手段来恢复委内瑞拉民主。美国做此宣布的数分钟之前，胡安·瓜伊多宣布自己担任临时总统一职。期间正值加拉加斯爆发大范围反政府抗议。瓜伊多称自己获得了军队的支持，并选举过程绝对自由。一些地区国家政府，比如巴西、哥伦比亚、智利、秘鲁也都表示支持瓜伊多。在对瓜伊多的宣布做出响应时，委内瑞拉总统马杜罗表示其政府将与美国政府断绝外交关系。某马杜罗的知名盟友表示，瓜伊多违背了委内瑞拉宪法。他也并不在意美国等美洲国家有何看法。有报道指出，政府军在加拉加斯发生大规模反对派抗议时使用了催泪弹。\n特朗普总统表示自己想继续下周二的国情咨文演讲，虽然有人担心政府停摆会造成安全问题。众议院议长南希·佩洛西对此回应称，特朗普不会在众议院进行国情咨文演讲的，除非政府停摆结束。\n特朗普前律师迈克尔·柯恩将向国会做证词的时间延后了两周。他的法律顾问戴维斯表示，此次推迟的原因是现在柯恩一家正受到特朗普总统的威胁。\n亚利桑那州警方逮捕了一名护士，因为一名长期处于植物状态的病人生了孩子。这名36岁的男护士被控性侵无自我保护能力的成年人。\n德国多位检察官起诉了一名寻求庇护的伊拉克人，罪名是奸杀14岁女孩。此案备受关注。该嫌疑人在作案后不久就离开德国，但后来被追捕到了行踪。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>67</id>
        <date>January 28, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The Czech tennis star Petra Kvitova is about to play for a first Grand Slam title</title>
        <description>
            The Czech tennis star Petra Kvitova is about to play for a first Grand Slam title since suffering hand injuries in a knife attack two years ago.She's facing Naomi Osaka of Japan in the Australian Open final in Melbourne.
        </description>
        <cover>images/czech-petra-kvitova.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190128_1039537Atr.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News with Sue Montgomery. The five-week standoff between President Trump and the Democrats that led to the longest shutdown in US history has been resolved, at least for the moment. Mr. Trump has signed bipartisan bill to fund the US government for the next three weeks. He did so without securing the 5.7 billion dollars he wanted for a wall along the Mexican border. Chris Buckler reports. Most commentators believe Mr. Trump had to back down because he was being blamed in the polls for a dispute that led to workers queuing at food banks and planes being grounded because of a lack of air traffic control staff. The Minority leader in the Senate, Chuck Schumer insists Democrats will not agree to money for the wall. Shutting down the government over a policy difference is self-defeating. It accomplishes nothing but pain and suffering. President Trump is also considering the option of declaring a national emergency at the border with Mexico that could allow him to build the wall from other funds, although it would probably face a legal challenge.\nUp to three hundred people are missing and feared dead in Brazil after a dam collapsed at a mining complex in the state of Minas Gerais. Nine bodies have been recovered so far. Julia Carneiro reports. A sea of slides swept through a green rural area near the city of Brumadinho, swallowing everything in its track. It was a regular weekday with over four hundred workers busy at the local valley headquarters, many having lunch in the cafeteria which was buried. The government has set up the crisis cabinet and firefighters will continue rescue operations today.\nThe Czech tennis star Petra Kvitova is about to play for a first Grand Slam title since suffering hand injuries in a knife attack two years ago. She's facing Naomi Osaka of Japan in the Australian Open final in Melbourne. Here's Russell Fuller. Kvitova's surgeon feared she was unlikely to be able to compete at the highest level ever again. She underwent surgery in the Czech Republic in December 2016, just hours after an intruder had burst into her apartment and slashed all the fingers on her playing hand. Last year Kvitova won five tour titles and like Osaka, will also become the world number one if she triumphs on the Rod Laver Arena. Osaka's story is also a remarkable one. Her stunning victory over Serena Williams in Septembers's US Open final was overshadowed by the American's row with umpire Carlos Ramos. But if the 21-year-old wins in Melbourne, she'll be the first player for eighteen years to win a second Grand Slam title in the event immediately following her first. BBC News.\n**参考译文：**\n苏·蒙哥马利为您播报BBC新闻。美国总统特朗普与民主党之间长达五周的对峙目前已暂时解决，这也成为美国历史上最长的一次停摆，特朗普已经签署了两党法案，在接下来的三周时间里为美国政府提供资金。该协议不包括57亿美元墨西哥边境墙资金。以下是克里斯·巴克勒的报道。大多数评论人士认为特朗普不得不做出让步，因为民调批评他造成了政府职工在食物救助站排队以及因缺少交通管制人员导致飞机无法起飞。参议院少数党领袖查克·舒默表示民主党将不会同意拨款给边境墙。因政策分歧而让政府停摆是自食其果，只会导致痛苦和灾难。特朗普也在考虑就墨西哥边境问题宣布国家进入紧急状态，这样他就有可能得到其他的资金用于边境墙的建造，这也有可能遇到法律问题。\n巴西米纳斯吉拉斯州的一座矿坑堤坝坍塌，导致将近300人失踪，并且恐怕已经遇难。目前只发现了9具遗体。以下是茱莉亚·卡内罗的报道。大量的泥浆冲进了布鲁玛基纽附近的农村绿地，流经之处全部被淹没。当时是一个正常的工作日，有超过400名工人当地峡谷总部里工作，很多人当时正在餐厅吃午餐，该餐厅现已被掩埋。政府现已成立了一个紧急内阁小组，消防员将会在今天继续进行营救活动。\n捷克网球明星佩特拉·科维托娃在两年前遇袭手部受刀伤之后，即将冲击第一个大满贯冠军。她将在墨尔本的澳大利亚网球公开赛决赛上对阵日本选手大坂娜奥米。以下是拉索·富勒的报道。科维托娃的外科医生曾担心她有可能再也不能在最高级别的赛场上比赛了。她在2016年12月在捷克共和国进行了手术，因为几小时前一名不法分子闯入她的住所，用刀划伤了她持拍的那只手的所有手指。去年，科维托娃获得了5个巡回赛冠军，如果她在罗德拉沃尔球场取胜也会像大坂娜奥米成为世界头号选手。大坂的故事也同样很精彩。她在去年9月份的美国公开赛上打败了塞雷娜·威廉姆斯，但是被美国与裁判卡洛斯·拉莫斯的分歧盖住了风头。如果这名21岁的选手在墨尔本胜出，她将成为18年来首位获得第一座大满贯后又连续获得大满贯的选手。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>68</id>
        <date>January 29, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - A bomb attack on a cathedral in the southern Philippines has killed more than twenty people</title>
        <description>
            The first device went off inside the cathedral on Jolo island where worshippers had gathered for Sunday Mass. A second bomb exploded in the car park as the security forces responded.
        </description>
        <cover>images/philippines-bomb-attack.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190129_4440786tPi.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is David Austin with the BBC News. A bomb attack on a cathedral in the southern Philippines has killed more than twenty people and injured dozens of others. The first device went off inside the cathedral on Jolo island where worshippers had gathered for Sunday Mass. A second bomb exploded in the car park as the security forces responded. Howard Johnson reports from Manila. The Defense Secretary of the Philippines Delfin Lorenzana issued a statement in which he strongly condemned the attack and urged the public to remain calm to deny terrorism a victory as he put it. Decades of fighting in the region between numerous armed groups and the Philippine Army has claimed the lives of more than 120,000 people and displaced around two million. The island of Jolo lies in the proposed Bangsamoro autonomous region, a political solution to the conflict brokered by the government and the Moro Islamic Liberation Front. Last week, voters in the area overwhelmingly backed the new region in a referendum.\nVenezuela' s top military envoy to the United States has recognized the opposition leader Juan Guaido as his country's interim president. Announcing his defection from the government of Nicolas Maduro, the defense attache Colonel Jose Luis Silva called for fresh elections. He urged what he called his brothers in the armed forces to help restore democracy. Today, I speak to the people of Venezuela, and especially to my brothers in the armed forces of the nation to recognize President Juan Guaido as the only legitimate president. This is all based on the constitution of our Republic that states that no person or institution can be above it.\nRescue teams in Brazil are restarting their search for survivors after a dam collapsed on Friday, unleashing a torrent of mud and industrial waste. Thirty four people are confirmed to have died. Fifty people were pulled alive from the sludge on Saturday before the rescue operation was paused overnight. The authorities say hopes of finding more survivors among the 250 still missing a slim. The dam is owned by Brazil's largest mining company Vale.\nThe American Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has welcomed what he called encouraging news from talks between the US envoy and the Afghan Taliban. He made the comments as the US diplomat Zalmay Khalilzad headed to Afghanistan to brief the government in Kabul on six days of talks in Qatar with the Taliban.\nCeremonies are taking place in the Russian city of St. Petersburg to mark the seventy fifth anniversary of the end of the siege of Leningrad as the city was then known. More than 800,000 people died during the siege. That's the latest BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·奥斯汀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。菲律宾南部发生了一起炸弹袭击事件，导致20多人死亡，多人受伤。第一枚炸弹在霍洛岛的一座教堂中爆炸，当时信众正聚在这里做弥撒。第二枚炸弹在安全部队到达时在停车场爆炸。以下是霍华德·约翰逊在马尼拉的报道。菲律宾国防部长德尔芬·洛伦扎纳发表声明，强烈谴责了该袭击并且呼吁群众保持冷静并否认恐怖主义取得胜利。在该地区，臭名昭著的武装分子和菲律宾军队已经斗争了几十年，造成了超过12万人死亡，两百万人流离失所。霍洛岛位于所谓的邦萨摩洛自治区内，它是菲律宾政府与摩洛伊斯兰解放阵线协商出来的政治解决方案。上周，当地的选民在全民公投大选票支持建立自治区。\n委内瑞拉驻美国最高武官承认反对党领袖胡安·瓜伊多为该国临时总统。国防专员何塞·路易斯·席尔瓦上校宣布脱离尼古拉斯·马杜洛的政府，并呼吁进行全新的选举。他号召了在军队中的兄弟们来帮助他重建民主国家。今天，我呼吁委内瑞拉民众、特别是我在军队中的兄弟们承认胡安·瓜伊多为唯一合法总统。这是基于我们共和国宪法的，任何个人和组织都不能僭越。\n巴西救援人员又重新开始了搜救行动，周五的时候一座水坝倒塌，大量的泥浆和工业废料倾泻了出来。34人已确认死亡。在周六夜间搜救行动中止之前，已有50人从淤泥中被救了出来。政府表示，找到失踪的250人中的幸存者希望很渺茫。这个水坝归巴西最大的采矿集团淡水河谷公司所有。\n美国国务卿迈克·彭佩奥称美国大使与阿富汗塔利班的谈判传来了振奋人心的消息。美国外交官扎尔梅·哈利勒扎德现已前往阿富汗，向其政府汇报在卡塔尔与塔利班长达6天的谈判结果。\n俄罗斯圣彼得堡正在举行活动庆祝列宁格勒保卫战结束75周年。超过80万人在那场战役中死亡。以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>69</id>
        <date>January 30, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - A powerful tornado has hit Cuba's capital Havana</title>
        <description>
            A powerful tornado has hit Cuba's capital Havana, killing at least three people. More than a hundred and seventy others were injured by the storm.
        </description>
        <cover>images/cuba-tornado.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190130_0133609XGE.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is David Austin with the BBC News.\nThe United Nation says the humanitarian situation in Yemen is now deeply precarious, and any further destabilization could provoke a famine. The warning from the UN's World Food Program comes as pressure mounts on a month-old ceasefire in the port city of Hodeida, which is a vital gateway for aid supplies to Yemen. In the last few days, a wheat storage facility and a camp for displaced people have come under fire. The UN humanitarian coordinator Lise Grande told the BBC that the food situation across the country remain desperate.\nThere are twenty million people in this country who don't know if they're gonna eat today. Two hundred and thirty-eight thousand people are as we speak, starving. We can't describe this crisis more starkly and this is why humanitarians across the country are insisting that everybody do everything possible to end this conflict. The time has come.\nInvestigators say the captain of a Bangladeshi aircraft which crashed at Kathmandu airport last March was under stress and emotionally disturbed during the flight. All four crew members and forty-seven out of sixty-seven passengers died after the US-Bangla Airline flight crashed. Here is Jill McGivering.\nThe investigator's report suggests the captain was extremely upset during the short flight. He was irritable, tense, moody and aggressive at various times. He said I'm tired because he's slept poor the previous night. He talked obsessively to his young copilot about a colleague's criticism of his performance as a trainer which deeply upset him and his plans to resign. As the plane came into land, his behavior was impulsive and inappropriate, it's said, and he made a series of mistakes which proved fatal for so many of those on board.\nPolice in southern Mexico say at least ten people have been killed in a shoot-out between two local armed groups. The security spokesman in the state of Guerrero said the gun fight took place on a highway in the town of Chilapa had lasted for three hours. Witnesses said the gun fight started when an armed gang attempted to drive through districts controlled by another local militia.\nA powerful tornado has hit Cuba's capital Havana, killing at least three people. More than a hundred and seventy others were injured by the storm. The Cuban President Miguel Diaz-Canel said on Twitter that the damage in the city had been severe. Pictures posted online showed collapsed buildings, crushed cars and fallen trees.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·奥斯汀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n联合国表示也门地区的人道主义现状十分严峻，如果局势进一步恶化将可能导致饥荒。也门港口城市荷台达是救援物资进入的重要关口，联合国粮食计划署的警告给该地维系一个月的停火增加了压力。在过去的几天里，一处小麦储存设施和一处安置难民的营地被烧毁。联合国人道主义协调员利塞·格兰德告诉BBC称也门的食物储备情况十分严峻。\n也门有两千万人口仍不知道今天还有没有饭吃。有238000人现正在挨饿。当地的粮食危机已经不能再严峻了，因此全国上下的人道主义人士呼吁人人采取一切措施来结束这场冲突。局势已经刻不容缓。\n调查人员称去年三月在加德满都机场坠毁的孟加拉飞机的机长在飞行期间心理压抑，情绪紊乱。这架美国-孟加拉航空公司飞机坠毁后，机上全部4名机组人员和67名乘客中的47名遇难。以下是吉尔·麦吉弗林的报道。\n调查报告显示该机长在短途飞行中情绪极其低落。他当时多次表现出易怒、紧张、不安和攻击性的情绪。他称自己很疲惫，因为前一晚没睡好。他当时多次向年轻的副驾驶员说起一名同事批评他作为一名教练表现不佳，这让他深受打击并产生了辞职的想法。据称飞机着陆时，他行为冲动，有反常态，并且犯了一系列的错误，导致机上大量人员死亡。\n墨西哥南部警方表示至少有十人在当地两个武装团伙的枪战中死亡。格雷罗州安全部队发言人表示枪战发生在奇拉帕镇上的一个高速公路上，并且持续了3个小时。目击者称，在一个武装黑帮团伙企图驾车穿过另一黑帮控制的区域时，双方爆发了枪战。\n一场强劲的龙卷风袭击了古巴首都哈瓦那，导致至少3人死亡，170多人在风暴中受伤。古巴总统米格尔·迪亚斯-卡内尔在推特上表示风暴造成的损失十分严重。网上的照片显示建筑倒塌，汽车损毁，树木也被风吹倒。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>70</id>
        <date>January 31, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Criminal sanctions imposed on Venezuelan owned oil company PDVSA by US</title>
        <description>
            The Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro has described as criminal sanctions imposed on the state owned oil company PDVSA by the United States. He accused Washington of setting out to steal the firm's US space of subsidiary Citgo and said PDVSA would take legal action to protect its asset.
        </description>
        <cover>images/the-white-house-finance-minister.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190131_1239118gwQ.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC News. Hello, I'm Gareth Barlow.\nThe Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro has described as criminal sanctions imposed on the state owned oil company PDVSA by the United States. He accused Washington of setting out to steal the firm's US space of subsidiary Citgo and said PDVSA would take legal action to protect its asset. The sanctions were announced by the US Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin in Washington earlier. From where Barbara Plett-Usher reports.\nThis is a critical economic move because Venezuela's oil sales to the United States are a big source of cash revenue for the Maduro government. The sanctions bar Americans from doing business with the state oil company and freeze any assets it has in the US. This is also an attempt to boost Mr. Maduro's rival, the opposition leader Juan Guaido. The Trump administration recognized him last week as Venezuela's leader. The aim is to transfer the oil money to him and the country's national assembly. As the announcement was made, Mr. Guaido said he was taking control of Venezuela's assets abroad to prevent Mr. Maduro from seizing them if he left power.\nProtesters have gathered outside the offices of the Brazilian mining company Vale as rescuers continue a desperate search for survivors from Friday's dam collapse. The firm's share price plunged by nearly twenty-five percent on Monday on the Brazilian stock market. Sixty-five people are so far confirmed dead.\nThe Supreme Court in Pakistan is due to hear a final legal challenge to the acquittal of a Christian woman who'd been sentenced to death for blasphemy. Secunder Kermani reports.\nAsia Bibi was convicted of insulting the prophet Muhammad in 2010 following an argument with two Muslim women who refuse to drink water from the same cup as her was working in a field. Two politicians who spoke out in her defence were murdered by militants, and the decision to quash her sentence last year resulted in angry protests. But the leaders of that unrest are currently in jail and it's expected if her acquittal is upheld, that Asia Bibi will be granted asylum abroad.\nMexico's largest railway operator has warned that the country could face shortages of staple foods as a result of a two-week protest by teachers been blocking train tracks in the west of the country. Kyle Winer reports.\nA spokeswoman for the Ferromex railroad company told local media that more than three hundred trains have been cancelled since the teachers started camping on the tracks in Michoacan state in a protest over pay and conditions. She said their actions were limiting the distribution of foods including potatoes and corn flour round the country and preventing the delivery of essential supplies to the steel and car industries. Mexico's largest seaport is in Michoacann and shipping industry associations say at least ten thousand containers have been held up at a cost of over seven hundred million dollars to the economy.\nThat's the BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nBBC新闻，大家好，我是加雷斯·巴洛。\n委内瑞拉总统尼古拉斯·马杜罗称美国对其国家石油公司PDVSA的制裁是一项犯罪行为。他指控美国设法窃取该公司的美国子公司雪铁戈石油公司，并表示委内瑞拉国家石油公司将会采取法律措施保护其资产。早前美国财政部长史蒂芬·努钦在华盛顿宣布了这些制裁。以下是芭芭拉·普莱特-亚瑟在华盛顿的报道。\n这是一个关键的金融举措，因为委内瑞拉对美国出售石油是马杜罗政府的主要现金收入来源。制裁禁止美国人与这家国有石油公司进行贸易，并且冻结了它在美国的所有资产。此举同样意在帮助马杜罗的政敌——反对党领袖胡安·瓜伊多。上周特朗普政府承认了他作为委内瑞拉领导人的身份。此举旨在将石油收入转移给他和该国的国民大会。随着这项措施的宣布，瓜伊多表示为了防止马杜罗下台后将其占为己有他将控制委内瑞拉在海外的资产。\n抗议者在巴西采矿公司清水河谷（Vale）的办公室外聚集，而救援人员还在竭尽全力搜救周五大坝倒塌事故中的幸存者。本周一，该公司在巴西股市中的股价暴跌近25%。目前已有65人确认死亡。\n巴基斯坦最高法院将审理赦免一名基督教女性的最终合法性问题，该女性因亵渎罪被判处死刑。以下是赛康德·科芒尼的报道。\n2010年阿西亚·比比因侮辱先知穆罕默德而被判有罪，原因是两名穆斯林女性拒绝和她同饮一个杯中的水而发生争执。为她辩护的两名政界人士遭到了武装分子的杀害，去年宣布的撤销判决的决定引起了愤怒的抗议活动。不过那场暴乱的领头人现已入狱，如果阿西亚·比比的无罪释放判决通过，她有望去国外寻求庇护。\n墨西哥最大的高速公路运营商警告称，国家可能面临主食短缺问题，因为一场由教师发起的持续了两个星期的抗议活动堵住了西部的铁路干线。以下是凯尔·维纳的报道。\n墨西哥Ferromex铁路公司的一名发言人告诉当地媒体，自从教师们在米却肯州的铁路上扎营抗议薪资和待遇问题以来，已有超过300列火车被取消。她表示他们的行为限制了包括土豆和玉米面粉在内的食物在全国范围内的分销，还阻碍了钢铁业和汽车制造业的关键材料的运输。墨西哥最大的海港就在米却肯州，航运业协会表示至少有一万只集装箱被滞留，造成经济损失超过7亿美元。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>71</id>
        <date>February 1, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - More than four hundred schools in the Thai capital Bangkok have been ordered to close</title>
        <description>
            More than four hundred schools in the Thai capital Bangkok have been ordered to close because of hazardous levels of smog. The governor of Bangkok said classes at all city-run schools were canceled for the rest of the week because of concerns for the health of students.
        </description>
        <cover>images/thai-smog.png</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190201_1450235sXb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Marion Marshall with the BBC News. The former motor tycoon Carlos Ghosn has said the charges pressed against him by Japanese prosecutors are the result of a plot by Nissen executives, which he described as treason. The comment was in his first interview since being arrested in November. Celia Hatton reports. Speaking from a Tokyo detention center to Japan's Nikkei newspaper, the man who once headed three car companies, Carlos Ghosn, hit back against a mounting number of financial misconduct charges. Mr. Ghosn said that some in Nissan opposed his plan to integrate Renault, the French car company he headed, with its Japanese alliance partners Nissan and Mitsubishi. They wanted to get rid of him, he said. The former alliance had denied any wrongdoing, including underreporting his salary and using Nissan's money to cover personal investment losses. He said those decisions had been signed off by colleagues at Nissan.\nThe Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro has said he's open to holding internationally mediated talks on the crisis in his country. He was speaking to Russia's state news agency. Sarah Rainsford reports from Moscow. This was a defiance, Nicolas Maduro speaking to the Russian news agency RIA, he insisted that his victory in elections last spring had been legitimate and transparent. He said if America and others wanted a fresh vote, then they'd have to wait to the end of his current term in 2025. But Nicolas Maduro also appeared to make a concession. He said he was ready to sit down for talks with the country's opposition for the sake of peace in the presence of international intermediaries. He was speaking ahead of a day of protests in Venezuela called by the opposition leader Juan Guaido, who's been recognized as the country's interim leader by the US and others.\nMore than four hundred schools in the Thai capital Bangkok have been ordered to close because of hazardous levels of smog. The governor of Bangkok said classes at all city-run schools were canceled for the rest of the week because of concerns for the health of students. The citie's pollution levels stood at about a hundred and seventy micrograms per cubic meter, which is considered unhealthy for everyone and particularly bad for children and the elderly.\nPolice in Australia say they intend to bring charges against one of the country's best known and most successful racehorse trainers. Darren Weir was arrested along with two other men during a raid at his stables in the state of Victoria as part of a corruption inquiry. Police seized a number of items, including a firearm and four taser-like devices that could be used to administer an electric shock to a horse. BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是玛丽安·马歇尔，欢迎收听BBC新闻。前汽车大亨卡洛斯·戈恩表示日本检方指控他的罪名都是日产高管阴谋陷害的，他称其为背叛。这段话是他在去年11月被捕后首次接受采访时说的。以下是西莉亚·哈顿的报道。在拘留所中接受日经新闻报采访时，曾经领导3个汽车公司的卡洛斯·戈恩否认了关于他越来越多的金融不当行为指控。戈恩表示日产的一些人反对他将雷诺与日产和三菱整合的计划，法国车企雷诺也由戈恩领导。他表示日产的人想要彻底摆脱他。他还否认了任何不当行为，包括过少申报自身报酬以及用日产的资金来弥补个人投资损失。他表示这些决定已经被日产的高管中止。\n委内瑞拉总统尼古拉斯·马杜罗表示他愿意就国内危机召开国际协调会谈。他接受了俄罗斯国家媒体的采访。以下是萨拉·雷因斯福德在莫斯科的报道。尼古拉斯·马杜罗对俄新社表示，这是对他的挑战，他还坚称在去年选举中取得的胜利是合法透明的。他表示如果美国和其他国家想要重新进行大选，那他们需要等到2025年他任期结束。尼古拉斯·马杜罗同样也想做出让步。他表示，为了和平愿意在国际协调者的参与下，坐下来与反对党进行协商。他讲话一天后，反对党领袖胡安·瓜伊多就领导了一起抗议活动，而后者也被美国和其他国家认为是该国的临时领导人。\n因雾霾达到危险水平，泰国首都曼谷400多所学校被关闭。曼谷政府表示，为了学生的健康考虑，市立学校本周的全部课程取消。该市的污染程度大约达到了170毫克/立方米，已经达到对健康有害的水平，尤其是对小孩和老人。\n澳大利亚警方表示他们将对该国最出名也是最成功的驯马师提起诉讼。警方突袭了他们位于维多利亚州的马厩，以腐败调查为由逮捕了达伦·威尔与其他两名驯马师。警察查获了一些物品，包括一支枪械和四个有可能用来对马进行电击的装置。BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>72</id>
        <date>February 2, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Parts of the United States have been hit by a deadly blast polar air</title>
        <description>
            Parts of the United States have been hit by a deadly blast polar air. Temperatures have plunged to minus 40 Celsius in the Midwest and some eastern states. 5 deaths have been blamed on the weather.
        </description>
        <cover>images/blast-polar-air.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0202_2202386q6F.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Stewart Macintosh.\nPresident Donald Trump has telephoned Venezuela's opposition leader Juan Guaido to assure him of U.S. support. The call came as people across the country heated Mr. Guaido's call to hold peaceful protests in city squares and on street corners. He declared himself interim president.\nSaudi Arabia says it's ended the anti-corruption drive that was launched dramatically more than a year ago, with the rounding up of hundreds of princes, billionaires and business leaders. The Saudi state news agency said that more than 100 billion dollars were transferred to the state.\nParts of the United States have been hit by a deadly blast polar air. Temperatures have plunged to minus 40 Celsius in the Midwest and some eastern states. 5 deaths have been blamed on the weather.\nIt's emerged in legal documents that the British-based bank Barkley is moving more than 200 billion dollars worth of assets to the Irish capital Dublin, because it can’t wait any longer to implement its Brexit contingency plan.\nIndia's top statistics official and a deputy have resigned in protest at a government delay in publishing a report many believe will show rising unemployment under the Prime Minister Narendra Modi. An independent think tank said 11 million jobs were lost last year.\nScientists in America have created an inflatable pill based on the puffer fish which is designed to carry sensors or even tiny cameras into the stomach. They say that once swallowed, the capsule swills to the size of a ping-pong ball and would allow doctors to detect diseases, such as cancer.\nThat is the BBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nStewart Macintosh为您播报BBC新闻。\n特朗普总统已致电委内瑞拉反对派领导人胡安·瓜伊多，向其保证美国政府会支持他的领导。这次致电正值委内瑞拉全国上下躁动之际，因为胡安·瓜伊多要求压制各城市广场和大街小巷的和平抗议。胡安·瓜伊多已宣称自己为临时总统。\n沙特称其已结束了反腐败运动。这次反腐败运动是1年多以前发起的。期间，有上百名王子、亿万富翁、商界领袖被捕。沙特官媒报道称，有1千多亿美元转到了本国。\n美国部分地区遭遇致命极地涡旋波及，中西部地区以及一些东部州气温已骤降到零下40度以下。已有5人因极寒天气死亡。\n一些法律文件显示，英国银行巴克莱银行正在将2000多亿美元的资产转到爱尔兰首都都柏林，因为巴克莱银行已等不及实施其应对脱欧的应急计划了。\n印度某高级统计部门官员以及副部长已引咎辞职，因为有民众抗议政府推迟发布了一份报告，而很多人认为这份报告会显示在纳伦德拉·莫迪担任总理期间，失业率升高。某独立智库称，去年，有1100万人下岗。\n美国的一些科学家研制出了一种充气式胶囊，其根据是河豚鱼。这种胶囊自带传感器乃至微型摄像头，可以进入胃部。科学家表示，一旦吞下这些胶囊，胶囊就会变成乒乓球的大小，这样医生就能检测各种疾病，比如癌症。\n以上是本期的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>73</id>
        <date>February 11, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Russia will follow US to suspend a key Cold War era nuclear weapons treaty</title>
        <description>
            President Putin has responded to a decision by the United States to suspend its participation in a key Cold War era nuclear weapons treaty by saying Russia will do the same.
        </description>
        <cover>images/new-mid-range-hypersonic-missile.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190211_2115647mNf.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is David Austin with the BBC News.\nPresident Putin has responded to a decision by the United States to suspend its participation in a key Cold War era nuclear weapons treaty by saying Russia will do the same. Our response will be a mirror one. Our American partners have announced they're suspending their participation in the treaty, and we are suspending ours, too. They have announced that they are engaged in research and development work, and we will do the same. At a meeting with his foreign and defense ministers, Mr. Putin said Russia would start to develop a new mid-range hypersonic missile. Steve Rosenberg in Moscow has more details. The Kremlin leader said Moscow mustn't and wouldn't get dragged into an expensive arms race. And Russia, he said, would not deploy short-and medium-range weapons in Europe or any other region unless US weapons were deployed there first. He instructed his ministers not to initiate further disarmament talks with Washington, although he made it clear that Russia's proposals on this issue remained on the table. The United States and NATO have accused Moscow of violating the terms of the INF Treaty. Russia has made similar allegations against the United States.\nVenezuela's self-proclaimed interim President Juan Guaido is attempting to mobilize tens of thousands of his supporters for a day of demonstrations. It's intended to increase pressure on Nicolas Maduro to relinquish the presidency. Orla Guerin in Caracas. However large the protest maybe, the sense here is that it will take a lot more than that to unseat Mr. Maduro. But the opposition believed that a process of change has begun. So far, it seems the president still has the backing of the military leadership, but he is under growing pressure, especially since the US imposed sanctions on the state-owned oil firm this week. That will starve him of revenue and could quickly paralyze the country, which is already stricken by shortages and hyperinflation.\nThousands of yellow vest protesters are congregating in Paris and elsewhere in France in the latest round of demonstrations against the cost of living and the policies of President Emmanuel Macron. This week they are also focusing their anger on the police's use of crowd control guns built as nonlethal that shoot large rubber balls. The projectiles known as flash balls have injured many protesters, resulting in some losing an eye. And that's the latest BBC News.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·奥斯汀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n美国决定退出一份冷战期间签订的核武器条约，普京回应称俄罗斯也会采取相同的措施。我们的回应将会与之相同。美方宣布退出协议，我们也会退出。他们宣布正在进行调查与研发工作，我们也会开始相同的工作。普京在与外交部长和国防部长的会议中表示，俄罗斯将会开始研发新的中程超音速导弹，以下是史蒂夫·罗森博格在莫斯科的详细报道。普京表示莫斯科不允许也不会再被带进一场军备竞赛之中。他还表示俄罗斯将不会在欧洲和其他地区部署短程和中程导弹，除非美国率先开始部署。他要求各部长不要与美国进行更进一步的裁军谈判，但他也明确表示俄罗斯关于该问题的提议仍可以进行协商。美国和北约指责莫斯科当局违反了《中导条约》，俄罗斯也向美国提出了相同的指控。\n自称为委内瑞拉临时总统胡安·瓜伊多正企图动员几万名支持者进行一天的抗议活动。此举意在向尼古拉斯·马杜洛施压，让他放弃总统职位。以下是欧蕾·盖林在加拉加斯的报道。不管这场抗议活动会有多大，人们认为这些还不足打败马杜罗。但是反对党认为变革的进程已经开始了。到现在为止，总统仍有军队领导人的支持，但是自从美国本周宣布对委内瑞拉国营石油公司进行制裁之后，马杜罗的压力也越来越大。此举将会断绝马杜罗的财政收入来源并迅速使国家瘫痪，委内瑞拉现已处于着资金短缺和恶性通货膨胀的困境。\n在最后一轮游行活动中，数千名黄马甲组织人员集合在巴黎和法国其他地区，抗议生活成本增加和总统埃马纽埃尔·马克龙的政策。本周他们将怒火集中在警方对抗议人群使用“人群控制枪”的问题上，这种枪的设计不会致命，只是发射大型的橡胶弹。这种枪弹被称为闪光球，已经使很多抗议人员受伤，导致一些人失去了一只眼睛。以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>74</id>
        <date>February 12, 2019</date>
        <title>English Essence For Recitation - A Father and A Son</title>
        <description>
            Passing through the Atlanta airport one morning, I caught one of those trains that take travelers from the main terminal to their boarding gates. Free, sterile and impersonal, the trains run back and forth all day long. Not many people consider them fun, but on this Saturday I heard laughter.
        </description>
        <cover>../english-essence/image/red-gray-train-miniature.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../english-essence/sound/a-father-and-a-son.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**A Father and A Son**\n**父子俩**\nPassing through the Atlanta airport one morning, I caught one of those trains that take travelers from the main terminal to their boarding gates. Free, sterile and impersonal, the trains run back and forth all day long. Not many people consider them fun, but on this Saturday I heard laughter.\n一天早晨去亚特兰大机场，我看见一辆列车载载着旅客从航空集散站抵达登记处。这类免费列车每天单调、无味地往返其间，没人觉得有趣。但这个周六我却听到了笑声。\nAt the front of the first car – looking out the window at the track that lay ahead – were a man and his son.\n在头节车厢的最前面，坐着一个男人和他的儿子。他们正透过窗户观赏着一直往前延伸的铁道。\nThey had just stopped to let off passengers, and the doors wee closing again. “Here we go! Hold on to me tight!” the father said. The boy, about five years old, made sounds of sheer delight.\n他们停下来等候旅客下车，之后，车门关上了。“走吧。拉紧我！”父亲说。儿子大约5岁吧，一路喜不自禁。\nI know we’re supposed to avoid making racial distinctions these days, so I hope no one will mind if I mention that most people on the train were white, dressed for business trips or vacations – and that the father and son were black, dressed in clothes that were just about as inexpensive as you can buy.\n车上坐的多半是衣冠楚楚，或公差或度假的白人，只有这对黑人父子穿着朴素简单。我知道如今我们不该种族歧视，我希望我这样描述没人介意。\n“Look out there!” the father said to his son. “See that pilot? I bet he’s walking to his plane.” The son craned his neck to look.\n“快看！”父亲对儿子说：“看见那位飞行员了吗？我敢肯定是去开飞机的。”儿子伸长脖子看。\nAs I got off, I remembered some thing I’d wanted to buy in the terminal. I was early for my flight, so I decided to go back.\n下了车后我突然想起还得在航空集散站买点东西。离起飞时间还早，于是我决定再乘车回去。\nI did – and just as I was about to reboard the train for my gate, I saw that the man and his son had returned too. I realized then that they hadn’t been heading for a flight, but had just been riding the shuttle.\n正准备上车的时候，我看到那对父子也来了。我意识到他们不是来乘飞机的，而是特意来坐区间列车的。\n"You want to go home now? " The father asked.\n爸爸问：“你想现在回家吗？”\n“I want to ride some more!”\n“我还想再坐一会儿！”\n“More?” the father said, mock-exasperated but clearly pleased. “You’re not tired?”\n“再坐一会儿！”父亲嗔怪模仿着儿子的语调，“你还不累？”\n“This is fun!” his son said.\n“真好玩！”儿子说。\n“All right,” the father replied, and when a door opened we all got on.\n“好吧，”父亲说。车门开了，我们都上了车。\nThere are parents who can afford to send their children to Europe or Disneyland, and the children turn out rotten. There are parents who live in million-dollar houses and give their children cars and swimming pools, yet something goes wrong.\n我们很多父母有能力送孩子去欧洲，去狄斯尼乐园，可孩子还是堕落了。很多父母住豪华别墅，孩子有车有游泳池，可孩子还是学坏了。\n“Where are all these people going, Daddy?” the son asked.\n“爸爸，这些人去哪？”儿子问。\n“All over the world,” came the reply. The other people in the air port wee leaving for distant destinations or arriving at the ends of their journeys. The father and son, though, were just riding this shuttle together, making it exciting, sharing each other’s company.\n“世界各地。”父亲回答。机场来来往往的人流或准备远行，或刚刚归来。这对父子却在乘坐区间列车，享受着父子间的亲情与陪伴。\nHere was a father who cared about spending the day with his son and who had come up with this plan on a Saturday morning.\n而这里。这位父亲却很在意花上一天陪伴儿子，并在这样一个星期六的早上，提出这个计划。\nParents who care enough to spend time, and to pay attention and to try their best. It doesn’t cost a cent, yet it is the most valuable thing in the world.\n父母愿意花时间，愿意关注，愿意尽心尽职。这不要花一分钱，可这却是世间无价之宝。\nThe train picked up speed, and the father pointed something out, and the boy laughed again.\n火车加速了。父亲指着窗外说着什么，儿子直乐.
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>75</id>
        <date>February 13, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - A fire that engulfed a residential building in Paris killed eight people</title>
        <description>
            Police in Paris say they believe a fire that engulfed a residential building during the night killing eight people was started deliberately.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fire-engulfed-residential-building.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190212_5439651Lnp.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Debbie Russ with the BBC news. Police in Paris say they believe a fire that engulfed a residential building during the night killing eight people was started deliberately. The Paris prosecutor Remy Heitz said a woman who lived in the building had been detained. At this stage, the information we have points to criminal activity as the main line of investigation. One person has been arrested, a person who lives in the building. This person was arrested during the night, not far from the scene, not far from the fire, and she's currently in custody. Residents say the woman had psychiatric problems and had been involved in a dispute with a neighbor, a fireman over loud music during which she threatened to set fire to the building. At least thirty other people have been injured in the blaze at the eight-storey building in the west of the French capital.\nThe former Afghan President Hamid Karzai and a delegation of influential opposition figures are meeting the Taliban in Moscow for political talks. Last month, hopes were raised when the Taliban and US officials apparently drafted the framework for an initial peace deal. But Afghan government officials are not taking part in the talks as the Taliban are refusing to meet them. Secunder Kermani reports. The insurgents have resisted American demands that they engage directly with President Ashraf Ghani's National Unity Government, which they dismissed as illegitimate. Those taking part in the talks say there is an opportunity to start a dialogue between the Taliban and important power brokers in Afghanistan, but some in Kabul see them as an attempt by political rivals to undermine the Afghan government, an exploring deal with the Taliban behind their backs.\nState media in Ethiopia are reporting that more than two hundred people have been arrested in the west of the country where they were receiving illegal military training. It says they were stopped by the army and police close to the Sudanese border, where ethnic clashes have displaced tens of thousands of people. The security forces in Burkina Faso say they've killed a large number of militants in response to an attack in which fourteen civilians were killed in the north of the country. The military said armed men attacked the village of Kain in Yatenga province on Sunday night. A military statement said the Burkinabe army conducted a large scale operation in three northern provinces, reportedly killing 146 militants.\nUS government scientists have published an unscheduled update to their model of the Earth's magnetic field to deal with the speeding-up of the magnetic North Pole. Magnetic north, which is the place that compasses point to, is constantly moving. But the latest changes have been greater than expected. And that's the latest world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是黛比·罗斯，欢迎收听BBC新闻。昨晚巴黎一座居民楼发生大火，导致8人死亡，警方认为是有人蓄意纵火。巴黎检察官雷米·赫兹表示该楼里的一名女性现已被拘捕。随着调查的进行，目前阶段的信息显示这是一起犯罪行为。该楼的一名住户现已被逮捕。该嫌疑人在当晚离火灾事发地不远处被捕，现在在监禁中。住户们表示这名女性精神有问题，她曾与邻居消防员因音乐声音过大发生争吵，当时她扬言要烧了这座楼。在这栋位于法国首都以西的8层建筑中，至少有三十人在大火中受伤。\n前阿富汗总统哈米德·卡尔扎伊和有影响力的反对党代表正在莫斯科与塔利班举行政治谈判。上个月，当塔利班与美国官员起草首个和平协议的框架时，希望重新燃起。但是阿富汗政府官员并没有参与到谈判中来，因为塔利班拒绝见他们。以下是赛康德·科芒尼的报道。塔利班拒绝了美国让他们与阿什拉夫·加尼的国家统一政府直接接触的要求，他们称这个政府是不合法的。与会者表示这是塔利班和阿富汗政治掮客开启对话的机会。首都喀布尔的一些人认为这是政治对手来削弱阿富汗政府的一种手段，是他们背后与塔利班进行的探索性交易。\n埃塞俄比亚的国家媒体报道称，在西部地区有200多人被逮捕，原因是他们正在接受非法的军事训练。据报道，埃塞俄比亚军队和警察在苏丹边境终止了他们的训练，当地的民族冲突也导致数万人从家乡逃离。布基纳法索的安全部队表示他们杀死了大量的武装分子，以报复他们在国家北部杀死十四名平民的袭击。军方表示武装分子周日晚袭击了亚滕加省该隐村。一名军方发言人表示布基纳法索军队在三个北方省份实施了大规模的行动，报道称杀死了146名武装分子。\n美国科学家意外地发表了一份他们的地球磁场模型的更新，该模型旨在记录地球磁场北极的加速移动。地磁北极，也就是指南针所指的方向，它正在不断地移动，最近的变化比预期的更快。以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>76</id>
        <date>February 14, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - More than 1700 people have died due to human-elephant conflict in India</title>
        <description>
            India says more than 1700 people have died in various incidents of human-elephant conflict in the past three years.In the same period, the Ministry of Environment says 373 elephants lost their lives due to electrocution and poaching.
        </description>
        <cover>images/human-elephant-conflict.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190213_30212755Av.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Eileen Mckue with the BBC News.\nUS-backed forces are continuing an all-out offensive to defeat hundreds of Islamic State fighters from their last hold out in northeastern Syria. IS militants are reported to be putting up fierce resistance. Sebastian Usher reports.\nAir strikes by the US-led coalition and artillery fire have pummeled the IS position which measures about four square kilometres. The SDF, a Kurdish-led alliance believes it will shortly achieve a decisive victory. There may still be up to six hundred IS fighters in the area. Thousands of civilians have escaped but others are believed to remain. IS does still hold another scrap of territory in Syria and it continues to carry out dozens of attacks. Even if it loses every last fragment of its once-vaunted and self-declared caliphate, the group still poses a potent threat in both Syria and Iraq.\nTrade and conflict will dominate discussions at the African Union Summit, which is getting underway in the Ethiopian capital Addis Ababa. Particular emphasis is being placed on the more than twenty million people who have been forced to flee their homes because of wars. Emmanuel Igunza reports from the meeting.\nThe UN Refugee Agency says Africa holds more than a quarter of the world's refugees and internal displace, a total of more than twenty million people. The leaders will also discuss efforts to integrate the continent's trade policies, following the signing last year of an European Union style free market agreement. The African Union has embarked on a series of reforms to streamline its operations and make it less dependent on international financial support. It hopes the changes can also help the AU shed its image of a body that has plans and ambitions but achieves little.\nIndia says more than 1700 people have died in various incidents of human-elephant conflict in the past three years. In the same period, the Ministry of Environment says 373 elephants lost their lives due to electrocution and poaching. This report from Anbrathan Antirajon.\nWildlife expert say deforestation and expanding human settlements along space of forest used by elephants known as elephant corridors as the reasons for the high number of deaths of both humans and the animals. Farmers trying to chase away marauding elephants using firecrackers, drums and fire bombs have become a regular occurrence, particularly in states like Assam, West Bengal and Tamil Nadu. Desperate farmers often put up illegal electric fences to stop the animals from destroying the crops leading to elephant deaths. India is home to the largest population of Asian elephants in the world and estimated twenty-seven thousand animals.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是艾琳·麦克尤，欢迎收听BBC新闻。\n美国支持的军事力量将对叙利亚北部数百名伊斯兰国战士所坚守的最后领域发起全面进攻。据报道，伊斯兰国激进分子将进行激烈的抵抗。以下是塞巴斯蒂安·厄什尔的报道。\n美国领导的联盟已对伊斯兰国组织约四平方公里的驻地进行了空袭和炮击。库尔德领导的联盟，叙利亚民主力量（SDF）认为他们很快便将取得决定性的胜利。该区域内可能还有多达600名伊斯兰国战士。数千名平民已经逃离该区，但据信仍有人留在那里。伊斯兰国组织在叙利亚还有一块驻地，他们还继续了发起了数十次袭击。即使失去了最后一片自称的伊斯兰领土，该组织仍是叙利亚和伊拉克境内一个潜在的威胁。\n贸易和冲突仍将是非洲联盟峰会的主要议题，峰会正在埃塞俄比亚首都亚的斯亚贝巴进行。峰会将特别关注两千多万因战事而被迫逃离家乡的难民。以下是埃马纽埃尔·伊谷文泽的报道。\n联合国难民署表示非洲有世界四分之一的难民以及国内的无家可归者，总数超过了两千万。领导人们还将讨论整合非洲大陆贸易政策的措施，他们在去年也签署了一份欧盟式自由市场协议。非盟现已开启了一系列改革措施来提高工作效率，并减少其对国际金融援助的依赖。他们希望这些改革能够帮助非盟摆脱“有计划有抱负，但是很少能实现”的形象。\n印度表示在过去的三年里有1700多人死于各种人象冲突。印度环境部表示，同期有373头大象死于触电和偷猎。以下是安德布里森·安迪罗杰的报道。\n野生动物专家表示，森林砍伐和人类居住地扩张侵占了有“大象走廊”之称的森林这是导致人类和动物大量死亡的原因。农民用鞭炮、锣鼓和燃烧弹驱赶破坏庄稼的大象已成为常态，特别是在阿萨姆邦，西孟加拉邦和泰米尔纳德邦等州。绝望的农民通常是架起非法电围栏来防止大象破坏他们的庄稼，这也导致了大象死亡。印度是世界上拥有亚洲象最多的国家，据估计有27,000头。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>77</id>
        <date>February 15, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - Democrats and Republicans in US reached an agreement in principle on border security</title>
        <description>
            Democrats and Republicans in the United States say they've reached an agreement in principle on border security that they hope will avoid a second government shutdown.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-agreement-border-security.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190214_1318229wyJ.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, I'm Nick Kelly with the BBC News. Democrats and Republicans in the United States say they've reached an agreement in principle on border security that they hope will avoid a second government shutdown. They hope to turn the agreement into legislation by Wednesday, two days before the current federal funding agreement runs out. Gary O'Donoghue reports. The tentative deal reached between Republicans and Democrats still has to be finalized, but sources close to the negotiations suggest the President may only get around a quarter of the 5.7 billion dollars he was looking for to build more border wall. The big uncertainty is what the President will be prepared to sign. At a rally in el Paso in texas last night, he was giving little away about his attitude to the emerging deal. What there was at the rally was plenty of heated rhetoric about illegal immigrants and crime, and of course, fake news with my BBC cameraman Ron Skins attacked by a Trump supporter as he went about his job filming the speech.\nThe former Vice President of the Spanish region of Catalonia, Oriol Junqueras and eleven other separatists are going on trial later in Madrid over the 2017 Catalan referendum and subsequent declaration of independence. Guy Hedgecoe is in Madrid. This is Spain's most politically sensitive trial for decades. Among the defendants is Oriol Junqueras, former Vice President of Catalonia, who could face up to twenty-five years in prison if found guilty of rebellion. He and several other defendants have been held in custody for months ahead of the trial, prompting claims by their defense teams that this whole judicial process lacks credibility. But the government says the trial, which is expected to last around three months, has all the necessary guarantees.\nPoliticians have been accused of failing to comprehend the dangers posed by multiplying environmental crises. The warning comes from the Institute for Public Policy Research in Britain. Here's Roger Harrabin. The report warns of a potentially deadly combination of factors affecting the planet, including climate change and the mass loss of species, especially insects. The authors note widespread erosion of topsoil, forest felling, acidifying oceans, extrem weather, plastic in the seas, overfishing and more. The report says these factors are driving what they call a complex dynamic process of environmental destabilization. They say this destabilization is occurring at speeds unprecedented in human history. This is the world news from the BBC.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是尼克·凯利，欢迎收听BBC新闻。美国民主党和共和党表示他们已经就边境安全问题达成了一项原则性协议，并希望可以避免下一次政府停摆。他们希望周三前对此进行立法，而两天后现有的联邦资金就将用尽，以下是盖里·奥多诺霍的报道。民主党和共和党之间达成的尝试性协议还有待落实，但是接近该协商的消息人士称特朗普可能只会得到他要求的57亿边境墙资金的四分之一。特朗普将会如何签署这份协议成为了一个很大的不确定因素。在昨晚的埃尔帕索集会中，特朗普并没有透露太多对新协议的看法。集会上充满了关于非法移民、犯罪和假新闻的激进言论，BBC摄影师罗恩·斯金斯在拍摄集会讲话时就遭到了一名特朗普支持者的袭击。\n前西班牙加泰罗尼亚副总统奥利奥尔·容克拉斯以及其余11名分裂主义分子将会在晚些时候在马德里就2017年的加泰罗尼亚公投和以及后续的宣布独立事件接受审判。以下是盖伊·海吉科的报道。这是西班牙几十年来最具政治敏感性的审判。被告奥利奥尔·容克拉斯是加泰罗尼亚前总统，如果反叛罪名成立，他将面临最高25年的监禁。在审判之前，他和几名其他被告已被关押数月之久，他们的辩护团队称整个司法过程缺乏可信度。但是政府表示该审判将会持续约三个月，并且有所有必要的保障。\n研究指出政府人员没能正确理解多重环境危机带来的危害。该警告出自英国公共政策研究院，以下是罗杰·哈里宾的报道。该报告对影响地球的潜在危险因素的合集做出了警告，其中就包括气候变化以及特别是昆虫在内的大量物种灭绝。报告指出的问题包括表层土壤的侵蚀、森林砍伐、海洋酸化、极端天气、海洋的塑料污染、过度捕鱼以及更多问题。他们的报告称这些因素导致了环境不稳定的复杂动态过程。他们表示环境不稳定过程正在以人类历史上最快的速度发展。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>78</id>
        <date>February 16, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The European aerospace firm Airbus will stop making the A380 superjumbo</title>
        <description>
            The European aerospace firm Airbus has announced that it will stop making the world's biggest airplane the A380 superjumbo. The double-decker aircraft was designed to challenge the 747 of Airbus's rival Boeing.
        </description>
        <cover>images/biggest-airplane-A380.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc190215_4414484nPV.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>The BBC News with Fiona MacDonald.\nThe European aerospace firm Airbus has announced that it will stop making the world's biggest airplane the A380 superjumbo. The double-decker aircraft was designed to challenge the 747 of Airbus's rival Boeing. Rob Young reports.\nThe era of the Superjumbo is drawing to an end, just thirteen years after the A380 flew for the first time, Airbus says it will stop production with the final plane to be delivered in two years' time. The A380 is regarded as a great technological achievement. It's estimated to have cost about fifteen billion pounds to develop. But Airbus has struggled to sell the giant planes with airlines increasingly turning to smaller, more fuel efficient aircraft for long haul flights. The final nail in the coffin was a decision by Emirates, the Gulf Airline that's been the planes biggest fan to cut substantially its outstanding order.\nThe journalist at the head of an award-winning news website in the Philippines which criticized the country's President has been bailed after spending the night in detention. Maria Ressa, the head of Rappler website was arrested on Wednesday over a libel charge relating to an article published seven years ago. Here's Howard Johnson.\nLots of people have come forward to condemn this move. We've heard from the Vice President of the country Leni Robredo, she said that this is pure political harassment a view that's been echoed by many people in the media here who say that this is a clampdown on freedom of speech. Let's not forget Rapper had urged Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte in the past for their coverage of his drug war. Now the president's spokesperson came forward and said that this has got nothing to do with freedom of speech. He says that this is purely a libel case, a private libel case brought by a businessman against Rapper.\nSaudi Arabia has expressed regret at a proposal by the European Commission to add it to a list of countries that don't do enough to prevent money laundering and the financing of terrorism. A report by the official Saudi Press Agency said the Gulf kingdom had taken a number of measures to combat financial irregularities.\nFemale students at a prestigious Indian college have called for the scrapping of a decades-old Valentine's day tradition in which their male colleagues worship a so-called Virgin Tree. Women at the Hindu college in Delhi say the practice of adorning the tree with ribbons, condoms filled with water and posters representing the curvaceous goddess Damdami Mai is patriarchal and misogynistic. The male students say the ritual is a bit of harmless fun.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\n欢迎收听BBC新闻，我是菲奥娜·麦克唐纳德。\n欧洲飞机制造公司空客宣布他们将停止生产世界最大客机“空中巨无霸”A380。这款双层飞机是空客为了挑战对手波音的747而设计的。以下是罗勃·杨的报道。\n在A380 首次起飞仅13年后，“空中巨无霸”的时代就已经落幕了。空客表示最后一架A380将会在两年内交付，之后将会停产。A380被誉为是一项巨大的科技成就。据估计其研发成本超过了150亿英镑。但是空客在这款巨无霸客机的销售上遇到了问题，因为越来越多的航空公司更倾向于在长途航线上采用体型更小更省油的飞机。导致停产的致命一击还在于阿联酋的海湾航空公司，该公司一直以来都是A380最忠实的粉丝，但现在却大规模削减订单了。\n菲律宾一家新闻网站的著名新闻工作者在经过一夜的拘留后被保释，她曾批评过该国总统。玛丽亚·雷萨是Rappler新闻网的首席执行官，周三她因7年前涉嫌撰文诽谤总统被捕。以下是霍华德·约翰逊的报道。\n很多人站出来谴责该做法。我们从该国副总统莱妮·罗布雷多处得到消息，她表示这是纯粹的政治迫害，这一观点也得到了很多媒体人士的响应，他们称这是对言论自由的镇压。需要记住的是，Rapper新闻网曾在毒品战争的报道中告诫过总统罗德里戈·杜特尔特。现在总统发言人站出来称此事无关言论自由。他表示这纯粹是一起诽谤案，是一名商人起诉这家媒体的私人诽谤案。\n欧盟委员会提议将沙特阿拉伯列入一份名单之中，该名单包括在反洗钱方面力度不足以及资助恐怖主义的国家。对此，沙特表示遗憾。沙特官方新闻社报道称，海湾王国已经采取了大量的措施打击金融不法行为。\n印度一所著名大学的女学生呼吁废除一项数十年之久的情人节习俗，在这一天，男同学将会祭拜一棵所谓的处女树。这所位于德里的印度大学的女性表示，为这棵树装扮上彩带、灌满水的避孕套以及代表‘爱之神’的海报的行为是男权和歧视女性的表现。该校男学生表示该习俗并无恶意。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>79</id>
        <date>February 16, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - The notorious Mexican drug lord guilty on all 10 counts at his drug-trafficking trial in New York</title>
        <description>
            A jury has found the notorious Mexican drug lord, Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman, guilty on all 10 counts at his drug-trafficking trial in New York.The unanimous decision means the 61-year-old faces a mandatory life sentence.
        </description>
        <cover>images/Mexican-drug-lord.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0216_56189999rH.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Marian Marshall.\nA jury has found the notorious Mexican drug lord, Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman, guilty on all 10 counts at his drug-trafficking trial in New York. The unanimous decision means the 61-year-old faces a mandatory life sentence. Guzman, once among the world’s richest men, ran the Sinaloa drug cartel, one of the biggest suppliers of drugs for the United States.\nTens of thousands of supporters of the Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido have rallied in the center of the capital Caracas. Many are carrying placards, demanding President Nicolas Madura stand down. Others are chanting slogans in support of Mr. Guaido.\nThe Italian parliament has called on Venezuela to hold new presidential elections to replace what it called the illegitimate ones last May that re-elected President Nicolas Madura. Italy is one of the few European countries not to back Mr. Guaido as Interim President.\n15 people have been arrested in the Democratic Republic of Congo in connection with Common Law clashes in December. United Nations says the violence left almost 900 people dead.\nRussian parliament has passed draft legislation that will give the state tighter control of the internet to defend it from foreign meddling. The bill seeks to route Russian web traffic through points controlled by state authorities.\nThe former Yugoslavia Republic of Macedonia has begun using its new name of North Macedonia, ending three decades of dispute with its southern neighbor Greece. It confirmed the name change in the official gazette. Until the United Nations is formally notified of the change, the new name will be for domestic use only.\nThe European Union has signed a new multi-million dollar agreement with Morocco that will allow EU vessels fishing rights off the coast of the disputed territory of Western Sahara. But it has angered the territory’s independence movement, and has been rejected by the Saharan residents.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nMarian Marshall为您播报BBC新闻。\n某陪审团判定臭名昭著的墨西哥毒枭乔奎恩·古兹曼获罪10项，这是在纽约的贩毒审判上做出的判决。陪审团意见一致，认为这名61岁的毒贩要面临强制性终身监禁刑罚。古兹曼曾是市场上屈指可数的富豪之一，他曾经营过锡那罗亚贩毒集团，该集团是美国最大的毒品供应商。\n上万名委内瑞拉反对派胡安·瓜伊多的支持者聚集在首都加拉加斯的中心。很多人都手持布告，要求总统马杜罗下台。还有一些人高喊着支持瓜伊多的口号。\n意大利议会呼吁委内瑞拉举行新一届总统大选，以替换其眼中的非法大选，即去年5月的那次。去年的大选再次选举马杜罗为总统。意大利是为数不多的几个欧洲国家之一，这几个欧洲国家并不支持瓜伊多担任临时总统。\n15人在刚果民主共和国被捕，原因是与12月发生的普通法冲突有关。联合国表示，那次暴力事件导致近900人死亡。\n俄罗斯议会已通过草案法，该法让政府可以更加紧密地管控互联网，从而避免本国受境外势力干预。该法案寻求让俄罗斯网路在当局管控的节点上运作。\n前南斯拉夫马其顿共和国已经开始使用其新名称北马其顿共和国，此举结束了30年来该国与其南部邻国希腊之间的争议。该国在官方公报上证实了改名这件事。在联合国正式收到改名的通知之前，新名字仅在该国内部使用。\n欧盟签署了价值数百万美元的新协议，协议对象是摩洛哥。该协议将授予欧盟舰艇在受争议的西撒哈拉进行捕鱼的权利。但该协议的签订激起了西撒哈拉独立运动的愤怒，也受到了撒哈拉民众的排斥。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>80</id>
        <date>February 16, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - A petition to bring about laws to protect bees is drawing to a close in the German</title>
        <description>
            A petition to bring about laws to protect bees is drawing to a close in the German State of Bavaria. Campaigners have until the end of the day to collect nearly a million signatures needed to ensure that the government takes action.
        </description>
        <cover>images/bees.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0216-2_3536289kPg.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Marian Marshall.\nDonald Trump has warned Venezuela’s President Nicolas Maduro that he is making a terrible mistake by blocking access to foreign humanitarian aid. Mr. Trump said the US was working with other countries in the region to find ways of delivering food and medicines to the Venezuelan people.\nAt least 27 members of Iran’s elite Revolutionary Guard have been killed in a suicide attack in the southeast of the country. A Sunni Muslim militant group said it carried out the bombing.\nAmerican prosecutors have charged a former intelligence officer in the US Air Force with spying for Iran. Monica Witt is said to have defected to Iran in 2013 and supplied classified information.\nTwo suspected members of the Syrian Secret Service accused of involvement in killing and torturing critics of President Assad have been arrested in Germany, one of them accused of hunting down army deserters and torturing at least 2,000 people.\nNASA has declared that the Opportunity Rover that’s sent to Mars is not functioning, 8 months after last contact with ground control on earth. The robotic vehicle transformed an understanding of the red planet by confirming that water once flowed there.\nThe UN’s labor agency, the ILO, has revealed that it took until last year for the world’s unemployment rate to recover from the financial crash of 2008. The ILO said more than 170 million people had no job.\nA Sudanese refugee who has been held in Australia’s controversial Manus Island Detention Center has won the prestigious human rights prize. Abdul Aziz Muhamat received the Martin Ennals Award for his campaign for better conditions of the camp in Papua New Guinea.\nA petition to bring about laws to protect bees is drawing to a close in the German State of Bavaria. Campaigners have until the end of the day to collect nearly a million signatures needed to ensure that the government takes action.\nBBC world service news.\n**参考译文：**\nMarian Marshall为您播报BBC新闻。\n特朗普警示委内瑞拉总统马杜罗，称他现在犯了一个严重的错误，即不让境外人道主义援助进入。特朗普总统表示，美国正在与该地区的其他国家合作，以寻找方法向委内瑞拉人民输送粮食和药物。\n伊朗精英革命卫队中至少有27人在一次自杀式袭击中死亡，袭击地点在该国东南部。某逊尼派激进组织承认是其发动了这次爆炸。\n美国多位检察官指控一名美国空军前情报官为伊朗从事间谍活动。该情报官名为威特，据称，他曾于2013年叛变，为伊朗效力，并为其提供机密情报。\n2名疑似叙利亚特工处的特工被控涉嫌杀害并拷打阿萨德总统的批评者。目前，这2人已在德国被捕。其中一人还被控追捕逃兵以及拷打至少2000人。\n美国宇航局（NASA）宣布，被派往火星的机遇号现已报废。它与地球地面控制的最后一次联系8个月前。机遇号探测器颠覆了人类对火星的理解，证实了火星曾有水源存在。\n联合国国际劳工组织（ILO）称，直到去年，全球失业率才从2008年的金融危机中恢复过来。ILO表示，那次危机后，曾有1.7亿多人失业。\n一名苏丹难民被扣押在澳大利亚备受争议的马努斯岛拘留中心。此人获得了著名的人权奖。他叫阿卜杜勒，他获得的是马丁恩纳斯人权捍卫者奖，此奖表彰他为改善巴布亚新几内亚难民营地条件所做的贡献。\n德国巴伐利亚州发起了一项请愿，希望能设立保护蜜蜂的法律。目前，请愿的截止日期正在迫近。请愿者们在今天结束之前要集齐近100万个签名才能保证德国政府采取行动。\nBBC世界新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>81</id>
        <date>February 17, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - President Trump declared a national emergency to fund his border wall</title>
        <description>
            In the past few minutes, a senior US Republican has announced that President Trump will sign a bipartisan spending deal to avoid another government shutdown and then declared a national emergency to fund his border wall.
        </description>
        <cover>images/trump-declare-national-emergency.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc0217_0428977D5f.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>BBC news with Stuart Mackintosh.\nThe British Prime Minister Theresa May has suffered another parliamentary defeat on her Brexit plans. Members voted against the government’s appeal to back the approach agreed two weeks ago. Brexit supporters who rebelled said the motion would have ruled out leaving the EU next month without a deal.\nCuba has accused the United States of secretly moving troops to several Caribbean islands in preparation for an attempt to depose the Venezuelan leader Nicolas Maduro. Havana said the US military aircrafts landed last week in several strategic locations in the region.\nA third man suspected of helping to poison the former Russian spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter in Britain last year has been identified as a senior Russian military intelligence officer. The investigative website Bellingcat named him as Denis Sergeev.\nIndia has called for international sanctions against the leader of a militant group based in Pakistan which is said to have carried out a suicide attack in Kashmir, killing at least 40 people. In a statement, India asked for the leader of Jaish-e- Mohammad Group, Maulana Masood Azhar, to be designated as terrorist by the UN.\nIn the past few minutes, a senior US Republican has announced that President Trump will sign a bipartisan spending deal to avoid another government shutdown and then declared a national emergency to fund his border wall. The senate majority leader Mitch McConnell said the two moves would be made together.\nStudents and teachers across the United States have been holding vigils to mark the anniversary of the Parkland shooting in which 17 people were killed at a high school in Florida. Schools in the state held a moment of silence.\nA new research into aging brains suggested they could be rejuvenated, allowing mental decline to be reversed. US scientists say we lose mental sharpness not because our brain cells die, but because they fall out of sync with each other.\nBBC news.\n**参考译文：**\nStuart Mackintosh为您播报BBC新闻。\n英国首相特雷莎·梅再次在议会遭遇脱欧计划的失败。议会议员通过投票否决了内阁呼吁支持的脱欧计划，该脱欧计划达成于2周前。表示反对的脱欧支持者则认为，该动议能够避免下个月无协议脱欧。\n古巴指责美国秘密将军队派往多个加拉比海盗，旨在为罢免委内瑞拉领导人马杜罗做准备。古巴政府表示，美军多架飞行棋已于上周着陆该地区的多个战略位置。\n涉嫌参与去年在英国毒害俄罗斯前特工斯克里帕尔及其女儿的第三人已被确认，此人系俄军某高级情报官。调查性网站Bellingcat指出此人名为丹尼斯。\n印度呼吁采用国际制裁针对位于巴基斯坦某激进组织的头目。据称，该组织在克什米尔发动了自杀式袭击，导致至少40人死亡。在一份声明中，印度呼吁联合国将激进组织穆罕默德军的头目马苏德·阿兹哈尔列为恐怖分子。\n就在几分钟前，美国某高级共和党议员宣布，特朗普将签署一份两党的支出协议，以避免政府再次停摆。然后会宣布国家进入紧急状态，以为建造边境墙提供资金。这位参议院的多数党领袖是明奇·麦康奈尔，他表示，这两步会同时进行。\n美国各地的师生都在守夜，以纪念帕克兰枪杀事件一周年。在这次事件中，17人死于佛罗里达周的一所高中。帕克兰州的多所学校举行了默哀。\n一项有关大脑老龄化的新研究表明，大脑可以恢复活力，从而逆转智力下降。美国科学家表示，我们大脑失去活力并不是因为脑细胞死亡，而是因为脑细胞彼此之间不能同步。\nBBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>82</id>
        <date>February 18, 2019</date>
        <title>BBC News - India's fastest train has broken down a day after it was inaugurated</title>
        <description>
            India's fastest train has broken down a day after it was inaugurated by the Prime Minister Narendra Modi with much fanfare.Soon after that drivers noticed a smoke in the last four coaches, and power was lost in all compartments.
        </description>
        <cover>images/India-fastest-train.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20190218_584946936M.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>Hello, this is David Austin with the BBC News. The two main political parties in Nigeria have condemned the country's electoral commission for postponing the presidential and parliamentary elections hours before polling was due to start. The head of the commission is Mahmoud Yakubu. This will afford the commission the opportunity to address identified challenges in order to maintain the quality of our elections. This was a difficult decision for the commission to take, but necessary for the successful delivery of elections and the consolidation of our democracy. Mr. Yakubu said legistical problems had made it impossible to hold the vote on schedule, but both the governing All Progressives Congress and the opposition People's Democratic Party criticized the commission for not being prepared and then accused each other of trying to manipulate the vote. Both have urged calm.\nThe Roman Catholic Church has defrocked the former Cardinal Theodore McCarrick over allegations of child abuse. The Vatican said Pope Francis had ruled his expulsion from the clergy as definitive and would not allow any further appeals against the decision. Theodore McCarrick was the former Archbishop of Washington D.C. Martin Bashir reports. Theodore McCarrick was informed of the church's decision to remove him from the priesthood last night. And a terse statement from the Vatican this morning said that he'd been found guilty of sins against minors and adults with the aggravating factor of the abuse of power. Last July, he resigned as a cardinal, the first to do so in more than a hundred years, after credible allegations emerged that he'd sexually assaulted a sixteen-year-old altar boy and then molested another fourteen-year-old.\nIndia's fastest train has broken down a day after it was inaugurated by the Prime Minister Narendra Modi with much fanfare. Anbrathan Antirajon has the story. The state-of-the-art Vande Bharat Express was returning from the Indian city of Varanasi after its first outing when the brakes reportedly jammed in one of the carriages. Soon after that drivers noticed a smoke in the last four coaches, and power was lost in all compartments. Those on board, mostly railway officials and journalists, had to take another train to get back to Delhi. Some reports said the express had hit a stray cow. The train is expected to reduce the travel time between Delhi and Varanasi by six hours. The new train service is expected to start its commercial run from Sunday. And that's the latest BBC News.\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是大卫·奥斯汀，欢迎收听BBC新闻。尼日利亚选举委员会在投票开始几小时前推迟了总统和议会大选，该国两大政党对此表示谴责。以下是马哈茂德·雅库布的讲话。该决定将会让委员会有更多时间处理已发现的问题，从而保证选举的质量。这对于委员会来说也是一个艰难的决定，但是对选举的成功交接和民主的稳定来说是必须的。雅库布表示出于法律问题要推迟原定的投票时间，但是执政的“进步国会”党和反对党人民民主党都批评了选举委员会准备不足，然后互相谴责对方企图操纵选举。双方都敦促冷静。\n罗马天主教教会就虐待儿童的指控免去了前主教西奥多·麦卡里克的职务。梵蒂冈方面表示，教宗方济各已经开除了他的神职，并且不允许对该决定提起上诉。西奥多·麦卡里克曾是前华盛顿特区的大主教。以下是马丁·巴希尔的报道。昨晚，西奥多·麦卡里克收到教会通知开除了他的神职。今天早晨梵蒂冈的一份简短声明表示，已认定他严重滥用权力，对未成年人和成年人犯下罪行。去年七月，他辞去了主教职务，这也是一百多年来的首次，原因是证据确凿的指控称他性侵了一名16岁辅祭男孩，并且猥亵了另一名14岁的男孩。\n由总理纳伦德拉·莫迪隆重宣布的印度最快火车在一天后出现故障。以下是安德布里森·安迪罗杰的报道。先进的的范德·巴拉特快车当时正从印度城市瓦拉纳西返回，据报道，首次发车之后一节车厢的制动器卡住了。司机发现最后四节车厢冒烟不久后，所有的车厢失去动力。车上大部分都是铁道官员和记者，他们不得不坐另一辆火车返回德里。有报道称火车撞上了一头离群的牛。据悉，该火车预计可以将德里和瓦拉纳西的行程减少6个小时。新的火车服务预计将在周日开启商用。以上就是最新的BBC新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
</blogs>
