<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--以下特殊字符不可使用：-->
<!--&rsquo;全局替换为'-->
<!--<br/>换行符全局替换为\n-->
<blogs>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>1</id>
        <date>November 27, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Difficult Customer</title>
        <description>
            A: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I’ll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order? B: No, I’m still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What’s good here?
        </description>
        <cover>images/waitress.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0001pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Difficult Customer **\nA: Good evening. My name is Fabio, I'll be your waiter for tonight. May I take your order?\nB: No, I'm still working on it. This menu is not even in English. What's good here?\nA: For you sir, I would recommend spaghetti and meatballs.\nB: Does it come with coke and fries?\nA: It comes with either soup or salad and a complimentary glass of wine, Sir.\nB: I'll go with the spaghetti and meatballs, salad and the wine.\nA: Excellent choice, your order will be ready soon.\nB: How soon is soon?\nA: Twenty minutes?\nB: You know what? I'll just go grab a burger across the street.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**still working on** : not yet completed, need more time\n**would recommend** : suggest\n**complimentary**: free\n**go with**: to choose, pick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>2</id>
        <date>November 28, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Calling In Sick</title>
        <description>
            A: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you? B: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.
        </description>
        <cover>images/calling.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/B0002pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Elementary - Calling In Sick**\nA: Hello, Daniel speaking, how may I help you?\nB: Hi, Daniel, Julie here.\nA: Hi, Julie, how are you?\nB: Actually, I'm feeling quite ill today.\nA: I'm sorry to hear that. What's wrong?\nB: I think I'm coming down with the flu. I have a headache, a sore throat a runny nose and I'm feeling slightly feverish.\nA: I see... so you're calling in sick?\nB: Yes, I was hoping to take the day off to recover.\nA: OK, then. Try and get some rest.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**was hoping** :to kindly expect\n**calling in sick**: report that you will not go to work because you are sick\n**coming down:**getting, acquiring\n**quite ill**: very sick</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>3</id>
        <date>November 29, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Hotel Upgrade</title>
        <description>
            A: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?
        </description>
        <cover>images/hotel.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0003pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Hotel Upgrade **\nA: Good afternoon. What can I do for you?\nB: I'd like to check in please. I have a reservation under the name Anthony Roberts.\nA: All right R.O.B.E.R.T.S... Oh, Mr. Roberts we'vebeen expecting you&amp; and here is your keycard to the presidential suite.\nB: But there must be some mistake; my reservationwas for a standard room.\nA: Are you sure? Let me double check .\nB: Yeah&amp;Here, this is my confirmation number.\nA: You're right Mr. Roberts, there seems to be a mixup,unfortunately we're overbooked at the moment.\nB: So..\nA: Not to worry. We're pleased to offer you a complimentaryupgrade.\nB: Presidential suite baby!\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**check in** :register at a hotel or airport\n**under the name:** name used for the reservation</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>4</id>
        <date>November 30, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - I need an assistant</title>
        <description>
            A: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.
        </description>
        <cover>images/fist-bumps.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0004pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Office - I need an assistant!**\nA: ...like I told you before, we just don't have the resources to hire you an assistant.\nB: I understand that, but the fact is we're understaffed.\nA: The timing is just not right. The economy is bad,and it's too risky to take on new staff.\nB: Yeah, I guess you're right.... here's an idea, what if we hire an intern? She would take some of the weight off my shoulders.\nA: She?\nB: Yeah, you know, a recent graduate. She could give me a hand with some of these projects and we could keep our costs down.\nA: That sounds reasonable... let me see what I can do.\nA: Tony, I'd like to introduce you to your new assistant.\nB: OK, great! Let's meet her!\nC: Hi, I'm Adam.\nB: Oh... hi... I'm Tony...\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**resources** : money\n**understaffed** : not enough people to do the job\n**the timing is just not right** : it is not a good time now\n**weight off my shoulders** : remove pressure or stress</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="markdown_tools.html">
        <id>5</id>
        <date>November 30, 2018</date>
        <title>Tool - Markdown实时预览及Html互转</title>
        <description>
            Markdown 是一种简单的、轻量级的标记语法。用户可以使用诸如 * # 等简单的标记符号以最小的输入代价生成极富表现力的文档。
        </description>
        <cover>images/markdown.jpg</cover>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>6</id>
        <date>December 1, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Cut In Line</title>
        <description>
            A: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.
        </description>
        <cover>images/queue.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0005pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**Daily Life - Cut In Line**\nA: I can't believe it took us two hours to get here. The traffic in New York is unbelievable.\nB: Yeah, but just relax honey, we're here and we're going on vacation. In a few hours we'll be in Hawaii, and you'll be on the golf course.\nA: Oh no! Look at that line! It must be a mile long!There's no way I'm waiting for another two hours.\nB: Honey... don't...\nC: Hey man, the end of the line is over there.\nA: Yeah...\nC: No seriously, I was here first, and you can't cut in line like this.\nA: Says who?\nC: I do!\nA: So sue me!\nC: Alright...that's it....\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**There's no way** : impossible\n**cut in line** : jump the queue (in British English)</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>7</id>
        <date>December 2, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Road Trip</title>
        <description>
            A: So, are we all ready to go? B: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.
        </description>
        <cover>images/roadtrip.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0006pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>**The Weekend - Road Trip**\nA: So, are we all ready to go?\nB: Yup, I think so. The car's packed; we have munchies and music, and the map's in the car.\nA: Did you get the camera?\nB: Got it! Did you fill up the tank?\nA: Yup, it's all set.\nB: You're sure we're not forgetting anything?\nA: I'm sure... we've got all our bases covered.\nB: Well&amp; let's get going then! I love road trips!\nB: Um... do you think we can make a pit stop?\nA: But we've only been on the road for ten minutes.\nB: I know, but I forgot to go to the bathroom before we left.\n**Key Vocabulary**\n**all ready to go**:prepared, ready to leave\n**packed**:full, everything is inside\n**fill up the tank**:put gas in the car\n**all set**:ready</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>8</id>
        <date>December 3, 2018</date>
        <title>Authentic English - Computer Virus</title>
        <description>
            A: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.
        </description>
        <cover>images/computer-stethoscope.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../authentic-english/sound/kouyu/englishpod/200911/C0007pb.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>"**The Office - Computer Virus! **\nA: Oh great! This stupid computer froze again!That's the third time today! Hey Samuel, can you come take a look at my PC? It's acting upagain. It must have a virus or something.\nB: Just give me a second; I'll be right up.\nB: I ran a virus scan on your computer, and it turns out that you have a lot of infected files!\nA: But I'm quite careful when I'm browsing the internet, I have no idea how I could have picked up a virus.\nB: Well, you have to make sure that your anti-virus software is updated regularly; yours wasn't up to date, that's probably what was causing your problems.\nA: Ok. Anything else?\nB: Yeah, try not to kick or hit the computer!\nA: Um yeah; Sorry about that."</markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>9</id>
        <date>December 4, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - G20 Summit is Holding in Buenos Aires</title>
        <description>
            World leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine.
        </description>
        <cover>images/G20.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181203_0014852xLB.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nWorld leaders are in Buenos Aires for a G20 summit already marked by tensions and disagreements, many of them caused by President Trump's combative stance on trade and climate change. Tensions have been further inflamed by Russia's military action against Ukraine. James Landale is at the summit. President Putin is likely to face tough questions over Russia seizure of Ukrainian vessels. President Trump said he wouldn't meet the Russian leader until the confrontation was resolved. And Mohammad bin Salman the Saudi Crown Prince is also in town looking to repair his reputation after the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi. But for all these tensions, European leaders said it was important for the G20 to come together to tackle the world's problems.\nBefore the summit formally got underway, the United States, Canada and Mexico signed a new trade deal. This is seen as a victory for Mr. Trump who opposed the previous agreement. Andrew Walker reports. Many barriers to commerce between the US, Canada and Mexico were removed or reduced by the North American Free Trade Agreement, which came into force a quarter of a century ago. But President Trump called it the worst trade deal ever. Now, the three leaders have signed a replacement which keeps much of the original agreement. But it includes additional provisions that will, for example, make it more expensive for car makers to use parts from outside the region and will mean more opportunities for US dairy farmers to sell their milk products in Canada. It has been a contentious negotiation and there were reports that late disputes about the dairy issue might have held up the signing ceremony.\nInternational Olympic Committee says it's freezing all planning for the boxing tournament at the Tokyo 2020 Olympics because of concerns about the sport's governing body. It's launching an inquiry into the International Boxing Association AIBA over its governance, ethics and financial management. Our sports correspondent Alex Capstick reports. The IOC halted preparations for the Olympic boxing tournament in Tokyo, including the qualifying process following talks among the organization's leading officials in the Japanese capital. For several months, serious concerns have been expressed over the way the sport's governing body has been run. It came to a head earlier this month when Gafur Rahimov was elected as president of AIBA, despite allegations that he's part of an international criminal network, something he's always denied. But whatever is ultimately decided regarding the future of AIBA, the IOC still wants boxing to be part of the Tokyo Games.\nWorld news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181204.jpg](images/bbc-20181204.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n世界各国领导人现正在布宜诺斯艾利斯参加G20峰会，峰会已表现出了紧张和分歧，许多是因为特朗普总统在贸易和气候变化上的好斗态度引发。俄罗斯对乌克兰采取的军事行动又进一步加重了大会的紧张氛围。以下是詹姆斯·兰德尔的报道。普京很有可能会因俄罗斯扣押乌克兰船只而面临尖锐的提问。特朗普表示在对峙解决之前他不会与普京见面。沙特王储穆罕默德·本·萨尔曼也来到了这里，试图挽回一下因沙特记者贾马尔·哈苏及被杀事件而受损的名声。虽然本次大会充满了紧张气氛，欧洲领导人表示最重要的是各国能聚在一起解决世界问题。\n在峰会正式开始之前，美国、加拿大和墨西哥签署了一份新的贸易协议。这被认为是特朗普的胜利，因为他反对之前的协议。以下是安德鲁·沃克的报道。北美自由贸易协定消除或降低了很多美国、加拿大和墨西哥之间的贸易壁垒，该协议在25年之前正式生效，但是特朗普称这是有史以来最差的贸易协议。现在这三名领导人已经签署了一个替代协议，保留了很多之前的协议内容。但是也新增了一些附加条款，比如汽车生产商使用该区域之外零件将会更加昂贵，另外也会更有利于美国奶农向加拿大销售奶制品。协商的过程很激烈，有报道称近期的乳制品问题争端或延长签字仪式。\n国际奥组委称正在冻结2020年东京奥运会的拳击比赛筹备工作，原因其管理机构存在问题。它正在对国际拳击联盟AIBA的管理情况、道德和金融状况进行调查。以下是本台体育通讯员亚历克斯·卡普斯蒂克的报道。国际奥组委停止了东京奥运会拳击比赛的筹备工作，包括资格赛，此前奥组委主要官员在日本首都举行了会谈。几个月以来，国际奥组委一直都在担心该体育机构的运作方式。本月初，加弗尔·拉西莫夫成功当选 AIBA主席，事情也达到了非做不可的地步，拉西莫夫被指是国际犯罪网络成员，但他本人否认。无论AIBA的前景如何，国际奥组委仍然希望拳击项目出现在东京奥运会上。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>10</id>
        <date>December 5, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Yellow Vest Movement in Paris</title>
        <description>
            The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances.
        </description>
        <cover>images/yellow-vest-movement.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc20181204_3542471yYn.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>I'm Stuart Mackintosh with the BBC News, hello. The French President Emmanuel Macron has condemned the outbreak of violence at anti-government protests in Paris, saying it had nothing to do with a lawful expression of legitimate grievances. He was speaking after the latest protest saw the demonstrators attack police and spray graffiti on the Arch of Triumph. This report from Hugh Schofield. Demonstrators, some of them clearly agitators rather than bona fide yellow vests have fought running battles with police. They have torn up cobblestones to serve as projectiles and set fire to cars and even buildings. Police responded with tear gas and anti-riot grenades. What's been happening today takes the "yellow vest" movement to a new level. The scenes unforgettably vivid are of destruction. President Macron who's in Argentina at the G20 needs urgently to find a way out of this confrontation.\nMexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has promised to scrap the neoliberal economic policies of the past twenty five years. Speaking at his inauguration ceremony and Congress, Mr. Lopez Obrador said neoliberalism had led to poverty, crime and mass migration in Mexico and promised a new start. Starting from now, a peaceful and orderly transformation has begun that at the same time will be profound and radical, because we will end the corruption and impunity that impede Mexico's rebirth. The left-wing leader also announced the creation of a free trade zone in a vast area next to the border with the United States, where taxes will be lower and the minimum wage higher.\nThe African Union says it's worried about the lack of progress of peace talks for Burundi and has urged all sides to refrain from taking any judicial action that could cause further rifts. The warning comes a day after the Burundian government issued an international arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya and sixteen high ranking officials. Will Ross reports. The warning from the African Union appears to be aimed at the government of Burundi. Peace talks with the opposition have stalled and some feared the government has risked opening old ethnic wounds by issuing the arrest warrant for the former President Pierre Buyoya. The move is an awkward one for the African Union because Mr. Buyoya is now working for the AU as its special representative in Mali. The 1993 assassination of President Melchior Ndadaye, the country's first Hutu leader triggered the civil war in which three hundred thousand people were killed. That was Will Ross. This is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181205.jpg](images/bbc-20181205.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n大家好，我是斯图亚特·麦金托什，欢迎收听BBC新闻。法国总统马克龙谴责了巴黎反政府游行暴力事件，称这根本不是表达不满的合法方式。在最近的示威活动中，游行人群袭击了警察，还在凯旋门上涂鸦，之后法国总统做了这番讲话。以下是休·斯科菲尔德的报道。许多游行者很明显是鼓动者而不是真正的“黄马甲”抗议人士，他们与警察打起了游击战。他们将鹅卵石当作投掷物，点燃汽车甚至是建筑物。警察用催泪弹和防爆手雷进行了反击。今天发生的事情让“黄马甲”运动再次升级。这里到处都是毁灭的景象，让人历历在目。总统马克龙正在阿根廷参加G20峰会，他正迫切地想解决冲突的方法。\n墨西哥新总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔承诺将会取消施行25年的新自由经济政策。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔在就职仪式和国会上表示新自由经济政策导致了贫穷、犯罪和大规模移民，他承诺墨西哥将会有一个新的开始。现在，一个和平有序的变革已经开始，同时它也是深刻彻底的，因为我们会根除阻碍墨西哥重生的贪污和法外逃脱。这名左翼领导人还宣布将会在与美国接壤的广阔区域开创一个自由贸易区，这里的税率将会更低，最低工资也会更高。\n非洲联盟称他们对布隆迪和平谈判没有进展感到担心，并且敦促各方避免采取可能导致分歧加深的任何司法行动。在非盟发出警告的前一天，布隆迪政府发布了对前总统皮埃尔·布约亚和16名高级官员的国际逮捕令。以下是威尔·罗斯的报道。非盟的警告很明显是针对布隆迪政府的。布隆迪政府与反对党的和平谈判已经陷于僵局，一些人担心政府将会通过发布前总统皮埃尔·布约亚的逮捕令重新揭开之前的民族伤疤。此举让非盟处于一个尴尬的境地，因为布约亚现正为非盟工作，在马里任特派代表。1993年，该国首个胡图族领袖，总统梅尔基奥尔·恩达达耶被刺杀，这引发了国内战争，导致30万人被杀。以上是威尔·罗斯的报道。BBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
    <blog location="english.html">
        <id>11</id>
        <date>December 6, 2018</date>
        <title>BBC News - Mexico's new President start investigating the disappearance of 43 students</title>
        <description>
            On his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago.
        </description>
        <cover>images/安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔.jpg</cover>
        <audio>../bbc/sound/bbc1205_2603183KA2.mp3</audio>
        <markdown-content>This is the BBC News. Hello, I'm Jonathan Izard.\nOn his first full day in office, Mexico's new President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has signed a decree creating a truth commission to investigate the disappearance of 43 students four years ago. The incident sparked weeks of protests. Will Grant reports.\nThe whole government is going to help with this plan. President Lopez Obrador told the victims' families who had gathered for the event, "and I can assure you that there will be no impunity either in this sad and painful case or in any other." It has been more than four years since the group of 43 young men and women were disappeared allegedly by State Security Forces. The lack of meaningful action or any prosecution of those involved was a stain on the previous administration, and human rights groups have long called for a new investigation.\nOne of Afghanistan's top sports officials has admitted for the first time that players in the women's national football squad and in other sports have been sexually abused and the problem must be addressed. The allegations of years of rape, sexual harassment and sexual coercion have been voiced publicly by a former captain of the women's football team. Jill McGivering reports.\nThe comments by Hafizullah Rahimithe, the head of Afghanistan's National Olympic Committee are the first official acknowledgment that the allegations of abuse made by some Afghan women footballers may be credible. Khalida Popal, a former team captain has been trying for years to highlight sexual assault, harassment and bullying by coaches and officials, which she claims to have witnessed and had reported to her. Officials in the Afghanistan Football Federation say the claims are untrue. Women involved in other sports have also spoken to the BBC,but are frightened of being identified.\nAn eighty-year-old woman has become the latest casualty of anti-government protests in France. She died in hospital in the southern city of Marseille after being hit in the face by a tear gas canister as she drew the shutters of her fourth floor apartment during rioting on Saturday. Three other deaths have been blamed on the protests.\nTwo jailed Catalan separatist leaders have announced that they're going on hunger strike from Tuesday, joining two colleagues who stopped eating at the weekend. Joaquim Forn and Josep Rull, said they were protesting against the Constitutional Court's refusal to let them appeal to European Courts against pretrial detention. The trials of nine Catalan separatists who have been held in jail for up to fourteen months are due to begin in January. Uruguay has rejected an asylum request by the former President of Peru Alan Garcia, who's under investigation for corruption. He entered Uruguay's embassy in Lima two weeks ago after a court banned him from leaving the country for the next eighteen months. Mr. Garcia says the allegations are politically motivated. The Uruguayan government praised Peru's legal system.\nThis is the world news from the BBC.\n![bbc-20181206.jpg](images/bbc-20181206.jpg)\n**参考译文：**\n这里是BBC新闻，大家好，我是乔纳森·伊泽德。\n在墨西哥新任总统安德烈斯·曼努埃尔·洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔就职的第一天，他签署了一项法令启动一个真相调查委员会，调查4年前43名学生失踪一案。该事件也引发了数周的抗议活动。以下是威尔·格兰特的报道。\n政府将全力协助实施该计划。洛佩斯·奥夫拉多尔总统对集结的受害者家属表示，“我能向你们保证，在该起沉重悲痛的案中或是在任何其他的案件中，凶手都逃脱不了惩罚。”当时据国家安全部队称有43名年轻男女失踪，此时距此已过去四年多的时间了。上一届政府没有实质性作为，也没有对涉案人员提起诉讼，这已经成为他们的一个污点，另外，人权组织在很久之前就要求对此展开新的调查。\n一名阿富汗体育部门高官首次承认国家女子足球队以及其他体育队的运动员受到性侵害，并称该问题必须要得到解决。女子足球队的前队长公开发声，称她们受到多年的强奸、性骚扰和性胁迫。以下是吉尔·麦吉弗林的报道。\n阿富汗国家奥委会主席哈飞祖拉·拉西梅斯所做出的评论是官方首次承认，阿富汗女足队员提出的性侵指控或许是可信的。哈莉达·博帕尔是一名前队长，多年来她一直试图曝光球队教练和官员的性侵、性骚扰和霸凌行为，她声称曾亲眼目睹也向主席报告过这些行为。阿富汗足协官员表示这些指控并非事实。其他项目的女队员也向BBC说了这件事，但她们害怕被认出来。\n一名80岁的女性成为法国反政府游行活动的又一位遇难者。她在法国南部城市马赛市的医院中去世，死因是在周六暴乱中，她在四楼房间里拉百叶窗时被一枚催泪弹击中面部。还有其他三名遇难者死于抗议活动中。\n两名被监禁的加泰罗尼亚分裂主义领导人宣布他们将从周二开始绝食抗议，他们的两名同事早在上周就开始了绝食。乔吉姆·弗恩和约瑟夫·罗尔表示，他们是在抗议宪法法庭拒绝让他们就审前羁押向欧洲法庭提起上诉，狱中的九名加泰罗尼亚分裂主义分子被判监禁14个月之久，并将从一月份开始服刑。乌拉圭拒绝了秘鲁前总统阿兰·加西亚的庇护请求，现在他正在接受腐败调查。两周之前，法院判定他在未来18个月内不得出国，之后他来到乌拉圭驻利马大使馆。加西亚表示这些指控都带有政治动机的，而乌拉圭则称赞了秘鲁的法律体系。\nBBC国际新闻。
        </markdown-content>
    </blog>
</blogs>
